<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText>
    <![CDATA[
        <p><tags ms.service="announcement" ms.date="" wacn.date="" wacn.lang="cn"/></p>
        <h1>Azure 紧急提示: 关于自查整改“翻墙”行为的通知！</h1>
        <h2>尊敬的客户，</h2>
        <p>根据电信法律法规的规定，以及工信部与国家相关网络监管部门的要求，任何公司或个人不能为非法“翻墙”代理网站提供托管服务，或者非法挂载任何可以连通国外网络的 VPN 服务。近期，监管部门已发现有几家 Azure 客户违反相关规定，要求我们立即关闭其部署。</p>
        <p>我们随时会收到来自监管部门的通知，要求关闭此类网站或部署。<strong>为避免不必要的风险与损失，我们建议您立即进行自查整改。如您有涉及以上违法违规行为，请立即停止，否则将承担违规行为所造成的一切后果。</strong></p>
        <p>如有疑问，您可致电我们的客服热线 400-089-0365。</p>
        <h2>Dear Customer,</h2>
        <p>According to the telecom regulations and the requirement of MIIT and Internet supervision agency, no company or individual can provide hosting service for illegal “over the wall” proxy sites, or illegally mount any VPN service to abroad. Recently, the regulators have found several Azure customers violated the related regulations and demanded immediate shut-down of service deployment.</p>
        <p>We will continuously receive notification from the regulators to close such sites or shut down service deployment. <strong>In order to avoid unnecessary risks and losses, we recommend that you conduct self-examination and rectification immediately. In case you have involved in any above illegal behaviors, please stop immediately. Otherwise, you would assume all the consequences of such violation.</strong></p>
        <p>If you have any questions, you may call our customer service hotline at 400-089-0365.</p>
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Azure 紧急提示: 关于自查整改“翻墙”行为的通知！- Azure 云计算</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription>
        <![CDATA[
            Azure 紧急提示: 关于自查整改“翻墙”行为的通知！
        ]]>    
    </metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
