<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2014-10-20T09:41:59" urlName="backup" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="backup" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/backup.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/backup@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Backup</h2>
                        <h4>Simple and reliable server backup to the cloud</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_backup_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_backup_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Azure Backup is a reliable, low-cost, and scalable solution, allowing for backup of local data onto the cloud. Without any capital investment, you can protect your key business data with the lowest operating expenses.</p>
                <p>Azure Backup now enables backup of virtual machines on Azure through a few simple steps, and also permits placing the restore points on the cloud storage. Whenever necessary, you can respond from the restore points to meet various demands for protecting Azure Virtual Machines.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active">
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>Backup services are charged by the size of every protected instance, at an increment of 500 GB. In addition, Azure storage space is charged individually, allowing for reduction in long-lasting storage cost. Customers can make a flexible selection between LRS or GRS Block Blob Storage (please refer to the pricing details for <a id="pricing-bankup_storage-blob" href="/pricing/details/storage/blob/" target="_blank">Block Blob for general-purpose Storage Accounts</a>).</p>
                    <!-- <p>从2016年4月1日起， 价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Data stored per protected instance per month</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Instances with 0 to 50 GB (including 50 GB) of data</td>
                            <td>￥31.65/protected instance + storage used</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Instances with 50 GB to 500 GB (including 500 GB) of data</td>
                            <td>￥63.29/protected instance + storage used</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Instances with more than 500 GB of data</td>
                            <td>Increments of ￥63.29 every 500 GB + storage used</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQs</h2>
                    <em class="pos-em">Expand all</em>
                    <h3>Overview</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question1">Which content am I being charged for in the new pricing model? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The new pricing has two components:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Used Azure Block Blob Storage capacity: used for storing backup data and restore points. Storage redundancy options are also flexible. For the backup vault, customers can choose between locally redundant storage (LRS) and geo-redundant storage (GRS).</li>
                                        <li>Price of Azure Backup software for protected instances.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                    <p>This content will be listed on your Azure monthly bills as individual line items.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question2">Why did you modify the pricing model?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>When maintaining data for a short period of time, a model that charges customers for the stored backup data for every GB is effective. With continued improvements in <a id="pri_bankup_keep2" href="http://azure.microsoft.com/zh-cn/updates/azure-backup-increases-features-and-supports-additional-dpm-workloads/">long-term retention</a> functions in Azure Backup, as well as continuous increases in the amount of data to be backed up, the GB charging model brings high costs for customers that need to maintain data for a long period of time. The new business model enables customers to utilize the scale benefits brought by Azure storage space while continuously enjoying the enhanced functions of Azure Backup.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question3">Do I have to pay for restoration and Internet exports?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>We will not charge customers for any restore operations and/or outgoing network bandwidth (exports) relating to restore operations.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question4">How much can I expect to save on costs? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The main driving factor for this modification is allowing customers to get huge value by using Azure Backup. Compared with the GB charging model, customers can save costs by up to 52% when using LRS Block Blob Storage and the new pricing. </p>
                                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                                        <tr>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Size of protected instances (GB)</strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>AZURE Backup price per GB (RMB)</strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Saving on costs with the new pricing and usage of LRS Block BLOB storage (RMB)</strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Saving on costs with the new pricing and usage of GRS Block BLOB storage (RMB)</strong></th>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>50</td>
                                            <td>￥60</td>
                                            <td>￥63 (-5%)</td>
                                            <td>￥83.5 (-39%)</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>100</td>
                                            <td>￥120</td>
                                            <td>￥126 (-5%)</td>
                                            <td>￥167 (-39%)</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>250</td>
                                            <td>￥300</td>
                                            <td>￥187.5 (38%)</td>
                                            <td>￥290 (3%)</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>500</td>
                                            <td>￥600</td>
                                            <td>￥290 (52%)</td>
                                            <td>￥495 (18%)</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1000</td>
                                            <td>￥1,200</td>
                                            <td>￥580 (52%)</td>
                                            <td>￥990 (18%)</td>
                                        </tr>
                                    </table>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <h3>Protected Servers and Instances</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question6">What are protected instances? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Protected instances refer to the billing units used in Azure Backup. The software overhead is charged according to the size of the protected computers (also called “size of front-end”). Therefore, larger protected instances mean more expenses charged to customers. For instance, if a document server with a volume of 2,200 GB is protected in Azure Backup, customers are charged ￥316.45/month (2,200 GB/500 GB = 4.4, rounded to 5 in increments of 500 GB , with each increment charged ￥63.29).</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question7">Which types of protected instances are included?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>There are three types:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Virtual Machines: can be Hyper-V virtual machines</li>
                                        <li>Windows or Linux server computers: can be physical host computers or guest virtual machines. These computers generally have some applications requiring backup or some running workloads. The common workloads include: document server roles for Microsoft SQL Server, Microsoft Exchange, Microsoft SharePoint, Microsoft Dynamics, and Windows Server.</li>
                                        <li>Windows Client Computers</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question8">How do I estimate the quantity of protected instances? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You can estimate the quantity of protected instances by summing up the following items:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Quantity of virtual machines</li>
                                        <li>Quantity of computers equipped with DPM proxy (excluding Hyper-V host)</li>
                                        <li>Quantity of computers equipped with Azure Backup proxy</li>
                                    </ul>
                                    <p>The bill for every protected instance will depend on its front-end size.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question9">How do I estimate the front-end size of protected instances? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The “front-end” size of a protected instance refers to the sum (before compression) of all data sizes from the computer to be protected in Azure Backup. Data not protected on the computer will not be included in the size of a protected instance.</p>
                                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                                        <tr>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Protected Instances </strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Size of Protected Instances </strong></th>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Virtual Machines</td>
                                            <td>Used size of the virtual hard disk to back up to Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Microsoft SQL Server</td>
                                            <td>Database and instances requiring backup onto Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Microsoft Document Server</td>
                                            <td>Documents and folders to be backed up onto volumes on Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Microsoft SharePoint</td>
                                            <td>Total size of SharePoint content field to be protected on Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Microsoft Exchange</td>
                                            <td>Size of email on the Exchange Server requiring backup onto Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>Microsoft Windows (Client)</td>
                                            <td>Documents and folders to be backed up onto volumes on Azure</td>
                                        </tr>
                                    </table>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question10">What should I do if my protected instances are very small?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>We provide layers of smaller scale, which are an ideal option for small-scale servers and client computers. If the front-end size of the protected instance is less than 50 GB, the instance belongs to the minimum price layer of ￥31.65/month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question11">If I protect the computer on Azure starting in the middle of a month, do I still need to pay the full price for the protected instances? </a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>No, the cost is prorated according to the number of days the computer is protected in the month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question12">If I modify the retention policy of backup data and store more data on Azure, do I need to pay more fees for this part of the protected instances?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>No, this part of the protected instances will not be charged according to the data size (back-end data) stored in Azure. Azure Backup storage data is charged in addition to the rate of Azure Block Blob storage. The fees of the protected instances are charged completely on the basis of the front-end size, without being affected by different backup and retention policies.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_question13">Do I need to upgrade my Azure Backup proxy?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Yes, the new pricing can be used only after the Azure Backup proxy is upgraded to the latest edition. Use of the proxy for older editions will yield adverse effects on the front-end size of the protected instances being charged.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <h3>Backup Storage Costs</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor1">With regard to storage, which content am I being charged for?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>After using the new pricing, the backup data (also called "back-end size") stored in Azure will be charged according to the Block Blob rate in the corresponding region.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor2">Does Block Blob pricing apply to LRS or GRS storage?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>This depends on the storage options selected for the backup vault. The storage options for backup vaults include: locally redundant storage (LRS) or geo-redundant storage (GRS).</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor3">Can I have two different vaults, namely, one using LRS and the other using GRS?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Yes, this is supported. The backup data in every vault will be charged by the corresponding LRS or GRS Block Blob rate in the vault’s region. Customers have full control over Azure storage space billing for selected vault options. </p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor4">When should I select LRS storage and when should I obtain GRS storage?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The Azure <a id="bp_pri_stor4" href="/home/features/storage/#pricing">Storage Pricing Page</a> provides basic guidance relating to the value of LRS and GRS storage types.</p>
                                    <p>In ideal conditions, the backup data should be placed on GRS if the recovered object needs to be used immediately. This ensures that there are always copies of other backup data for time-critical recovery.</p>
                                    <p>Price-sensitive customers seeking to maintain inexpensive storage (in lieu of local disk) on a long-term basis will find huge value in using Local Redundant Storage.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor5">Which factors will affect the backup storage capacity used?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The total backup data size ("back-end size") maintained in Azure Backup for specific protected instances may vary according to the following factors:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Retention period of backup data.</li>
                                        <li>Net changes stored in every restore point.</li>
                                        <li>Compression levels implemented for backup data.</li>
                                        <li>Frequency of planned backup jobs.</li>
                                        <li>Any correlated backup metadata.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Backup_price_stor6">How do I ascertain the backup storage capacity used?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>As with’ current pricing, you’re not required to pay for Azure Backup storage transactions. This content is included as a part of the software price you pay.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <h3>Data backup from DPM to Azure</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="backup_price_dpm1">Are there examples of how to apply the pricing model to various workloads and sizes?</a>
                                <section>
                                   <p>After using the new pricing, the backup data (also called "back-end size") stored in Azure will be charged according to the Block Blob rate in the corresponding region.</p>
                                    <table border="0" style="margin-bottom: 30px; width: 100%; margin-left: 0px;">
                                        <tr>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Host Computer</strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Workload</strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Size of Protected Instances </strong></th>
                                            <th align="left"><strong>Billing Amount</strong></th>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1 Windows host computer</td>
                                            <td>Windows Server 2012 (documents/folders backup)</td>
                                            <td>300 GB</td>
                                            <td>￥63.29/month</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>3 Windows host computers</td>
                                            <td>
                                                Windows Exchange<br>
                                                Windows Exchange<br>
                                                Windows Exchange
                                            </td>
                                            <td>
                                                600 GB<br>
                                                1,300 GB<br>
                                                400 GB
                                            </td>
                                            <td>
                                                ￥126.58/month<br>
                                                ￥189.87/month<br>
                                                ￥63.29/month
                                            </td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1 Windows client computer</td>
                                            <td>Windows 8.1 (documents/folders backup)</td>
                                            <td>25 GB</td>
                                            <td>￥31.65/month</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1 Hyper-V Virtual Machine</td>
                                            <td>Virtual Machine backup</td>
                                            <td>30 GB</td>
                                            <td>￥31.65/month</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1 Windows guest computer</td>
                                            <td>Windows Server 2012 (documents/folders backup)</td>
                                            <td>120 GB</td>
                                            <td>￥63.29/month</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>1 Windows guest computer</td>
                                            <td>Microsoft SQL Server (independent)</td>
                                            <td>600 GB</td>
                                            <td>￥126.58/month</td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>3 Windows guest computers</td>
                                            <td>
                                                <span>Microsoft SQL Server (cluster):</span>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Computer 1: 50 databases</li>
                                                    <li>Computer 2: 75 databases</li>
                                                    <li>Computer 3: 20 databases</li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </td>
                                            <td>
                                                70 GB<br>80 GB<br>15 GB<br/>
                                                <span style="height:30px; display:block;"></span>
                                                <br>
                                            </td>
                                            <td>
                                                ￥63.29/month+<br>￥63.29/month+<br>￥31.65/month<br/>
                                                <span>Note: if the databases move around in the cluster, the size of the backup is used for calculation</span>
                                            </td>
                                        </tr>
                                        <tr>
                                            <td>5 Windows guest computers</td>
                                            <td>Complete SharePoint field including front-end and content database, etc.</td>
                                            <td>1,300 GB</td>
                                            <td>
                                                ￥189.87/month (size of SharePoint field is larger than 1,000 GB and smaller than 1,500 GB)
                                                <br/> Note: A SharePoint field is a special entity, which is charged on the basis of the total size of protected data in it.
                                            </td>
                                        </tr>
                                </table>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="backup_price_dpm2">I have a Microsoft SQL Server Virtual Machine with 250 GB of data. How will I be billed for Azure Backup?</a>
                                <section>
                                   <p>For a SQL Server database of a protected size of 250 GB in Azure Backup, the SQL Server is taken as the protected instance. As the size of the protected instance is larger than 50 GB but smaller than 500 GB, ￥63.29 is charged. If the virtual machine is also backed up in Azure Backup, it will be counted as another protected instance. Because the size of the virtual machine is smaller than 500 GB, ￥63.29 is charged. </p>
                                   <p>Note: Virtual machine backup and workload backup (running in a virtual machine) are charged independently</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>Azure Backup services are available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="backup-contact-page">Azure Support</a> to select self-service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
                <p>We guarantee that the availability of the backup and recovery functions of Azure Backup services reaches at least 99.9%. The availability is calculated by the monthly billing cycle. If you want to learn more about the details of our server level agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/back-up/" id="pricing_backup_sla">Service Level Agreement</a> page.</p>
                </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                                                    
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Backup Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-back-up</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Backup, data, prices, pricing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn more about the pricing details for Azure Backup. Azure Backup is a reliable, low-cost, and scalable solution, allowing for backup of local data into the cloud. Without any capital investment, you can protect your key business data with the lowest operating expenses. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing details - Backup</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
