<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-10-15T10:00:00" urlName="virtual-machines" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="cdn" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/cdn.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/cdn@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Content Delivery Network (CDN)</h2>
                        <h4>Ensure secure, reliable content delivery with broad reach</h4>                        
						<em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_cdn_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_cdn_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Azure CDN improves application performance by caching content to the location nearest the customer.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->					
					<h3>CDN outbound data transfers</h3>
                    <!--<p>自 2016 年 12 月 1 月起，将取消阶梯式收费，CDN 数据传输价格将按照目前 0 - 10 TB/月的价格进行收取。</p>-->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Service</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Standard version</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Premium version<sup style="color:#e66102; font-weight: bold"> 2</sup></strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN data transfer (0-10 TB<sup>1</sup>/month)</td>
                            <td>￥0.19/GB</td>
                            <td>￥0.45/GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN data transfer (10-50 TB/month)</td>
                            <td>￥0.16/GB</td>
                            <td>￥0.42/GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN data transfer (50-100 TB/month)</td>
                            <td>￥0.13/GB</td>
                            <td>￥0.39/GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN data transfer (more than 100 TB/month)</td>
                            <td>￥0.1/GB</td>
                            <td>￥0.36/GB</td>
                        </tr>
						<!--
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN 数据传输（500 - 1024 TB/月）</td>
                            <td>¥0.22/GB</td>
                            <td>¥0.44/GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN 数据传输（1024 - 5120 TB/月）</td>
                            <td>¥0.19/GB</td>
                            <td>¥0.40/GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CDN 数据传输（超过 5120 TB/月）</td>
                            <td><a id="CDN_contact_us" href="/support/contact/">联系我们</a></td>
                            <td><a id="CDN_price_us" href="/support/contact/">联系我们</a></td>
                        </tr>
						-->
                    </table>
                    <p><sup>1</sup> 1 TB = 1,000 GB</p>
					<p><sup style="color:#e66102; font-weight: bold">2</sup> For customers who are still using the HTTPS service with Azure supplied certificate, the HTTPS service will continue to be charged with Premium CDN SKU.</p>
                    <p>If you have requirements for bandwidth pricing model, please reach out to your Account Executive for more details.</p>
                    <!-- <p>  自 2017 年 7 月 1 日起，用户自有证书的 HTTPS 加速服务将归为标准版 CDN 服务，高级版 CDN 服务将只包含 Azure CDN 代申请证书的 HTTPS 加速服务。</p>					
                    <p>  高级版服务自 2017 年 5 月 1 日起 降价，降幅最高达 33%，上表内高级版价格为降价后价格。</p> --> <!-- END: Table1-Content-->
                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->  
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL --> 
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_region">Which regions correspond to CN Zone 1?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>CDN data transfer pricing is based on the node location from where the transfers are served, not the end user’s location. The following geographic areas correspond to the zones for Azure CDN as listed above ：</p>
                                    <ul>
                                    <li>CN Zone 1 — China.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_premium-version">What’s the difference between Standard CDN service and Premium CDN service?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Standard CDN service refers to static contents acceleration, including Web Acceleration, Download Acceleration and Video-On-Demand Acceleration.</p>
                                    <p>Premium CDN service refers to accelerations other than the Standard CDN service, including Dynamic Acceleration and Live-streaming Acceleration.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_higher-data-transmission">Are all data transfers charged at a higher rate once the amount of data transferred each month exceeds 10 TB?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>No. Usage at each tier will be charged according to the rate for that tier. For example, if you generate 50 TB of Standard version CDN data transfers in Zone 1, the first 10 TB will be billed at a rate of ￥0.272/GB, and the remaining 40 TB will be billed at a rate of ￥0.266 per GB.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_question2">Can I designate a CDN data center to provide services to end users? </a>
                                <section>
                                   <p>No. The service will select a CDN data center based on an end user's network configuration, developers cannot decide which CDN data center to use. Users will be provided services according to their ISP's preferred location or a logically determined "closer" (not necessarily physically closer) node.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_question3">Do CDN charges include requests to Storage to retrieve data, and data transfers from Storage to the CDN location? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>No. When the CDN receives an object request for a non-edge location, it will make a request to Azure Storage to obtain the data. Operations for reading data from Storage and transferring it from Storage to the CDN will be charged at standard <a id="CDN_price_data" href="/pricing/details/data-transfer/">data transfer</a> rates.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="CDN_price_question4">What factors impact the availability of content in the CDN's local caches, and how can I reduce the need to make frequent origin requests? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The availability of content in the CDN's local caches (often called "cache efficacy" or "offload") will be influenced by many factors, including:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Expiration (“max-age”) header values</li>
                                        <li>Overall total size of the developer's content library (how much can be cached)</li>
                                        <li>Active working set (how much is currently cached)</li>
                                        <li>Traffic (how much is being provided)</li>
                                        <li>Cache churn (how often are objects being added to cache, or aging out)</li>
                                    </ul>
                                    <p>For example, a developer with higher churn and traffic has less cache efficacy than other users because objects are swapped in and out more frequently. This will lead to higher storage and data transfer charges, as more origin requests are required.</p>
                                    <p>To reduce the need to make origin requests, you can set longer max-age headers, thereby allowing the CDN to hold objects longer.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>CDN services are available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table> -->
               <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="cdn-contact-page">Azure Support</a> to select self-service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				 <p>We guarantee that CDN will respond to client requests and deliver the requested content without error at least 99.9% of the time. We will examine and accept data from any commercially reasonable independent measurement system that you choose to monitor your content. You must select a set of agents from the measurement system's list of standard agents that are generally available and represent at least five different geographical locations in major metropolitan areas of the People's Republic of China. If you want to learn more about the details of our server level agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/cdn/" id="pricing_cdn_sla">Service Level Agreement</a> page.</p>
                </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                                      
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Content Delivery Network (CDN) Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-cdn</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, CDN, pricing, data transfer, content delivery, CDN acceleration, CDN services, website acceleration, cloud CDN, API acceleration, live streaming acceleration, application acceleration, HTTPS, HTTP2</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn more about the pricing details for Azure CDN. Azure CDN is mainly priced by CDN outbound data transfers. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Content Delivery Network (CDN)</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
