<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2019-05-28T07:49:24" updateDate="2019-05-28T16:00:00" urlName="active-directory-b2c" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="en-us-active-directory-b2c" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> 
            <style>
                #aad-b2c-table-mau tr,#aad-b2c-table-separate tr{
                    background-color:rgb(255,255,255) !important;
                }
            </style>
            <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/activity_directory_b2c.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/active-directory-b2c@2x.svg" />
                        <h2>Azure Active Directory B2C</h2>
                        <h4>Consumer identity and access management for the cloud</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_active_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_active_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Azure Active Directory B2C is a cloud-based identity and access management solution for your consumer-facing web and mobile applications. It is a highly-available global service that scales to hundreds of millions of consumer identities. Built on an enterprise-grade secure platform, Azure Active Directory B2C keeps your business and your consumers protected.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <h2>Pricing details</h2>
                <h4>Monthly Active Users (MAU)</h4>
                <p>Azure Active Directory B2C is priced on a <b>Monthly Active User (MAU)</b> basis, helping customers to reduce costs and plan ahead with confidence. A MAU is counted when a unique user authenticates within a given calendar month.</p>
                <p>Azure AD B2C is billed at the following standard tier rates.* Enterprise Agreement customers will be billed at a low, flat rate.</p>
                <div class="tags-date">
                    <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                    <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimation is based on a usage of 31 days per month.</div>
                </div>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" id="aad-b2c-table-mau">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left" width="33%"><strong>MONTHLY ACTIVE USERS/MONTH</strong></th>
                            <th align="left" width="33%"><strong>GENERAL AVAILABILITY PRICE</strong></th>
                            <th align="left" width="33%"><strong>ENTERPRISE AGREEMENT PRICE</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>First 50,000</td>
                            <td>Free</td>
                            <td rowspan="5">Enterprise Agreement customers are eligible to switch to MAU-based billing which includes the Free tier of 50,000 MAUs. Subsequent Azure AD B2C usage will be billed at a low, flat rate per MAU. For more information, please contact your partner or Microsoft representative.</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Next 50,000</td>
                            <td>&yen;0.056</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Next 900,000</td>
                            <td>&yen;0.0468</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Next 9,000,000</td>
                            <td>&yen;0.0331</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Greater than 10,000,000</td>
                            <td>&yen;0.0254</td>
                        </tr>
                </table>

                <h4>Separate Charges:</h4>
                    <div class="tags-date">
                    <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                    <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimation is based on a usage of 31 days per month.</div>
                </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%" id="aad-b2c-table-separate">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left">MFA and SMS/Phone Events</th>
                            <th align="left">&yen; 0.305 per SMS/Phone event</th>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    <p>We listened carefully to customers about their needs regarding predictable, intuitive, and cost-efficient billing for customer identity solutions. With MAU-based billing, customers benefit from:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>Expanded Free tier:</b> The new Free tier stretches further by granting customers 50,000 MAUs per month-enabling more authentications per unique user than under the previous free allotment of 50,000 authentications. Most customers-with 50,000 or fewer MAUs per month-will be able to use Azure AD B2C for free.</li>
                        <li><b>Predictable forecasting:</b> Estimating monthly billing on a per MAU basis is simpler and more predictable than trying to forecast the number of monthly authentications.</li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Usage-based billing:</b> Pay only for your MAUs. Customers are not charged for a MAU`s subsequent authentications or for storing inactive users within that calendar month.
                            <p>For example, if you have 100,000 monthly active users (MAUs) using standard features, your monthly bill would be &yen; 2,800 regardless of how many times each MAU authenticates:</p>
                            <p>(50,000  MAUs x &yen;0(Free tier)) + (50,000 MAUs x &yen;0.056) = &yen;2800</p>
                            <p>A worldwide flat fee of &yen;0.305 is billed for each MFA attempt or SMS/Phone event.</p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>

            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="inentity-contact-page">Azure Support</a> to select self-service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				 <p>The free version of Azure Active Directory doesn’t offer a service level agreement. If you want to learn more about the details of our server level agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/active-directory-b2c/" id="pricing_identity_sla">Service Level Agreement</a> page.</p>
            </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                                      
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Active Directory B2C - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-identity</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>iaas, infrastructure as a service, active directory, pricing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Active Directory B2C is an identity and access management cloud solution for your consumer-facing web and mobile apps. A 1RMB Trial gets you RMB1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy an up to 99.99% service level agreement.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Azure Active Directory B2C</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
