<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2019-03-18T07:49:24" updateDate="2019-03-18T16:00:00" urlName="time-series-insights" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
      <![CDATA[
<tags ms.service="time-series-insights" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags>
	  		<style type="text/css">
            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-nav{
                padding-left: 0!important;
                margin-top: 5px;
                margin-bottom: 0;
                overflow: hidden;
            }
            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-nav li {
                list-style: none;
                float: left;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-nav li.active a {
                border-bottom: 4px solid #00a3d9;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-nav li.active a:hover {
                border-bottom: 4px solid #00a3d9;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-content .tab-panel{
                display: none;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-content .tab-panel.show-md{
                display: block;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-content .tab-panel .tab-nav li a{
                padding-left: 5px;
                padding-right: 5px;
                color: #00a3d9;
                background-color: #FFF;
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-content .tab-panel .tab-nav li.active a{
                color: #FFF;
                background-color: #00a3d9;              
            }

            .pricing-detail-tab .tab-content .tab-panel .tab-nav li a:hover{
                color: #FFF;
                background-color: #00a3d9;              
            }
            .pure-content .technical-azure-selector .tags-date a,.pure-content .technical-azure-selector p a,.pure-content .technical-azure-selector table a{
            background: 0 0;padding: 0;margin: 0 6px;height: 21px;line-height: 22px;font-size: 14px;color: #00a3d9;float: none;display: inline;
            }
	        </style> 
            
			<div class="hide-info" style="display:none;">
                <div class="bg-box"><div class="cover-bg">&nbsp;</div></div>
                <div class="msg-box"><div class="pricing-unavailable-message">Not available in the selected region</div></div>
            </div>
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/time-series-insights.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                    	<img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/time-series-insights.svg" />
                        <h2>Azure Time Series Insights</h2>
                        <h4>Instantly explore and analyze time series data in IoT solutions</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_time-series-insights_trial">Apply for trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_storage-table_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>

			<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
            </div>

			<!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector pricing-detail-tab tab-dropdown">
				<div class="tab-container-container">
				<div class="tab-container-box">
				<div class="tab-container">
					<div class="dropdown-container software-kind-container" style="display:none;">
						<label>OS/SoftWare:</label>
						<div class="dropdown-box os-tab-nav hidden-sm hidden-xs">
							<span class="selected-item">Time Series Insights</span>
							<i class="icon"></i>
							<ol class="tab-items">
                                <li class="active"><a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#tabContent1" id="home_time-series-insights">Time Series Insights</a></li>
							</ol>
						</div>
						<select class="dropdown-select software-box hidden-lg hidden-md" id="software-box">
                            <option selected="selected" data-href="#tabContent1" value="Time Series Insights">Time Series Insights</option>
						</select>
					</div>
					<div class="dropdown-container region-container">
						<label>Region:</label>
						<div class="dropdown-box os-tab-nav hidden-sm hidden-xs">
							<span class="selected-item">China East 2</span>
							<i class="icon"></i>
							<ol class="tab-items">
								<li class="active"><a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#east-china2" id="east-china2" >China East 2</a></li>
								<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#north-china2" id="north-china2" >China North 2</a></li>
								<!-- <li><a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#east-china" id="east-china" >China East</a></li>
								<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#north-china" id="north-china" >China North</a></li> -->
							</ol>
						</div>
						<select class="dropdown-select region-box hidden-lg hidden-md" id="region-box">
							<option selected="selected" data-href="#east-china2" value="east-china2">China East 2</option>
							<option data-href="#north-china2" value="north-china2">China North 2</option>
							<!-- <option data-href="#east-china" value="east-china">China East</option>
							<option data-href="#north-china" value="north-china">China North</option> -->
						</select>
					</div>
					<div class="clearfix"></div>
					</div>
				</div>
				</div>
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-content">
                    <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-3 -->
                    <div class="tab-panel" id="tabContent1">
                        <!-- BEGIN: Tab level 2 navigator 2 -->
                        <!-- BEGIN: Tab level 2 content 3 --> 
                        <div class="tab-content">
							<p>Data Processing Unit <sup>PREVIEW</sup> = &yen; 299.3 per unit per month (Each unit allows customers to process up to 100 GB/month)</p>
							<p>Additional Data Processed <sup>PREVIEW</sup> = &yen; 2.035 per GB</p>
							<p>Meta Data Storage <sup>PREVIEW</sup> = &yen; 0.407 per MB</p>
								<div class="tags-date">
									<div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
								</div>
								<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%" id="time-series-insights-analytics">
									<tr>
										<th align="left"><strong></strong></th>
										<th align="left"><strong>WARM DATA ANALYSIS (USED TO ANALYZE DATA ON AD-HOC BASIS)</strong></th>
										<th align="left"><strong>COLD DATA ANALYSIS (USED TO ANALYZE TIMESERIES-OPTIMIZED DATA)<sup>PREVIEW</sup></strong></th>
									</tr>
									<tr>
										<td>Storage<sup>PREVIEW</sup></td>
										<td>&yen; 30.528/GB</td>
										<td>Blob pricing<sup>*</sup></td>
									</tr>
									<tr>
										<td>Queries <sup>PREVIEW</sup></td>
										<td>No charge (limited to 10 concurrent queries)</td>
										<td>&yen; 0.102/GB</td>
									</tr>
								</table>
								<div class="tags-date">
									<div class="ms-date">*Cold data is stored in customers’ own Storage Account that customers can configure during Time Series Insights set up. Customers will see additional blob transaction charges for data reads and writes that Time Series Insights service will be doing over data stored in the customer-owned Azure Storage account.</div>
									<div class="ms-date">Note: Cold Data Analysis capabilities are immediately available in public preview. Warm data analysis which folds in the current in-market GA service capabilities will light up in the next few months within the same service offering.</div>
									<div class="ms-date">Customers can continue to use Time Series Insights with the old pricing model for warm, adhoc data analysis. However, we highly encourage you to use the updated offering as it offers many new capabilities with timeseries-optimized analytics as well as Pay-As-You-Go pricing, cost savings and flexibility to scale as per customer needs.</div>
								</div>

                            <div class="tags-date">
                        		<div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                        		<div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    		</div>
                            <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%" id="time-series-insights-s1-s2">
							<tr>
								<th align="left"><strong></strong></th>
								<th align="left"><strong>S1</strong></th>
								<th align="left"><strong>S2</strong></th>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Storage per unit<sup>2</sup></td>
								<td>30 GB or 30 million events<sup>1</sup></td>
								<td>300 GB or 300 million events<sup>1</sup></td>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Daily ingress per unit<sup>2,3</sup></td>
								<td>1 GB or 1 million events<sup>1</sup></td>
								<td>10 GB or 10 million events<sup>1</sup></td>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Maximum retention<sup>5,6</sup></td>
								<td>13 months<sup>5</sup></td>
								<td>13 months<sup>5</sup></td>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Queries</td>
								<td>Unlimited</td>
								<td>Unlimited</td>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Maximum number of units<sup>4</sup></td>
								<td>10</td>
								<td>10</td>
							</tr>
							<tr>
								<td>Price (per unit/month)</td>
								<td>&yen; 1526.4</td>
								<td>&yen; 13737.6</td>
							</tr>
						</table>
						<div class="tags-date">
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>1</sup> An event is a single unit of data with a timestamp. For billing purposes, we count events in 1-KB blocks. For example, a 0.8-KB actual event is billed as one event, but a 2.6-KB event is billed as three events. The maximum size of an actual event is 32 KB.</div><br />
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>2</sup> Ingress and total storage are measured by the number of events or data size, whichever comes first.</div><br/>
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>3</sup> Ingress is measured per minute. S1 can ingress up to 720 events/minute/unit and S2 can ingress 7,200 events/minute/unit.</div><br/>
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>4</sup> An environment can be scaled up to 10 times by adding more units.</div><br/>
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>5</sup> The data is retained in Time Series Insights based on the selected retention days or maximum limits.</div><br/>
							<div class="ms-date"><sup>6</sup> Retention is configurable in the Azure portal. The longest allowable retention period is a rolling year of 12 months + 1 month, which is defined as 400 days.</div>
						</div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-3 -->
                    </div>
                </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->

			<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQs</h2>
                    <em>Expand</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_why_is_azure_introducing_a_new_business_model" aria-label="Why is Azure introducing a new business model">Why is Azure introducing a new business model?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Customers have provided feedback that they would prefer pricing that allows them to scale data processing, storage and querying independent of each other. As we introduce the revamped Time Series Insights service with the new set of industrial IoT insights capabilities, we are introducing a new business model that aligns pricing with our customer usage patterns.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_What_happens_to_the_current_in-market_S1_and_S2_SKUs?" aria-label="What happens to the current in-market S1 and S2 SKUs?">What happens to the current in-market S1 and S2 SKUs?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Azure will continue to support customers who are using the S1 and S2 SKUs. However, we encourage customers move to the new business model as it offers several benefits - new set of industrial IoT insights capabilities that come with lower price points, lower total cost of solution, flexibility to pay-per-use and ability to control costs by changing data storage and querying patterns.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_What_is_included_in_the_new_Time_Series_Insights_SKU?" aria-label="What is included in the new Time Series Insights SKU?">What is included in the new Time Series Insights SKU?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>The new SKU introduces the new timeseries-optimized cold path analytics while continuing to support warm path ad-hoc data exploration capabilities. The service, at the time of public preview launch will start by supporting the cold path analytics scenarios. The service will be updated in the coming months to fold in the in-market warm path, ad-hoc analytics with the ability to route timeseries data to either one or both storage layers as your business requires.</p>
									 <p>The user experience for setting up your time series environment will include the current S1/S2 SKUs as well as the updated new SKU for the time being. We expect that over time, as the warm adhoc analytics capabilities get folded into the new SKU, we will encourage customers to move away from S1/S2 SKUs into the single, unified SKU and capabilities in the Time Series Insights offering to leverage the updated pricing benefits as well as more comprehensive capabilities of the end-to-end solution.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_Whats_included_in_the_Time_Series_Insights_S1_SKU?" aria-label="What's included in the Time Series Insights S1 SKU?">What's included in the Time Series Insights S1 SKU?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Each unit of S1 includes a maximum of 30 GB of total storage or 30 million events (whichever comes first), as well as maximum daily ingress and configurable retention. Also included is the Time Series Insights visualization experience. There is no limit on the number of users or queries that can be conducted.</p>
									 <p>For example, If you provision 1 unit of S1, you can configure your environment to retain data for up to 400 days of retention. If configured to 400 days retention, you cannot exceed an average daily ingress of 1/400th of the allotted environment (for 1 unit of S1, 30 GB). In this example, 1/400th of the total storage capacity per day is .075 GB or 75 MB.</p>
									 <p>Another example-if you configure your environment to retain data for 180 days with one S1 unit, you cannot exceed daily ingress of .166 GB (166 MB) per day. If your ingress rate exceeds .166 GB per day, your data will not be stored for 180 days. If, for example, your ingress rate averaged .189 GB per day, you would realize just over 158 days of retention (30 GB/.189 = 158.73 days of retention).</p>
									 <p>If you want to maximize your daily ingress, you can ingress up to 1 GB per day, and retain that data for up to 30 days.</p>
								</section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_Whats_included_in_the_Time_Series_Insights_S2_SKU?" aria-label="What's included in the Time Series Insights S2 SKU?">What's included in the Time Series Insights S2 SKU?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Each unit of S2 includes a maximum of 300 GB or 300 million events (whichever comes first) of total storage and configurable daily ingress and retention. Also included is the Time Series Insights visualization experience. There is no limit on the number of users or queries that can be conducted.</p>
									 <p>For example, if you provision 1 unit of S2, you will achieve 400 days of retention if you configure the environment to retain for 400 days and your average daily ingress is 1/400th of 300 GB (.75 GB or 750 MB per day) or less.</p>
									 <p>Another example-if you configure your environment to retain data for 180 days with one S2 unit, you will achieve 180 days of retention so long as you do not exceed daily ingress of 1.66 GB (1,660 MB) per day. If your ingress rate exceeds 1.66 GB per day, your data will not be stored for 180 days. If for example, your ingress rate averaged 1.89 GB per day, you would achieve just over 158 days of retention (300 GB/1.89 = 158.73 days of retention).</p>
									 <p>If you want to maximize your daily ingress, you can ingress up to 10 GB per day, and retain that data for up to 30 days.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_What_happens_if_I_want_to_send_events_larger_than_1_KB_using_the_S1_or_S2_SKU?" aria-label="What happens if I want to send events larger than 1 KB using the S1 or S2 SKU?">What happens if I want to send events larger than 1 KB using the S1 or S2 SKU?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>An event is a unit of data up to 1 KB. Larger events are counted in multiples of 1 KB. For example, 0.8 KB is billed as one event, but a 2.6 KB event is billed as three events. Events larger than our maximum, 32 KB, will be rejected.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_How_can_I_scale_up_or_scale_down_the_number_of_units_I_have_purchased?" aria-label="How can I scale up or scale down the number of units I have purchased?">How can I scale up or scale down the number of units I have purchased?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>You can change the number of units via the <a href="https://portal.azure.cn/">Azure Portal</a>.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_time-series-insights_How_does_billing_work_for_the_S1_and_S2_SKUs?" aria-label="How does billing work for the S1 and S2 SKUs?">How does billing work for the S1 and S2 SKUs?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>You will be billed on a daily prorated basis. A day commences at midnight UTC for the purposes of billing. The billing is generated on a monthly basis. For instance, if a customer uses three units of Time Series Insights S1 for a total of 5 days, the customer is billed at the end of the month for 3 units x 5 days x (&yen; 1526.4/31) = &yen; 738.581.</p>
									 <p>Similarly, if a customer uses three units of Time Series Insights S2 for a total of 5 days, the customer is billed at the end of the month for three units x 5 days x (&yen; 13737.6/31) = &yen; 6647.226.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
			
    		<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="storage-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/time-series-insights/" id="pricing_storage_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
			</div> 
            <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk-->
            <!-- <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />                                                                        -->
            <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                         
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Cloud Time Series Insights - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-time-series-insights</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Time Series Insights</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure Time Series Insights.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Time Series Insights</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
