<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-04T10:41:59" urlName="iot-hub" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="iot-hub" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/azure-Iot-hub.jpg','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/azure-iot-hub80.png" />
                        <h2>Azure IoT Hub</h2>
                        <h4>Connect, monitor, and control billions of IoT assets</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_iot-hub_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_iot-hub_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Connect, monitor, and control millions of IoT assets running on a broad set of operating systems and protocols to jumpstart your Internet of Things project with the IoT Hub. Enhance security of your IoT solutions by using per-device authentication to communicate with devices with the appropriate credentials. Securely establish reliable, bi-directional communication with these assets, even if they are intermittently connected, to analyze incoming telemetry, synchronize device management workflows, and send commands and notifications as needed.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>The Azure IoT Hub has four editions: the Free Edition, S1 Edition, S2 Edition and S3 Edition, which are now published by the Azure IoT Hub. The new pricing will take effect as indicated below.</p>
                    <p><strong>Free Edition：</strong> free trial of Azure IoT Hub services. Upon signup, you can transmit up to 8,000 messages per day. It is suitable for understanding and testing features of IoT Hub Services.</p>
                    <p><strong>S1 Edition：</strong> the IoT Hub S1 edition is designed for IoT solutions that generate relatively small amounts of data. Each pricing unit of the S1 Edition allows you to transfer up to 400 thousand messages per day across all connected devices.</p>
                    <p><strong>S2 Edition：</strong> the IoT Hub S2 Edition is designed for IoT solutions that generate relatively large amounts of data. Each pricing unit of the S2 Edition allows you to transfer up to 6 million messages per day across all connected devices.</p>
                    <p><strong>S3 Edition：</strong> the IoT Hub S3 Edition is designed for IoT solutions that generate relatively super large amounts of data. Each pricing unit of the S3 Edition allows you to transfer up to 300 million messages per day across all connected devices.</p>
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Edition Type</strong></th>
                                <th align="left"><strong>Original price </strong></th>
                                <th align="left"><strong>New price</strong> <sup style="color:#e66102; font-weight: bold">new</sup></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Total Number of Messages/Day per Unit</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Message Meter Size</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Free</td>
                            <td>Free</td>
                            <td>Free</td>
                            <td>8,000</td>
                            <td>0.5KB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>S1</td>

                            <td>￥ 388.00/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>￥ 254.40/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>400,000</td>
                            <td>4KB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>S2</td>

                            <td>￥ 3888.00/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>￥ 2,544.00/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>6,000,000</td>
                            <td>4KB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>S3</td>

                            <td>￥ 38880.00/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>￥ 25,440.00/Unit/Month</td>
                            <td>300,000,000</td>
                            <td>4KB</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                   
                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQs</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q1">What is included in the Azure IoT Hub Free Edition?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The IoT Hub Free Edition is intended to encourage proof of concept projects. It enables you to transmit up to a total of 8,000 messages per day, and register up to 500 device identities. The device identity limit is only present for the Free Edition.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q2">What is included in the Azure IoT Hub S1 Edition?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Each pricing unit of the S1 Edition allows you to transfer up to 400,000 messages per day across all devices. If more than 400,000 messages are transmitted on all devices each day, you will need to purchase more units.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q3">What is included in the Azure IoT Hub S2 Edition?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The S2 Edition of Azure IoT Hub is used for scenarios where the customer has a large number of devices and generates large amounts of data, thus requiring frequent transmission of messages. Each pricing unit of the S2 Edition allows you to transfer up to 6 million messages a day. If more than 6 million messages are transmitted on all devices each day, you will need to purchase more units.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q4">How can I scale up or scale down the number of IoT Hub units I have purchased?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Every tier has daily message limit after which you will experience throttling. Please check <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-devguide-quotas-throttling" target="_blank">throttling documentation</a> for more details. If your need change, you can adjust the units within IoT Hub. You can also change the unit type within a tier (e.g.: from S1 to S2).If you anticipate using more than 200 units of the IoT Hub S1 S2 SKU’s and more than 10 units of the IoT Hub S3 please contact Microsoft Support. </p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q5">What is the maximum size of message I can send through the IoT Hub?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The maximum message size for messages sent from a device to the cloud is 256 KB. These messages are metered in 4 KB blocks for the paid tiers (S1 and S2 edition) so for instance if the device sends a 16 KB message via S1 and S2 edition it will be billed as 4 messages. The messages sent by devices connected via the free edition are metered in 0.5 KB blocks. For instance, if the device sends a 16 KB message via the IoT Hub free tier it will be billed as 32 messages.</p>
                                    <p>As for the paid SKU (namely S1 Edition and S2 Edition), the maximum message size for message sent from the cloud to a device is 64 KB and is metered in 4-KB blocks. For instance, an 8-KB message sent via S1 or S2 edition would be billed as two messages. The messages sent using the free edition are metered in 0.5-KB blocks. For instance, an 8-KB message sent via the IoT Hub free tier will be billed as 16 messages.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q6">How does billing work for the IoT Hub service?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The consumption of IoT Hub units is measured on a daily basis, and the billing is generated on a monthly basis. Customers are billed based on the number of IoT Hub units that have been consumed during the month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="ih-que-q7">Is the billing prorated if I purchase an additional IoT Hub unit mid-month?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You can choose to increase the number of IoT Hub units purchased at any time. If you sign up for the service mid-month, your monthly bill will be pro-rated based on the number of days remaining in the month. (For the purpose of the IoT Hub service, a month is defined as 31 days). If you increase the number of units of IoT Hub mid-month, your monthly bill will be based on the number of units available for each day during the month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="vm-que-q8">Can I reduce the number of units if the business need changes?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Yes, you can reduce the number of units from the Settings page at any point. The changes will take effect by the following day and be reflected on your bill at the end of the month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="vm-que-q9">Can I switch from the Free Edition to the paid Editions?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>No, you can not switch from the Free Edition to the paid editions. The free edition is meant to test out proof-of-concept solutions only.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="vm-que-q10">Can I switch between the S1 Edition and S2 Edition of IoT Hub?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Yes, you have to take the action of explicitly switching from one paid edition to another. The device identity and all messages are carried over to the new edition. Switching from the paid edition to the free edition is not allowed.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>Azure IoT Hub is available in the following areas:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
				<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="iot-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
                <p>For IoT Hub, we guarantee that, at least 99.9% of the time, the deployed IoT Hub can send information to and receive information from registered devices, and the service can perform operations such as creation, reading, updates, and deletion on the IoT Hub.</p>
				<p>Service Level Agreement is not available in the free edition of IoT Hub.</p> 
				<p>To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/iot-hub/" id="pricing_iot-hub_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p> 
                </div>
            <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  --> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                             
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure IoT Hub Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-iot-hub</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, Internet of Things, Azure IoT Hub, Azure IoT Hub, monitoring Internet of Things assets, two-way communications, and price</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure IoT Hub. Connect, monitor, and control millions of Internet of Things assets by using Azure IoT Hub. Azure IoT Hub offers free, S1, S2, and S3 Editions. The free version of Azure IoT Hub can transmit up to 8,000 messages per day. A 1RMB Trial gets you RMB1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Azure IoT Hub</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
