<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-06-30T16:00:00" urlName="mysqldatabaseonazure" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="mysqldatabaseonazure" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/mysql-database%20on%20azure.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/mysql_database_on_azure_icon@2x.png" />
                        <h2>MySQL <small>Database on Azure</small></h2>
                        <h4>Managed MySQL database service for app developers</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_mysqldatabaseonazure_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_mysqldatabaseonazure_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>MySQL Database on Azure is a relational database provided by Azure. It is compatible with the MySQL agreement, offering users a database platform with stable performance, easy operations and high security. It takes only one to two minutes for you to create a MySQL database server with high availability on Azure without the need to manage the Virtual Machine or infrastructure. MySQL Database on Azure provides users with easy management and maintenance features and experience. You can easily monitor database performance and resource use and shift among different versions based on your demand. MySQL Database on Azure provides at most 35 days of data backups and recovery options. Moreover, compared with MySQL servers set up by users themselves on Azure Virtual Machine, MySQL Database on Azure offers a better price to performance ratio.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h2>Versions and Detailed Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>MySQL Database on Azure provides eight different versions, with performance increasing from lowest to highest.</p>
                    <!-- <p>从2016年4月1日起，价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>    
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"  style="min-width:50px;">
                                <div><strong>Performance Version</strong></div>
                                <div><a id="home_mysql_guidance" href="https://docs.azure.cn/mysql/mysql-database-performance-guidance-asdb-test-result/" target="_blank" style="color: #00a8d9;"><strong>View Performance Test Data</strong></a></div>
                            </th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 1</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 2</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 3</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 4</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 5</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MS 6</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MP 1</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>MP 2</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Free Database Capacity<br/><span style="color: #00a8d9;">Charge for the excess part: ¥0.61/GB/month</span></td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>100 GB</td>
                            <td>125 GB</td>
                            <td>125 GB</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Data backup</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 30 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 7 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 35 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 35 days</td>
                            <td>Backups are automatically made every day and retained for 35 days. Roll-back is supported at any time within 35 days</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Max Supported Simultaneous Number of Links</td>
                            <td>100</td>
                            <td>200</td>
                            <td>500</td>
                            <td>1,000</td>
                            <td>1,500</td>
                            <td>2,000</td>
                            <td>4,000</td>
                            <td>6,000</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>Pricing</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>¥0.09/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥66.96/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>¥0.18/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥133.92/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div> ¥0.48/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥357.12/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>¥1.44/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥1071.36/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>¥2.16/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥1607.04/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td class="left_align">
                                <div>¥3.24/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥2410.56/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td>
                                <div>¥7.64/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥5684.16/month)</div>
                            </td>
                            <td>
                                <div>¥12.02/hour</div>
                                <div style="margin-left:-5px;">(about ¥8942.88/month)</div>
                            </td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
					<!-- <p><sup>1 </sup>MP 1 及 MP 2 于 2017 年 7 月 1 日至 2017 年 12 月 31 日提供 5 折促销优惠。从 2018 年 1月 1 日开始，MP1 的价格将恢复为 ¥7.64/小时 （¥5684.16/月），MP2 的价格将恢复为 ¥12.02/小时（¥8942.88/月）。</p> -->
                    <p>MySQL Database on Azure supports rapid and flexible shifting between different versions. You can choose a version according to estimated current performance of your application and then make timely adjustment according to actual operation status and performance monitoring provided by MySQL Database on Azure to find the most suitable version.</p>
					<p>* Readable standby database can be operated to add a subordinate instance that is the same as the primary library, which will be charged at the same rate as the primary instance.</p> 
                    <!-- END: Table1-Content-->
                </div>
            </div>       
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <h3>MySQL Classic Retirement Customer FAQ</h3>
                    <p>We are ending the MySQL Database on Azure service on December 1st, 2019, which will be replaced by the Azure Database for MySQL service. </p>
                    <p>If you are an existing customer:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>· No interruption of service</li>
                        <li>· You will be automatically migrated to the new service before the end of life of the existing service</li>
                        <li>· Migration will begin on Feb 15th, 2019</li>
                        <li>· Special pricing will be lost when scaled to a different service tier or if server is deleted</li>
                        <li>· You will continue to pay the same price post migration – detailed information about the SKU mapping between the old service and the new service will be published before end of December 2018</li>
                        <li>· No action necessary for now. At a minimum, 30 days prior to your scheduled migration you will receive additional notifications including the exact timeline for your migration</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>If you are a new customer:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>· You will not be accepted on the “MySQL Database on Azure” service as of the date of this announcement</li>
                    </ul>
                    <ul>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question4">Will my total bill increase when moving from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL? </a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>No. Your monthly total bill once on Azure Database for MySQL will be the same as your total monthly bill on MySQL Database on Azure. For example: if you are an MS4 customer currently paying ¥1,071.36 per month for MySQL Database on Azure, you will continue to pay ¥1,071.36 per month once on Azure Database for MySQL.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question5">Will my bill look different after I migrate from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL? How will my bill look different?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>Yes, your bill will look different after we migrated you from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, but your total bill amount will remain the same. Today with MySQL Database on Azure you are charged for the version   you are using (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2), which includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. If you use more storage than is included in this free database capacity, then you are billed ¥0.6116 per GB per month for that excess storage.</p>
                                        <p>After the migration to Azure Database for MySQL, you will be charged for the compute and storage resources you provision. Compute resources are charged per vCore per hour. Storage is charged  per provisioned GB per month. Azure Database for MySQL does not include “free database capacity”. </p>
                                        <p>Let us look at an example that describes how you will be billed before and after you migrate to Azure Database for MySQL: </p>
                                        <p>Let us assume you are using MS5 with 200 GB of storage. MS5 includes 100 GB of “free database capacity”. That makes the bill look like this:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>MS5 server:  ¥2.1613 per hour x 744 hours per month = ¥1,608.01 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage Overage: ¥0.6116 per GB per month x (200 GB used – 100 GB free) = ¥61.16 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,608.01 per month + ¥61.16 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>During the migration to Azure Database for MySQL the MS5 server will migrate to General Purpose 4 vCore with 200 GB provisioned storage.  The pricing look as follows:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Compute: ¥0.5198 per vCore per hour x 4 vCore x 744 hours per month = ¥1,546.85 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage: ¥0.6116 per GB per Month x 200 GB = ¥122.32 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,546.85 per month + ¥122.32 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>So in this example, the total monthly bill for MySQL Database on Azure MS5 and the equivalent offer on Azure Database for MySQL is the same.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question7">How will you maintain my total bill if you are charging for storage?</a>
                                 <section>
                                        <p>MySQL Database on Azure includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. This free database capacity varies by version (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2).</p>
                                        <p>Azure Database for MySQL does not include free storage. Instead Azure Database for MySQL charges for compute in vCores per hour and provisioned storage  in GB per month separately. Each MySQL Database on Azure migrated to Azure Database for MySQL will be provisioned with a minimum storage size equivalent to the free database capacity for MySQL Database on Azure. For example, if you are an MS1 customer, your database will be provisioned with a minimum of 100 GB of storage.</p>
                                        <p>To maintain the same total monthly bill for customers who have migrated from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, migrated customers will be billed using a special “legacy” compute and storage meters that maintain your total monthly bill. These “legacy” meters are priced to offset the loss of the “free database capacity” included in MySQL Database on Azure.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question8">What happens if I notice an increase in my total bill?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You should not see an increase in your total monthly bill. If you do, please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">open a support ticket</a> so that the team can investigate.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question9">How will my server be mapped to the new offering?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We will publish detailed mapping information before end of December 2018.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question10">When will my server be migrated?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You will get an email notification at least 30 days prior to the date your server is scheduled to migrate. Migrations will not start before Feb 15th, 2019.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question11">How will the billing meters be mapped?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We will publish detailed meter mapping information before end of December 2018.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question12">Do I have to migrate myself or will you provide assistance to migrate?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You do not have to take any action, your MySQL server will be migrated for you. You will receive another communication with additional details 30 days prior to your scheduled migration. Please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">file a support ticket</a> if you wish to be migrated earlier.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question13">What if I migrate to using a mysqldump and mysqlrestore?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You can migrate using mysqldump and mysqlrestore, however you will not be able to maintain use the legacy meters put in place to maintain your exact current price points. You will be billed using new pricing model.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question14">What happens if I want to change the performance level after I migrate (ex: I have migrated to a General Purpose 4 vCore from MS5, and then want to upgrade to General Purpose 8 vCore)?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>If you decide to increase your database size once on Azure Database for MySQL after you have migrated, you will no longer receive the “legacy” prices, but will migrate to the Azure Database for MySQL prices as displayed <a href="https://www.azure.cn/en-us/pricing/details/mysql/">here</a>.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>

                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question15">What is the experience during the migration?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>The impact to your server and workload will be minimal. We migrate server from MySQL Database for Azure to the new Azure Database for MySQL using replication. This means that the server will be online during the migration except for the final phase of the migration that includes the failover to the new server. The connection string to the server will remain the same, so that you do not have to change your application logic. </p>
                                        <p>Below are the migration steps in short:</p>
                                        <ol>
                                            <li>We take a snapshot of the server in MySQL Database for Azure.</li>
                                            <li>We restore that snapshot in a new Azure Database for MySQL server.</li>
                                            <li>Set up replication between the old and the new server to catch up all changes since the snapshot.</li>
                                            <li>When the new server is caught up except for in-flight transactions, we set the old server to read-only mode for new transactions.</li>
                                            <li>The new server catches up with the latest changes and we stop the replication.</li>
                                            <li>We then copy configurations, firewall rules and redirect DNS from the old to the new server and finally stop the old server. </li>
                                            <li>All new connections to against the new server. No changes to your application are required.</li>
                                        </ol>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                    </ul>

                    <h3>General</h3>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="pricing_mysql_question1">How can I expand its capacity if my database is over 100GB?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>We provide 100GB of free database capacity. For the exceeding part, users do not need to perform extra operations and we will automatically charge it as web Blob Storage (Geo-Redundant Storage): ¥0.61/GB/month.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="pricing_mysql_question2">What is billed if my database server is active for less than one hour?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Hours are charged based on the time the database server exists, and if the time is shorter than one hour, it will be charged for one hour. For instance, if you create an MS1 level database and immediately upgrade it into an MS2 level database, the first hour will be charged at the standard of an MS2 database. If you delete a database server and create another one with the same name later, the two independent database servers will be respectively charged for the hour.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="pricing_mysql_question3"> How long does it take to change the version of the database service?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Usually within 3 minutes.</p>
                                </section>
 
                            </div>
                        </li>

                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>MySQL Database on Azure is available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>   -->
             <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="mysql-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				 <p>MySQL Database on Azure provides a Service Level Agreement for 99.9% operating time to ensure high availability and business continuity for users. To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/mysqldatabaseonazure/" id="pricing_mysql_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
            </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                      
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>MySQL Database on Azure Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-mysql</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, MySQL Database on Azure, pricing details, pricing, billing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of MySQL Database on Azure. MySQL Database on Azure provides six versions with their performance improving from the lowest to the highest. A 1RMB Trial gets you ¥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - MySQL Database on Azure</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
