<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText>
    <![CDATA[
         <p><tags ms.service="legal-en" ms.date="02/2015" wacn.date="02/2015" wacn.lang="en"/></p>

        <h1>Legal Information</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="ms-date">Updated: 02/2015</div></div>
        <h2>Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet</h2>
        <h3>Service Agreement &amp; Terms</h3>
        <p>For customers who purchased through our website, use of Azure is governed by 21Vianet's <a href="/support/legal/subscription-agreement/">Online Services Standard Agreement</a>.</p>
        <p>For customers who purchased through a sales team, use of Azure is governed by the Online Services Premium Agreement (available from your sales contact). </p>
        <p>Both agreements incorporate the <a href="/support/legal/services-terms/">Azure Services Terms</a> which includes the Acceptable Use Policy.</p>
        <h3>Offer Details</h3>
        <p>Pricing and other terms and conditions for the particular Azure offer you choose are detailed in the <a href="/support/legal/offer-rate-plans/">offer details for your subscription</a>.</p>
        <h3>Privacy Statement</h3>
        <p>The Privacy Statement for Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet describes the privacy policy and practices that govern your use of Azure.</p>
        <h3>Service Level Agreements</h3>
        <p>The <a href="/support/legal/sla/">Service Level Agreements (SLAs)</a> describe commitments around uptime and connectivity for Azure. SLAs are not available for services in beta, preview or other pre-release. </p>
        <p><em>This page is provided for your convenience as an overview of the terms and conditions that govern the purchase and use of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet. Ancillary services, software, and content, including trials and beta releases, may be governed by additional or different terms not listed above.</em></p>
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Legal Information | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription>
        <![CDATA[
            Legal Information
        ]]>    
    </metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
