<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-07T11:41:59" urlName="storage-import-export" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            
            <div>   
                    <h1>Azure Import/Export<!--span>Import/Export</span--></h1>

					<p>With the Azure import/export service, you can use the HDD to transfer large amounts of data in and out of Azure. For the movement of large datasets, the importing/exporting is faster and more cost-effective than data transfer by the Internet. This service enables you to transfer data to Azure through the secure transfer from the HDD to the data center and the high-speed and secure internal network.</p>
			</div>
			<div class="pricing-page-section">
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p><strong>Device handling</strong>: the processing fee for each storage device is ￥380. No network data transfer charge between the device and Azure Storage within the same datacenter.  Please view the <a href="/pricing/details/storage/" id="storage-import-export_pricing-storage">Storage Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
                    <p><strong>Return shipping of devices</strong>: related shipping charges caused by device returns is free before March 1, 2017.</p>
                   
            </div>           
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Data_Transfer_question1"> Does an extra fee need to be paid while importing/exporting the service transfer data and storing it in Azure? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The standard <a id="storage-import-export_pricing-storage-faq" href="/pricing/details/storage/">Storage</a> pricing is applicable to the data stored in Azure Storage after being imported.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>            
                    </ul>
				</div>
			</div>
			<div class="pricing-page-section">
    <h2>Region</h2>
    <p>The import/export service is available in the following regions:</p>
    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
        <tr>
            <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
            <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mainland China</td>
            <td>China East, China North</td>
        </tr>
    </table>

<h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="storage-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>Currently, we will not provide a Service Level Agreement for importing/exporting. If you want to learn about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please access the <a id="pricing_storage-import-export_sla" href="/support/legal/sla/" target="_blank">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
</div>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Import/Export Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>storage-import-export</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Azure Storage - Import/Export, pricing details, pricing and billing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Import/Export. Users can learn the differences between the storage features and pricing to choose suitable storage. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Azure Import/Export</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
