<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-06-12T16:00:00" urlName="virtual-machines" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
                          <![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="site-recovery" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/site_recovery.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/site-recovery@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Site Recovery</h2>
                        <h4>Orchestrate protection and recovery of private clouds</h4>                      
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_recovery_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_recovery_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Automatic replication can help protect your services</h2>
                <p>Azure Site Recovery can help protect your major services by coordinating automatic replication and recovery of the private cloud at a secondary location. There are two major deployment choices.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>A virtual machine, operated while Hyper-V and system center are used, can be copied between two client sites. Azure Site Recovery can monitor the status and storage recovery plan of the application programs operated at home sites and execute the plan when necessary. When site interruptions happen at the main data center, the virtual machine recovers as arranged so as to help rapidly recover services. This process can also be used for recovery tests or temporary transmission services.</li>
                    <li>Now, a virtual machine can be copied directly from a home site to Azure instead of your own secondary site. When the home site interrupt happens, this service can coordinate the recovery of the virtual machine in Azure.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active">
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>Azure Site Recovery is charged based on the number of protected instances.</p>
                    <!-- <p>从2016年4月1日起， 价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br>
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>&#160;</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Pricing</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Azure Site Recovery to customer owned sites</td>
                            <td>￥101.27/month per instance protected</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Azure Site Recovery to Azure</td>
                            <td>￥342.55/month per instance protected</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    <p>Besides, storage, storage transactions and data transfers are independently charged.</p>
                    <p>Azure Site Recovery is charged by the average daily number of protected instances stored per month. For example, if you have 20 protected instances stored in the first half of the month and have no virtual machine instance storage protection in the second half of the month, the daily protected instance storage of the month will be 10.</p>
                 
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
           
            <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>Site Recovery service is available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table> -->
           <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="recovery-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>For every protected instance storage that is preset for local-to-local failover, we promise that the Recovery Services are at least 99.9% available.</p>
				<p>For every protected instance storage that is preset for planned or unplanned failover deployed from a local site to Azure, we promise the recovery time of each unencrypted protected instance storage will be 4 hours, and 6 hours for encrypted protected instance storage, depending on the size of the protected instance storage.</p>
				<p>To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/site-recovery/" id="pricing_recovery_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
            </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                         
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Site Recovery Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-site-recovery</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Site Recovery, Pricing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure Site Recovery. Azure Site Recovery automatically copy and recover private cloud by coordinating auxiliary locations so as to protect your major service. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Site Recovery</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
