<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <wazcomHomepage id="11978" parentID="-1" level="1" writerID="106" creatorID="22" nodeType="1056" template="4" sortOrder="15" createDate="2012-05-29T21:00:07" updateDate="2014-11-11T02:51:30" nodeName="zh-cn" urlName="zh-cn" writerName="content" creatorName="Brad" path="-1,11978" isDoc="">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
      	<style type="text/css">
      		.aipa{
            background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);
           
          }
          .aipa .banner{
            width: 100%;
            position:relative;
            background-image: url(//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/apia-img01.jpg);
            background-size: cover;
            height: 220px;
            background-position: 50% 50%;
          }
          .aipa .row{
          margin-bottom:10px;
          }
          .aipa-p{
            color: rgb(94, 109, 129);
            }
          .aipa p{
            font-size: 14px;
            margin-top: 7px;
            margin-bottom: 7px;
            line-height: 22px;
            color: #5e6d81;
            word-wrap: break-word;
            text-align: justify;
          }
          .ms-date {
            margin-right: 5px;
          }
          .tags-date .ms-date{
              font-size: 12px;
              display: inline-block;
          }
          .tags-date {
            color: #89919c;
            margin-bottom: 20px;
          }
          .aipa a{
            padding: 0;
            margin: 0 6px;
            height: 21px;
            line-height: 22px;
            font-size: 14px;
            color: #00a3d9;
            float: none;
            display: inline;
          }
          .aipa a:hover{
          text-decoration:underline;
          }
          .banner img{
          position: absolute;
          top: 40px;
          left: -10px;
          width:100%;
          }
          .aipa .banner .container{
          padding-top:40px;
          padding-bottom:40px;
          }
          .aipa .container h2{
            font-size:32px;
          }
          .banner .container h2,.banner .container h3,.banner .container p{
            color:#fff;
            font-weight:300;
          }
          .banner .container h2,.banner .container h3{
            margin-bottom:20px;
          }
          .mr-b{
            padding:40px 20px 60px;
          }
          .aipa .container{
            width:1240px;
          }
          .case-per{
            height: 360px;
            margin-bottom:20px;
          }
          .case-logo{
            height:160px;
          }
          .case-logo img{
            display:block;
            height:100%;
          }
          #t-a-r{
          text-align:right;
          }
          @media only screen and (min-width:980px){
            .case-per{
              margin-right:14%;
            }
          }
          @media only screen and (max-width: 981px){
            .mr-b{
            padding:40px 20px 30px;
            }
            .banner .container h2,.banner .container h3{
              margin-bottom:10px;
            }
            .aipa .container h2{
              font-size:26px;
            }
            .aipa .container{
              width:100%;
            }
            .aipa .row{
            margin:0;
            }
            .case-per{
            height:100%;
            margin-bottom:20px;
          }
          .mb{
            margin-top:-40px;margin-bottom:-12px;
          }
          .kl{
            margin-top:-58px;margin-bottom:-48px;
          }
          .yj{
            margin-top:-28px;margin-bottom:-20px;
          }
          }
          @media only screen and (max-width: 1240px){
            .aipa .container{
              width:100%;
            }
          }

      	</style>
        <div class="aipa">
          <div class="banner">
              <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <h2 style="line-height:44px;">Azure Intellectual Property Protection Plan</h2>
                    <h3 style="font-size:20px;">Protecting Creativity in the Cloud</h3>
                    <p>Reduce risks, innovate boldly, and operate freely in the Cloud. The Azure intellectual property protection plan provides the industry's first comprehensive protection against intellectual property (IP) risks.</p>
                </div>
              </div>
          </div>
      		<div class="container mr-b">
            <div class="row">
              <p class="aipa-p">In China, like customers using global Microsoft Cloud Services, customers of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet can now enjoy the cloud computing intellectual property (IP) protection program—Azure IP Advantage. This is an industry-first comprehensive IP protection program provided by Microsoft to help Azure customers protect cloud computing-based innovation and investment and against IP litigation and risks. Through the Azure intellectual property protection program, we strive to create an ecosystem where developers, newly established companies, enterprises, and customers can focus on innovation without additional worries.</p>
              <p class="aipa-p">Refer to the <a href="//azure.microsoft.com/overview/azure-ip-advantage/">Azure IP Advantage</a> page for detailed terms and applicable conditions<sup>*</sup> of the Azure Intellectual Property Protection Plan.</p>
              <div class="tags-date">
                <div class="ms-date">*For customers of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet, unlimited compensation for patent actions against Azure core services under the three customer rights of the plan is provided by 21Vianet, and other rights are provided directly by Microsoft.</div>
              </div>
            </div>
            
            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-md-4 col-md-12">
                <div class="case-per">
                  <div class="case-logo mb"><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mobike-logo-apia.png" /></div>
                  <div class="case-disc">
                    <p>“As of October 2017, Mobike had expanded its shared bicycle business in China and eight other countries around the world. In some areas, Mobike has decided to work with Microsoft SmartCloud. Mobike is accelerating its global market expansion with the help of Microsoft's high-quality services in the cloud and Azure IP Advantage.”</p>
                    <p id="t-a-r">- Mobike</p>
                  </div>
                </div>
              </div>
              <div class="col-md-4 col-md-12">
                <div class="case-per">
                  <div class="case-logo kl" style=""><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/kohler-logo-apia.png" /></div>
                  <div class="case-disc">
                    <p>“Kohler is a famous brand in the home furnishing and sanitary fields. Facing new technological trends, Kohler is also keeping pace with the times and actively promoting the digital transformation of business and products. Kohler is actively building a new generation of smart home systems and user experiences through collaboration with technology vendors such as Microsoft.</p>
                    <p>“Azure IP Advantage enables us to focus more on product and technology innovation on the cloud platform and gives us greater confidence in the future of cloud development.”</p>
                    <p id="t-a-r">- Wan Zhong, Asia Pacific Director of Kohler</p>
                  </div>
                </div>
              </div>
              <div class="col-md-4 col-md-12">
                <div class="case-per">
                  <div class="case-logo yj"><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/yjny-logo-apia.png" /></div>
                  <div class="case-disc">
                    <p>“We have built the EnOS Smart Internet of Things platform on the Azure Cloud and are using the Azure Cloud to enter the international market while deploying and running in China. The Azure Cloud provides us with a compliant and reliable smart cloud platform that is uniformly developed and flexibly deployed and managed, while Azure IP Advantage provides us with an umbrella for patented technology, allowing us to focus on technological innovation and reduce unnecessary waste of resources.”</p>
                    <p id="t-a-r">- Pan Yihong, Senior O&amp;M Manager of Envision Energy</p>
                  </div>
                </div>
              </div>
            </div>
      		</div>	
        </div>
			
    ]]></bodyText>
    <siteName>Azure IP Advantage</siteName>
    <siteDescription><![CDATA[
      Reduce risk, innovate boldly, and operate freely in the cloud. Azure IP Advantage provides the industry's first comprehensive protection against intellectual property (IP) risk.
    ]]></siteDescription>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <metaKeywords>Azure IP Advantage</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
      Azure Intellectual Property Protection Plan – Customers of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet are now also eligible for a cloud computing intellectual property (IP) protection project—the Azure IP Advantage program. This is an industry-first comprehensive intellectual property protection plan provided by Microsoft.
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <pageTitle>Azure IP Advantage – Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <localize>0</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <forbidPublish>0</forbidPublish>
  </wazcomHomepage>
</localize>
