<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-07-17T11:41:59" urlName="bandwidth" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
                      <![CDATA[
      
            
            <div>   
                    <h1>Azure Data Transfer</h1>
                    <p>Data Transfer means that data is moved in and out of Azure Data Centers that are not explicitly covered by Content Delivery Network, or ExpressRoute pricing.</p>
			</div>
			<div class="pricing-page-section">
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>Inbound data transfer and outbound data transfer:</p>
                    <p>Users of the 1RMB Trial receive 50GB of free data. In the event of excess of the data transfer usage limit, the customer's account will be suspended without prior notice and the free credit limit will be set to "0". You can click <a id="pricing_details_here" href="https://account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" style="color: #00a8d9;">here</a> to check your data usage in real time.</p>
                    <P>Official paying users can use incoming data transmission services for free</P>
                    <p>Inbound data transfer (data transmission into the data center): Free</p>
                    <p>Outbound data transfer (data transmission from the data center): ￥0.67/GB</p>
            </div>           
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Data_Transfer_region">Which regions correspond to CN Zone 1?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>A sub-region is the lowest level geo-location that you may select to deploy your applications and associated data.For data transfers (except CDN, ExpressRoute), the following regions correspond to CN Zone 1： </p>
                                    <ul>
                                    <li>CN Zone 1 — China East, China East 2, China North, China North 2.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Data_Transfer_question1">Is there a fee for data transfer between Azure services located in the same region (China East or China North)?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>No. For example, data transfer within an Azure SQL Database in the same region (China East or China North) will not incur any additional costs.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="Data_Transfer_question2">Is there a fee for data transfer between Azure services located in two different regions (China East or China North)?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Yes. Outbound data transfer is charged at the normal rate and inbound data transfer is free.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>                       
                    </ul>
				</div>
			</div>
			<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="reserved-contact-page">Azure Support</a> to select self-service or any other methods to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>Data transfer doesn’t provide a Service Level Agreement. If you want to learn about the details of our server level agreement, please access the <a href="/support/legal/sla/" id="pricing_data-transfer_sla">Service Levels Agreements</a> page.</p>
                </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!-- <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />                                                                        --> <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                         
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Data Transfer Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-data-transfer</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Price, Fapiao, FAQ, Data Transfer</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure Data Transfer. Data transfer means that data is moved in and out of Azure Data Centers that are not explicitly covered by Content Delivery Network pricing. A 1RMB Trial gets you RMB1,500 in service credits, or you can become an Azure Pay-in-Advance user through direct purchasing and enjoy the highest 99.99% Service Level Agreement.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Data Transfer</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
