<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-08-14T13:00:00" urlName="expressroute" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
                      <![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="expressroute" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/express_route.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/expressroute@2x.png" />
                        <h2>ExpressRoute</h2>
                        <h4>Dedicated private network fiber connections to Azure</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_expressroute_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_expressroute_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>ExpressRoute is a service that enables you to create private connections between Azure datacenters and infrastructure that’s on your premises or in a colocation environment. ExpressRoute connections don't go over the public internet, and offer more reliability, faster speeds, lower latencies, and higher security than typical connections over the internet.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#tabContent1" id="home_single_database" class="active">Unlimited Data Plan</a> <a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#tabContent2" id="home_elastic_database">Metered Data Plan</a>
                <div class="clearfix"></div>
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h3>Unlimited Data Plan</h3>
                    <p>All inbound and outbound data transfer is free. Users are charged a single fixed monthly port fee (based on high availability dual ports).</p>
                    <!-- <p>从2016年4月1日起，无限数据计划价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Port Speed</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price Per Month</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price Per Month with Premium Add-on</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Inbound Data Transfer Included</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Outbound Data Transfer Included</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>50 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥2,815.12/month</td>
                            <td>￥13,540.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>100 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥5,681.82/month</td>
                            <td>￥23,220.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>200 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥10,619.04/month</td>
                            <td>￥40,080.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>500 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥24,008.50/month</td>
                            <td>￥83,490.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>1 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥40,168.06/month</td>
                            <td>￥137,780.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>2 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥80,336.13/month</td>
                            <td>￥245,560.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>5 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥189,297.60/month</td>
                            <td>￥598,400.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>10 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥378,595.80/month</td>
                            <td>￥1,196,800.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    <p>Once connected to an ExpressRoute China location, users can connect to other regions in the same geo without the need for the premium add-on, and at no additional cost over existing plan charges. For example, once connected to China East, customers can send or retrieve data to or from China East 2 without the need to pay an additional fee on top of their existing plan charges. Similarly, once connected to China North, customers can send or retrieve data to or from China North 2 without the need to pay an additional fee on top of their existing plan charges.</p>
                    <p><strong>Note:</strong> ExpressRoute <span>connection service providers may charge other fees not included in the fees listed above.</span></p>
                    <!-- END: Table1-Content-->

                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 --> <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-2 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container" id="tabContent2">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h3>Metered Data Plan</h3>
                    <p>All input and output data traffic is free. All input data traffic will be charged according to the preset rates (see table below). Users also need to pay a fixed monthly port fee (based on a high-availability dual-port).</p>
                    <!-- <p>从 2016 年 4 月 1 日起，计量数据计划价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly price estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Port Speed</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price Per Month</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price Per Month with Premium Add-on</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Inbound Data Transfer Included</strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Outbound Data Transfer Included</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>50 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥253.02/month</td>
                            <td>￥10,100.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>100 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥461.68/month</td>
                            <td>￥16,210.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>200 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥670.02/month</td>
                            <td>￥26,720.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>500 Mbps</td>
                            <td>￥1,340.36/month</td>
                            <td>￥53,050.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>1 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥2,010.70/month</td>
                            <td>￥86,540.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>2 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥4,028.96/month</td>
                            <td>￥143,090.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>5 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥10,067.98/month</td>
                            <td>￥357,720.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>10 Gbps</td>
                            <td>￥23,085.14/month</td>
                            <td>￥719,400.00/month</td>
                            <td>Unlimited</td>
                            <td>None</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    <!-- END: Table1-Content-->
                    <p>The rate for output data traffic is: ￥0.22/GB.</p>
                    <p>Once connected to an ExpressRoute China location, users can connect to other regions in the same geo without the need for the premium add-on, and at no additional cost over existing plan charges. For example, once connected to China East, customers can send or retrieve data to or from China East 2 without the need to pay an additional fee on top of their existing plan charges. Similarly, once connected to China North, customers can send or retrieve data to or from China North 2 without the need to pay an additional fee on top of their existing plan charges.</p>
                    <p><strong>Note:</strong> ExpressRoute <span>connection service providers may charge other fees not included in the fees listed above.</span></p>
                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-2 -->
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">

            <h3>ExpressRoute Premium Add-on</h3>
                    <p>ExpressRoute Premium is an add-on over the ExpressRoute Unlimited Data Plan/Metered Data Plan charges. The ExpressRoute Premium add-on provides the following capabilities: </p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Increased route limits for public and private peering from 4,000 routes to 10,000 routes.</li>
                        <li>Connect any China regions through the Azure Core Network. An ExpressRoute circuit created in any China region will have access to resources across any other region. For example, a virtual network created in China East can be accessed through an ExpressRoute circuit provisioned in China North.</li>
                        <li>Increased number of VNet links per ExpressRoute circuit from 10 to a larger limit (depending on the bandwidth of the circuit).</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>For more details, please refer to the <a id="stor-sla-info" style="color: #00a8d9;" href="https://docs.azure.cn/expressroute/">ExpressRoute Service Documentation</a> page.</p>

                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQs</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute_dedicate-link">Which datacenters are available for ExpressRoute dedicate link in China? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>ExpressRoute dedicate link connections are available in China East, China East 2, China North and China North 2.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-cost">What additional charges will I incur from other parties in this solution? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You may have additional charges from your service provider to enable connectivity to ExpressRoute. Please contact your service provider to learn about their pricing.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-port">How many ports are included in one monthly fee for ExpressRoute? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>For redundancy purposes, 2 ports (on 2 routers) are included in the monthly fee shown.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-china">If I connect to one of China's ExpressRoute locations (such as China East), can I access other regions in China via ExpressRoute? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Yes. You can purchase ExpressRoute Unlimited Data Plan/Metered Data Plan to connect from China East to China East 2. You will have access to resources across any other region in China via ExpressRoute Premium Add-on.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-area">Can I connect to any Azure regions from a given ExpressRoute location? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>No. ExpressRoute in China can only be connected to regions within China. You cannot access Azure services in other countries through ExpressRoute in China.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-account">Can I set up multiple circuits in my account? If so, what do I need to do? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>If you are using Azure based on an Enterprise agreement with 21Vianet, please contact our data setup team to ensure correct setup.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-Rate">If I use ExpressRoute for a portion of the month, will the fees be different? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>If your ExpressRoute service is active for the entire month, you will be charged the monthly fee regardless of usage. However, if you cancelled your ExpressRoute service during the month, you would only receive a prorated bill for the hours used and data transfer overage incurred.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-billing">When does ExpressRoute billing start and stop? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>ExpressRoute billing starts when a service key is issued to the customer, and it stops after a customer deletes a circuit (the precondition is Exchange Provider or Network Service Provider has de-provisioned the circuit）.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-speed">Can I change the port speed in the middle of a month? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You can increase the port speed at any time without any disruption. You can decrease port speed by deleting the circuit under the existing pricing plan, and re-creating it under the new pricing plan. Please coordinate with your service provider to provision the new circuit</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-speed">Can I change the pricing plan for a circuit? </a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You can change your pricing plan from metered to unlimited at any time without any disruption. You can change the pricing plan from unlimited to metered by deleting the circuit under the unlimited pricing plan, and re-creating it under the metered pricing plan. Please coordinate with your service provider to provision the new circuit.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="expressroute-other-billing">When using ExpressRoute, besides those prices of data transfer, port and Cloud Connection dedicate links mentioned above, what else I will be charged?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>You will also be charged for ExpressRoute dedicate links, please refer to its pricing information <a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/vpn-gateway/"> pricing of VPN Gateway</a></p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>The ExpressRoute service is available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table> -->
                
                <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="expressroute-contact-page">Azure Support</a> to select self-service or any other methods to contact us for support.</p>
				 <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% availability of ExpressRoute private lines. To learn more about the details of our server level agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/expressroute/" id="pricing_expressroute_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
                </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                 
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>ExpressRoute Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-expressroute</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, Network, Virtual Network, ExpressRoute, Private line, VPN, IP Address, DNS</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the price details of Azure ExpressRoute. ExpressRoute is an integrated cloud solution which provides two pricing plans, namely an unlimited data plan and a metered data plan. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits, or you can become an Azure Pay-in-Advance user through direct purchasing and enjoy the highest 99.99% Service Level Agreement.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - ExpressRoute</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
