<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-07T11:41:59" urlName="data-transfer" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
      <![CDATA[
            <tags ms.service="storage" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags>
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/storage.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                    	<img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/storage@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Managed Disks</h2>
                        <h4>Persistent, secured disk storage for Azure virtual machines</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_storage-managed-disk_trial">Apply for trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_storage-managed-disk_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
			<div class="pricing-page-section">
				<p>Azure Managed Disk is a new and recommended disk storage product used for Azure Virtual Machines, enabling permanent data storage. Multiple Managed Disks can be used for every virtual machine. Managed Disks provide two types of lasting storage options: premium Managed Disk and standard Managed Disk. </p>
				<p>If you’re interested in the pricing details of Non-Managed Disk, please refer to the <a href="javascript:void(0)" id="pricing_storage_data-transfer"  data-href="#tabContent6" >Non-Managed Disk and Page Blob</a> pricing details page.</p>
		
				<h4>Premium Managed Disk</h4>
				<p>Premium Managed Disk, based on high-performance solid state drive (SSD), aims to support I/O intensive workloads, with extremely high throughput and low delay. With the help of Premium Managed Disk, we can set a permanent disk and configure its size and performance characteristics. </p>
				<p>The total expenses of Premium Managed Disk depends on the disk size and quantity, and is subjected to the <a id="pricing_storage_data-transfer-1" href="/pricing/details/data-transfer/">outgoing data transmission</a>. The disk size provides different input/output operations per second (IOP), throughput limits and monthly pricing per GB. We can select most appropriate options including storage size, IOP and throughput. We can add several permanent disks onto the VM and configure at most 64 TB of storage space to every VM. The disk throughput of every VM can reach up to 80,000 (input/output operations) and 1600 MB/second, with a read delay of less than 1 millisecond. Premium Managed Disk is supported by the sizes of the DS Series, DSv2 Series and FS Series VMs exclusively used for Premium Disks.</p>
				<div class="tags-date">
					<div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
					<div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
					<p>The pricing of screenshots is charged at the rate of ￥ 2.35/GB per month. </p>
				</div>
				<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
					<tr>
						<th align="left"><strong>Disk Types</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P4</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P6</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P10</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P15</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P20</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P30</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P40</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>P50</strong></th>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>Disk sizes</td>
						<td>32 GB</td>
						<td>64 GB</td>
						<td>128 GB</td>
						<td>256 GB</td>
						<td>512 GB</td>
						<td>1 TB</td>
						<td>2 TB</td>
						<td>4 TB</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>Monthly pricing</td>
						<td>￥ 47.53</td>
						<td>￥ 91.9</td>
						<td>￥ 132.15</td>
						<td>￥ 254.86</td>
						<td>￥ 490.93</td>
						<td>￥ 906.29</td>
						<td>￥ 1,736.83</td>
						<td>￥ 3,322.63</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>IOP of every disk</td>
						<td>120</td>
						<td>240</td>
						<td>500</td>
						<td>1,100</td>
						<td>2,300</td>
						<td>5,000</td>
						<td>7,500</td>
						<td>7,500</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>Throughput of every disk</td>
						<td>25 MB /second</td>
						<td>50 MB /second</td>
						<td>100 MB /second</td>
						<td>125 MB /second</td>
						<td>150 MB /second</td>
						<td>200 MB /second</td>
						<td>250 MB /second</td>
						<td>250 MB /second</td>
					</tr>
				</table>
				
				<div class="tags-date">
					<div class="ms-date">Premium Disk has no transaction processing expenses.</div>
				</div>
				<p>The aforementioned pricing are also suitable for Premium Non-Managed Disk. </p>
		
				<h4>Standard Managed Disk</h4>
				<p>Standard Managed Disks employ a hard disk drive (HDD)-based storage medium. They are most suitable for development/testing not sensitive to performance changes and other non-frequent access workloads.</p>
				<p>The total cost of Standard Managed Disk storage depends on the disk’s size and quantity, transaction amount and <a id="pricing_storage_data-transfer-2" href="/pricing/details/data-transfer/">outgoing data transmission</a>. There is no difference between different Standard Disk sizes in IOPS and throughput. </p>
				
				<div class="tags-date">
					<div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
					<div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
					<p>The pricing of screenshots is charged at the rate of ￥ 0.3/GB per month. </p>
				</div>
				<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
					<tr>
						<th></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S4</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S6</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S10</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S15</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S20</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S30</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S40</strong></th>
						<th align="left"><strong>S50</strong></th>
						<!-- <th align="left"><strong>S60</strong></th> -->
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>Disk sizes</td>
						<td>32 GB</td>
						<td>64 GB</td>
						<td>128 GB</td>
						<td>256 GB</td>
						<td>512 GB</td>
						<td>1 TB</td>
						<td>2 TB</td>
						<td>4 TB</td>
						<!-- <td>8 TB</td> -->
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td>Monthly pricing</td>
						<td>¥ 8.64</td>
						<td>¥ 17.28</td>
						<td>￥ 34.56</td>
						<td>￥ 69.12</td>
						<td>￥ 138.24</td>
						<td>￥ 276.48</td>
						<td>¥ 552.96</td>
						<td>￥ 1105.92</td>
						<!-- <td>￥2211.84</td> -->
					</tr>
				</table>
				<div class="tags-date">
					<div class="ms-date">We charge ￥ 0.0044 for every 10,000 Standard Managed Disk transactions. Any type of storage operation is considered to be a transaction, including reads, writes, and deletions.</div>
				</div>
				<h4>Local Redundant Storage (LRS)</h4>								
				<p>Create multiple synchronous copies of data in a Data Center. </p>
				<p>To learn more about the redundancy options and how to use these options to obtain high availability, please view the <a id="pricing_storage_documentation-storage-redundancy" href="/documentation/articles/storage-redundancy/">Azure Storage Space Replication Page</a>.</p>
				
            </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
		    	<div class="more-detail">
			        <h2>FAQ</h2>
			        <em>Expand all</em>
			        <ul>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
							<div>
								<a  id="Storage_question14">If I add the empty 100GB disk onto my virtual machine, will I be charged the entire 100 GB expense or just the cost of the storage space I used?</a>
			                    <section>
			                        <p>If the empty 100GB disk is supported by a Premium Storage account, you will be charged for a P10 (128GB) disk. If you use any other types of Storage account, only the storage space for storing data written into the disk will be charged, irrespective of the allocated disk size. </p>
			                    </section>
							</div>
						</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
							<div>
								<a  id="Storage_question15">Does the Service Level Agreement cover Premium Storage, the same as other Storage services?</a>
	                    		<section>
	                        		<p>Yes. 99.9% read/write availability also applies to Premium Storage accounts. </p>
			                    </section>
							</div>
						</li>
					</ul>
			    </div>
			</div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
			    <h2>Marketing Regions</h2>
			    <p>Storage services are available in the following regions:</p>
			    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
			        <tr>
			            <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
			            <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
			        </tr>
			        <tr>
			            <td>Mainland China</td>
			            <td>China North, China East</td>
			        </tr>
			    </table>
    		</div>

    		<div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="storage-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>We guarantee that we can successfully process data reading requests from an offsite redundant storage (RA-GRS) account at least 99.99% of the time (99.9% for the Cold Access Layer), provided that we will retry in the secondary zone from the data writing failure from the primary zone.</p>
				<p>We guarantee that we can successfully process data reading from local redundant storage (LRS) and offsite redundant storage (GRS) accounts at least 99.9% of the time (99% for the Cold Access Layer)</p>
				<p>We guarantee that we can successfully process data writing requests into onsite redundant storage (LRS) and geo-redundant storage (GRS) accounts and read and access geo-redundant storage (RA-GRS) accounts at least 99.9% of the time (99% for the Cold Access Layer).</p>
				<p>To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/storage/" id="pricing_storage_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
				<p>The Managed Disk itself doesn’t provide a Service Level Agreement with financial support. The availability of a Managed Disk depends on the Service Level Agreement governing the basic storage used and the Virtual Machine it’s attached to. To learn more about the details of the Service Level Agreement of the Managed Disk, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/managed-disks/">Managed Disk Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
			</div> 
            <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk-->
            <!-- <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />                                                                        -->
            <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                         
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Cloud Storage_Managed Disks - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-storage-managed-disks</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Managed Disks</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure Storage. Azure Storage is a highly durable, available and scalable cloud storage enabling access anytime, anywhere. A 1RMB Trial gets you ¥ 1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Storage - Managed Disks</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
