<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2018-07-25T12:00:00">
    <bodyText>
    <![CDATA[
        <p><tags ms.service="legal-en" ms.date="12/2017" wacn.date="12/2017" wacn.lang="en"/></p>
        <h1>Service Level Agreements</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="ms-date">Updated: 7/2018</div></div>
        <h2>API Management</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that API Management Service instances running in the Basic, Standard and Premium tiers will respond to requests to perform operations at least 99.9% of the time.</p>
        <p>No SLA is provided for the Developer tier of the API Management Service.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/api-management/" id="api-management-monitor-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Azure Monitor</h2>
        <p>Azure Monitor allows you to collect granular performance and utilization data, activity and diagnostics logs, and define alerts and notifications from your Azure resources in a consistent manner. We guarantee that 99.9% of the time notifications will be successfully delivered.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/monitor-en/" id="network-monitor-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Network Watcher</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that 99.9% of the time Network Diagnostic Tools will successfully execute and return a response.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/network-watcher-en/" id="network-watcher-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Azure Cosmos DB</h2>
        <p><a href="/home/features/cosmos-db/">Azure Cosmos DB</a>, operated by 21Vianet in China, is <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cosmos-db/distribute-data-globally/">a distributed</a> multi-model database service. It offers turnkey  distribution across any number of Azure regions in China by transparently scaling and replicating your data wherever your users are. The service offers comprehensive 99.99% SLAs which covers the guarantees for throughput, consistency, availability and latency for the Cosmos DB Database Accounts scoped to a single Azure region configured with any of the five Consistency Levels or Database Accounts spanning multiple Azure regions, configured with any of the four relaxed Consistency Levels. Furthermore, independent of the choice of a Consistency Level, Cosmos DB offers 99.999% SLA for read availability for Database Accounts spanning two or more Azure regions.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/cosmos-db-en/" id="abstract-en_cosmosdb-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Azure Analysis Services</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that, at least 99.9% of the time Client Operations executed on an Azure Analysis Services server will succeed.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/analysis-services-en/" id="abstract-en_analysis-services-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h3>Cognitive Services</h3>
        <p>We guarantee that Cognitive Services will be available at least 99.9% of the time. No SLA is provided for the Free tier.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/cognitive-services-en/" id="cognitive_services-en">See the full details</a></p>  
        <h2>Automation</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.9% of jobs will start within 30 minutes of their planned start times. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/automation-en/" id="abstract-en_auttomation-en">See the full details</a></p>  
        <h2>Application Gateway</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that each Application Gateway Cloud Service having two or more medium or larger instances will be available at least 99.9% of the time. We do not provide Service Level Agreement for Application Gateway Cloud Service that have only one instance or have small instance(s). </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/application-gateway-en/" id="abstract-en_application-gateway-en">See the full details</a></p>  
        <h2>Azure IoT Hub</h2>
        <p>For IoT Hub, we promise that at least 99.9% of the time deployed IoT hubs will be able to send messages to and receive messages from registered devices and the Service will able to perform create, read, update, and delete operations on IoT hubs.</p>
        <p>No SLA is provided for the Free Tier of IoT Hub. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/iot-hub-en/" id="abstract-en_iot-hub-en">See the full details</a></p> 
        <h2>Backup</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% availability of the backup and restore functionality of the Azure Backup service. Availability is calculated by monthly billing cycle. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/backup-en/" id="abstract-en_backup-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>CDN</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.9% of the time CDN will respond to client requests and deliver the requested content without error. We will review and accept data from any commercially reasonable independent measurement system that you choose to monitor your content. You must select a set of agents from the measurement system¡¯s list of standard agents that are generally available and represent at least five geographically diverse locations in major People Republic of China metropolitan areas. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/cdn-en/" id="abstract-en_cdn-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Cloud Services</h2>
        <p>For Cloud Services, we guarantee that when you deploy two or more role instances in different fault and upgrade domains, your Internet facing roles will have external connectivity at least 99.95% of the time. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/cloud-services-en/" id="abstract-en_cloud-services-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Event Hubs</h2>
        <p>For &quot;basic&quot; and &quot;standard&quot; level of the Event Center, we guarantee that the properly configured application is able to send or receive messages in the event center or perform other operations in at least 99.9% of the time. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/event-hubs-en/" id="abstract-en_event-hubs-en">See the full details</a></p>  
        <h2>ExpressRoute</h2>
        <p>We guarantee a minimum of 99.9% ExpressRoute dedicated circuit availability. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/expressroute-en/" id="abstract-en_expressroute-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>HDInsight</h2>
        <p>For HDInsight, we guarantee that any HDInsight cluster that you deployed will have external connectivity at least 99.9% of the time over a monthly billing cycle. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/hdinsight-en/" id="abstract-en_hdinsight-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Media Services</h2>
        <ul>
        <li>For Media Services Encoding, we guarantee 99.9% availability of REST API transactions.</li>
        <li>For Streaming, we will successfully service requests with a 99.9% availability guarantee for existing media content when at least one Streaming Unit is purchased.</li>
        <li>For Live Channels, we guarantee that running Channels will have external connectivity at least 99.9% of the time.</li>
        <li>For Content Protection, we guarantee that we will successfully fulfill key requests at least 99.9% of the time.</li>
        <li>For Indexer, we will successfully service Indexer Task requests processed with an Encoding Reserved Unit 99.9% of the time.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/media-services-en/" id="abstract-en_media-services-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <!-- <h2>MySQL Database on Azure</h2>
        <p>MySQL Database on Azure provides 99.9% uptime Service Level Agreement, to ensure the high availability and user business continuity of our services. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/mysqldatabaseonazure/" id="abstract-en_mysqldatabaseonazure">See the full details</a></p> -->
        <h2>Multi-Factor Authentication</h2>
        <p>We guarantee 99.9% availability of Azure Multi-Factor Authentication. 
         No SLA is provided for the Free tier of Multi-Factor Authentication. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/multi-factor-authentication-en/" id="abstract-en_multi-factor-authentication-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Notification Hubs</h2>
        <p>For basic and standard layer service notification center, we ensure that the notification services in basic or standard layer will sent through the appropriate configuration of the application notice or register management operations in at least 99.9% of the time. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/notification-hubs-en/" id="abstract-en_notification-hubs-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Power BI Embedded</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% availability of Power BI Embedded for users to execute API calls and embed reports.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/power-bi-embedded-en/" id="abstract-en_powerbi-embedded-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Radis Cache</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% of the time that customers will have connectivity between the Cache endpoints and our Internet gateway. </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.azure.cn/support/sla/redis-cache-en/" id="abstract-en_redis-cache-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Stream Analytics</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% availability of the Stream Analytics API.</p>
        <p>We guarantee that 99.9% of the time, deployed Stream Analytics jobs will be either processing data or available to process data. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/stream-analytics-en/" id="abstract-en_stream-analytics-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Scheduler</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.9% of the time all scheduled jobs will initiate within 30 minutes of their planned execution times. Availability is calculated by monthly billing cycle. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/scheduler-en/" id="abstract-en_scheduler-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Service Bus</h2>
        <ul>
        <li>For Service Bus Relays, we guarantee that at least 99.9% of the time,  properly configured applications will be able to establish a connection to a deployed Relay.</li>
        <li>For Service Bus Queues and Topics, we guarantee that at least 99.9% of the time , properly configured applications will be able to send or receive messages or perform other operations on a deployed Queue or Topic.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/service-bus-en/" id="abstract-en_messaging-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Site Recovery</h2>
        <ul>
        <li>For each Protected Instance configured for On-Premises-to-On-Premises Failover, we guarantee at least 99.9% availability of the Site Recovery service.</li>
        <li>For each Protected Instance configured for On-Premises-to-Azure planned and unplanned Failover, we guarantee a four-hour Recovery Time Objective for unencrypted Protected Instances, and a six-hour Recovery Time Objective for encrypted Protected Instance, depending on the size of the Protected Instance.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/site-recovery-en/" id="abstract-en_site-recovery-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Storage</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.99% (99.9% for Cool Access Tier) of the time, we will successfully process requests to read data from Read Access-Geo Redundant Storage (RA-GRS) Accounts, provided that failed attempts to read data from the primary region are retried on the secondary region.</p>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.9% (99% for Cool Access Tier) of the time, we will successfully process requests to read data from Locally Redundant Storage (LRS) and Geo Redundant Storage (GRS) Accounts.</p>
        <p>We guarantee that at least 99.9% (99% for Cool Access Tier) of the time, we will successfully process requests to write data to Locally Redundant Storage (LRS) and Geo Redundant Storage (GRS) Accounts and Read Access-Geo Redundant Storage (RA-GRS) Accounts.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/storage-en/" id="abstract-en_storage-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Managed Disks</h2>
        <p>Managed Disks does not have a financially backed SLA itself. The availability of Managed Disks is based on the SLA of the underlying storage used and virtual machine to which it is attached. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/managed-disks-en/" id="abstract-en_managed-disks-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>SQL Database</h2>
        <p><strong>Basic, Standard and Premium</strong></p>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.99% of the time customers will have connectivity between their Basic, Standard, or Premium Azure SQL Database and our Internet gateway. Availability is calculated by monthly billing cycle. </p>
        <p><strong>Web and Business (retired)</strong></p>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.9% of the time customers will have connectivity between their Web or Business Azure SQL Database and our Internet gateway. Availability is calculated by monthly billing cycle.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/sql-data-en/" id="abstract-en_sql-data-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>SQL Data Warehouse</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that, at least 99.9% of the time client operations executed on a SQL Data Warehouse database will succeed.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/sql-data-warehouse-en/" id="abstract-en_sql-data-warehouse-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <!-- <h2>DocumentDB</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.99% of the time we will successfully process requests to perform operations against DocumentDB Resources.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/documentdb-en/" id="abstract-en_documentdb-en">See the full details</a></p> -->
        <h2>Traffic Manager</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that DNS queries will receive a valid response from at least one of our Azure Traffic Manager name server clusters at least 99.99% of the time. Availability is calculated by monthly billing cycle. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/traffic-manager-en/" id="abstract-en_traffic-manager-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Key Vault</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that we will process Key Vault transactions within 5 seconds at least 99.9% of the time. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/key-vault-en/" id="abstract-en_key-vault-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Virtual Machines</h2>
        <p>For all Virtual Machines that have two or more instances deployed in the same Availability Set, we guarantee you will have Virtual Machine Connectivity to at least one instance at least 99.95% of the time.</p>
        <p>For any Single Instance Virtual Machine using premium storage for all disks, we guarantee you will have Virtual Machine Connectivity of at least 99.9%.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/virtual-machines-en/" id="abstract-en_virtual-machines-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Virtual Machine Scale Sets</h2>
        <p>Virtual Machine Scale Sets is a free service, therefore, it does not have a financially backed SLA itself. However, if the Virtual Machine Scale Sets includes Virtual Machines in at least 2 Fault Domains, the availability of the underlying Virtual Machines SLA applies.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/virtual-machine-scale-sets-en/" id="abstract-en_virtual-machine-scale-sets-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>VPN Gateway</h2>
        <p>We guarantee 99.9% availability for each Basic Gateway for VPN or Basic Gateway for ExpressRoute.</p>
        <p>We guarantee 99.95% availability for each Standard, High Performance, VpnGw1, VpnGw2, VpnGw3 Gateway for VPN.</p>
        <p>We guarantee 99.95% availability for each Standard, High Performance, Ultra Performance Gateway for ExpressRoute.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/vpn-gateway-en/" id="abstract-en_vpn-gateway-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>App Service</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that Apps running in a customer subscription will be available 99.95% of the time. No SLA is provided for Apps under either the Free or Shared tiers. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/app-service-en/" id="abstract-en_app-service-en">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Azure Database for MySQL</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.99% of the time customers will have connectivity between their Azure Database for MySQL Server and our Internet gateway. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/mysql/" id="abstract_mysql">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Azure Database for PostgreSQL</h2>
        <p>We guarantee at least 99.99% of the time customers will have connectivity between their Azure Database for PostgreSQL Server and our Internet gateway. </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/postgresql/" id="abstract_postgresql">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Load Balancer</h2>
        <p><b>Effective from 1/1/2019</b>, we guarantee that a Load Balanced Endpoint using Azure Standard Load Balancer, serving two or more Healthy Virtual Machine Instances, will be available 99.99% of the time.</p>
        <p>Basic Load Balancer is excluded from this SLA.  </p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/load-balancer/" id="abstract_load-balancer">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>DNS</h2>
        <p>We guarantee that valid DNS requests will receive a response from at least one Azure DNS name server 100% of the time.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/dns/" id="abstract_dns">See the full details</a></p>
        <h2>Container Registry</h2>
        <p>Azure Container Registry is a free service, therefore does not have a financially backed SLA. However, for the availability of underlying storage the Storage SLA applies. See <a href="/support/sla/storage/">Storage SLA</a> for further details.</p>
        <p><a href="/support/sla/container-registry/" id="abstract_container-registry">See full details</a></p>
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Service Level Agreements | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription>
        <![CDATA[
            Service Level Agreements
        ]]>    
    </metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
