<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="15" createDate="2016-06-29T15:44:24" updateDate="2016-06-29T15:44:24" urlName="hybird-benefit" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <style>
                .common-banner{
                    background-image:url("//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/azure_hybrid_benefit_banner.jpg");
                    background-size:cover;
                    background-position: center center;
                    position: relative;
                    width: 100%;
                    height: 360px;
                    background-repeat: no-repeat;
                }
                .common-banner:before {
                    content: '';
                    display: block;
                    width: 100%;
                    height: 100%;
                    position: absolute;
                    top: 0;
                    left: 0;
                    background: rgba(0,0,0,.8);
                }
                .common-banner-title{
                    width: 1240px;
                    margin: 0 auto;
                    position: relative;
                }
                .common-banner-title ul{
                    padding-left:20px;
                    margin-top:0;
                }
                .common-banner-title ul li{
                    font-size:14px;
                    padding:2px 0;
                }
                .section-component{
                    margin-top:0;
                }
                .content .single-page .row .pure-content h1{
                    margin-top:60px;
                }
                .tab-control-selector{
                    margin-top:60px;
                }
                .content .single-page .row .tab-control-container h1{
                    margin-top:60px;
                }.content .single-page .row .tab-control-container h1:first-child{
                    margin-top:20px;
                }
                .content .single-page .row .pricing-page-section h1{
                    margin-top:50px;
                }
                .azure-hybird{
                width:100%;
                }
                .azure-hybird .azure-hybird-sql {
                    width:470px;
                }
                .azure-hybird .azure-hybird-sql img{
                    width:100%;
                }
                .azure-hybird .azure-hybird-sql p{
                    text-align:center;
                }
                .common-banner .common-banner-image{
                    padding: 30px 0 60px;
                }
                @media only screen and (max-width: 769px){
                    .common-banner .common-banner-image .common-banner-title span{
                        font-size: 14px;
                        display: block;
                        height: 20px;
                        line-height: 22px;
                    }
                    .azure-hybird .azure-hybird-sql {
                        width:100%;
                    }
                }
                .common-banner .common-banner-image .common-banner-title h1{
                margin-top:0;
                }
            </style>
            <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="section-component">
                <div class="pricing-page-section">
                    <h1 style="margin-top:60px;">Accelerate your digital transformation</h1>
                    <p>Now is the time to move to Azure and enjoy the advantages of cloud technology, which include: scaling up or down quickly, paying only for what you use, and saving on compute power. Whether you are deploying new virtual machines, moving some workloads or migrating your data centers as part of your hybrid cloud strategy, Azure Hybrid Benefit provides significant savings as you move to the cloud.</p>
                </div>
                <div class="tab-control-selector">
                    <a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#tabContent1" id="home_Windows-server" class="active">Windows Server</a> <a href="javascript:void(0)" data-href="#tabContent2" id="home_sql-server">SQL Server</a>
                    <div class="clearfix"></div>
                    <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                    <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                        <h1>Digital transformation enables customers to maximize the value of their Windows Server license</h1>
                    
                        <p>Similar to other popular Microsoft solutions such as SQL Server and SharePoint, customers can now use their existing Windows Server licenses in combination with Azure and take full advantage of this benefit to scale data centers to the cloud smoothly.</p>
                        
                        <h2>Lower virtual machine prices</h2> 
                        <p>With the A-HUB (Azure Hybrid Use Benefit) plan, customers can deploy and run special price Windows Server virtual machines in Azure using local Windows Server licenses covered by Software Assurance (SA). Customers then only need to pay the basic virtual machine costs at the same rates as Linux virtual machine costs</p>
                        <p>(refer to the <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-machines/" id="a-hub_pricing-vm">Virtual Machine Pricing Details</a> page).</p>
                        
                        <h2>Flexible, cloud-ready licensing modes are supported</h2> 
                        <p>With the A-HUB benefit plan, customers can scale part of their organization's workload or their entire data center to the cloud, creating cloud-ready architecture that fits the needs of the organization.</p>
                        
                        <h2>Get this great value benefit now</h2> 
                        <p>If a customer’s license does not include Software Assurance (SA), then now is the best time to consider subscribing. With a Software Assurance Agreement, customers can save up to 20% on Azure instance usage (this depends on factors including usage, instance type, and data center location).</p>
                        
                        <p>To subscribe to Software Assurance, please contact your Microsoft Account team.</p>
                        
                        
                        <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                        <th align="left" style="width: 50%;"><strong>Data Center Edition License with Software Assurance</strong></th>
                        <th align="left" style="width: 50%;"><strong>Standard Edition License with Software Assurance</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                        <td class="left_align">
                            <ul>
                                <li>Two virtual machines can be deployed with each dual processor license, with up to 8 cores per virtual machine.</li>
                                <li>Save up to 20% on Azure deployment costs.</li>
                                <li>Each license can be used both locally and in Azure.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                        <td class="left_align">
                            <ul>
                                <li>Two virtual machines can be deployed with each dual processor license, with up to 8 cores per virtual machine.</li>
                                <li>Save up to 20% on Azure deployment costs.</li>
                                <li>Each license can either be used locally or in Azure.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                        </tr>
                        </table>
                                    
                        <h1>Case analysis</h1>
                        <div style="text-align: left;"><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/hybrid-use-benefit-save.jpg" alt="A-HUB-comparison" title="" style="max-width:auto;height:auto;"></div>
                        </br>
                        <p>This example shows the costs that customers can save compared to other public clouds by running Windows Server through Azure. Customers only need to pay for basic computing resources after using a local Windows Server license with Software Assurance.</p>
                        
                        <p>*The savings estimate is based on the A4 version operated by 21Vianet in mainland China. The example is a one-year estimate using the pricing on September 13, 2016. Pricing is subject to change without notice.</p>
                        
                        
                        <h1>How to participate in the A-HUB benefit plan</h1>
                        
                        <ul>
                        <li><strong>Confirm eligibility and calculate licenses.</strong> For each Windows Server dual processor license with Software Assurance, customers can run two virtual machines with up to 8 cores or a 16-core virtual machine, whichever is lower in price.</li>
                        
                        <li><strong>Upload image file.</strong> You need to create a Windows Server virtual machine locally using Windows PowerShell, add the Azure Hybrid Use Benefit tag to it, then upload it to Azure.</li>
                        
                        <li><strong>Benefit from significant savings.</strong> Azure will subsequently bill at the non-Windows virtual machine rate.</li>
                        </ul>
                        
                        </br></br>
                        <p><strong>Special tip:</strong></p>
                        <p>1. This plan is only valid for genuine Windows Server software and assurance (SA) customers within the validity period. 21Vianet will audit users who use the plan and make necessary adjustments to user prices based on the audit results, and/or request customers to make up the balance from their previous bill.</p>
                        <p>2. Reminder that CPP and A-HUB (Azure Hybrid Use Benefit) cannot overlap or be shared: If your virtual machine already contains multiple deals, you will only be eligible for individual discounts which cannot overlap or be shared.</p>
                        <p>3. The CPP plan is a yearly service for virtual machines. It currently only applies to Online Service Premium Agreements.</p>
                    </div>
                    <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 --> <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-2 -->
                    <div class="tab-control-container" id="tabContent2">
                        <h1>Save up to 30% on Azure SQL Database with Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server</h1>
                        <p>By using an existing SQL Server license, you can maximize your current Software Assurance investment to save up to 30% on vCore-based SQL Database options.</p>
                        <h2>Save up to 30% now</h2>
                        <img style="width:470px;" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/sql-ahub-compare.jpg" alt=""/>

                        <h1 style="margin-top:40px;">Get more benefits for virtualized workloads in SQL Database</h1>
                        <h2>SQL Server license replacement value</h2>
                        <div class="azure-hybird">
                            <div class="azure-hybird-sql">
                                <p>SQL Database vCore-based options</p>
                                
                                <img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/sql-tradein-value.jpg" alt=""/>
                                
                                <p>SQL Servers have software guarantees</p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <h2>For Azure only: Get more for virtualized workloads</h2>
                        <p>SQL Server Enterprise Edition customers who have Software Assurance and use unlimited virtualization benefits can migrate to SQL Database at a cost-effective rate.</p>
                        <p>When the General Purpose option is selected, Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server can offer Server Enterprise Edition customers with Software Assurance 4 cores in the cloud for every 1 on-premises core. The General Purpose option best meets the needs of virtualized workloads and can be implemented in a cost-effective way to migrate to SQL Database.</p>

                        <h1>Activate Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server</h1>
                        <h2>Already using Azure?</h2>
                        <p>Register an SQL Database Managed Instance from the <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a> or via <a href="//market.azure.cn/zh-cn/marketplace/apps/Microsoft.WindowsServer">Azure Marketplace</a>.</p>
                        <p>Try out an SQL Database single database or elastic pool from the <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a> or via <a href="//market.azure.cn/zh-cn/marketplace/apps/Microsoft.WindowsServer">Azure Marketplace</a>.</p>

                        <!-- <h2>是 Azure 的新手？<a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/zh-cn/pricing/purchase-options/?v=17.10">创建免费帐户</a></h2> -->

                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h1>FAQ</h1>
                    <span class="faq-floder"><em>Expand All</em></span>
                    </div>
                    <div class="more-detail floder-layer">
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="home_azure-hybrid-benefit-sql1">What is a vCore?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>A virtual core (vCore) represents the logical CPUs available to the server. Customers can choose between two generations of hardware. For servers created using the Gen4 vCore, the vCore is based on the Intel E5-2673 v3 (Haswell) 2.4 GHz processor. For servers created using the Gen5 vCore, the vCore is based on the Intel E5-2673 v4 (Broadwell) 2.3 GHz processor.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql2">What are the advantages of vCore-based models in Azure SQL Database?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>With a vCore-based purchasing model, local workload requirements can be translated to the cloud in a flexible, controlled, and direct manner. This allows independent scaling of calculation and storage resources based on workload requirements.</p>
                                    <p>A vCore-based model is suitable for SQL Database Managed Instances, single databases, and elastic pool deployment options. These options all use Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. Therefore, pricing within a vCore-based model applies whether or not you use Hybrid Benefit:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Licenses included: Does not include Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. This option is suitable for customers who are reluctant to apply existing SQL Server licenses with Software Assurance to vCore-based database deployment options.</li>
                                        <li>Baseline rate: Discount price that includes Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. Customers can choose this price by using an SQL Server license with Software Assurance.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql3">What is Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server? Am I eligible to use it?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server can help you to maximize the value of your current license investment and accelerate migration to the cloud. Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server is an Azure-based hybrid benefit. An SQL Server license with Software Assurance can be used through it in order to pay less SQL Database charges (baseline rate). All vCore-based options can be used via Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server: SQL Database Managed Instances, single databases, and elastic pools. You can apply this benefit even if SKUs are active, but please note that the baseline rate will be applied from when you make a selection in the portal. The credit limit will not be reissued.</p>
                                    <p>You can activate Azure Hybrid Benefit by proving that you have a valid license with Software Assurance in the Azure portal. The working principles for Azure Hybrid Benefit are as follows:</p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>If you have the Standard Edition with Software Assurance, issued per core license, choose the General Purpose option and get 1 vCore for every 1 local license core.</li>
                                        <li>If you have the Enterprise Edition with Software Assurance, issued per core license, select the Business-Critical option (coming soon) and get 1 vCore for every 1 local license core. Note: The Business-Critical option for Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server is only offered to Enterprise Edition customers.</li>
                                        <li>If you have the highly-virtualized Enterprise Edition with Software Assurance, issued per core license, choose the General Purpose option and get 4 vCores for every 1 local license core. This is a unique virtualization benefit that is limited to Azure.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql4">What are virtualization benefits?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Virtualization benefits apply to virtualized workloads on vCore-based Azure SQL Databases. They can be used to convert 1 SQL Enterprise Edition core through valid Software Assurance, to get up to 4 General Purpose vCores at the baseline rate. This is a cost-effective way to migrate virtualized applications to vCore-based SQL Databases. For example, if you have 4 core licenses for SQL Enterprise Edition, you can get up to 16 General Purpose vCores at the baseline rate.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql5">Can I use an SQL Server license on-premises and in the cloud?</a>
                                <section>
                                   <p>The license must be used on-premises or in the cloud, but there is a grace period of 180 days during which the license can be used both on-premises and in the cloud to facilitate migration.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql6">Can Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server be applied retrospectively?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>No. Azure Hybrid Benefit cannot be applied retrospectively.</p>    
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql7">If Software Assurance expires, what will happen to Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>Valid Software Assurance is required to use Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. If your Software Assurance expires and you do not renew it, you will be redirected to the "license included" pricing corresponding to the SKU.</p>    
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="azure-hybrid-benefit-sql8">Which products are eligible to use Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server?</a>
                                <section>
                                     <p>This hybrid benefit only applies to SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS) and vCore-based Azure SQL Database options: managed instances, single databases, and elastic pools.</p>    
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>Other resources</h1>
                <!-- <h2>完整的常见问题</h2>
                <p><a href="//azure.microsoft.com/zh-cn/pricing/hybrid-benefit/faq/">查看有关 Azure 混合权益的常见问题</a></p> -->
                <h2>Datasheet</h2>
                <p><a href="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/Windows_Server_Azure_Hybrid_Use_Benefit_Datasheet.pdf">Download a summary of the Azure Hybrid Benefit</a></p>
                <h2>Windows Server on Azure</h2>
                <p><a href="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/Ultimate-Guide-to-Windows-Server-on-Azure.pdf">Download the Ultimate Guide to Windows Server on Azure</a></p>
                <h2>Documentation</h2>
                <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/hybrid-use-benefit-licensing">Review technical tutorials and more resources</a></p>
                <div class="tags-date">
                    <div class="ms-date">1 Actual savings may vary based on location, instance type or usage</div><br />
                    <div class="ms-date">2 Savings based on two D2 v2 Promo virtual machines in West US 2 Region running 550 hours per month for 12 months, base compute rate at CentOS or Ubuntu Linux rate for West US 2, and Software Assurance cost (Level A) for Windows Server Standard edition (one 2-processor license or a set of 16 core licenses). Actual savings may vary based on location, instance type or usage. Prices as of June 2017. Prices subject to change.</div>
                </div>
            </div>
                                                                                               
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Hybrid Benefit - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-hybird-benefit</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure Hybrid Benefit</metaKeywords>
    <banner><![CDATA[
      <!-- BEGIN: Banner -->
          <div class="common-banner" id="azure-hybired-contact-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'', 'backgroundImage':'','imageHeight':''}">      
            <div class="common-banner-image">
                <div class="common-banner-title">
                    <h1>Azure Hybrid Benefit<span>（Azure Hybrid Benefit）</span></h1>
                    <p>Use Windows Server or SQL Server for cost-effective migration to the cloud.</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Use Azure Hybrid Benefit and Reserved Instances, save up to 82% of the cost on Windows Server；</li>
                        <li>Use Azure Hybrid Benefits when migrating to Azure SQL database <sup>1</sup> saving up to 30% <sup>2</sup> of the cost；</li>
                        <li>At your own pace - migrate some workload or an entire datacenter;</li>
                        <li>Maximize using current Software Assurance Investment  。</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
          </div>  
        <!-- End: Banner-->
    ]]></banner>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[You can use existing licenses and Software Assurance to save up to 40% on Windows Server virtual machine costs, and obtain all the advantages of cloud computing.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Azure Hybrid Benefit</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
