<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage id="12103" parentID="12095" level="3" writerID="106" creatorID="22" nodeType="1059" template="15" sortOrder="3" createDate="2012-05-29T21:04:52" updateDate="2018-10-12T14:20:00" nodeName="FAQ" urlName="faq" writerName="content" creatorName="Brad" path="-1,11978,12095,12103" isDoc="">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
        <div class="section-component">
            <!-- <h2>Please select the category of FAQ to browse</h2> -->
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="tab-control-selector">
                <a href="#" data-href="#general" id="faq-general" class="active">General inquiries</a> 
                <a href="#" data-href="#registration" id="faq-registration">Registration</a> 
                <a href="#" data-href="#billingAndSubscription" id="faq-billingAndSubscription">Billing, subscriptions and Fapiao</a> 
                <a href="#" data-href="#implementationAndMaintenance" id="faq-implementationAndMaintenance">Technical</a> 
                <a href="#" data-href="#wd-support" id="wd-faq-support">Online Purchase Customer Support</a> 
                <a href="#" data-href="#ea-support" id="ea-faq-support">Enterprise Customer Support</a> 
                <a href="#" id="new_control_bexpend" class="faq-floder"><em>Show all</em></a>
                <div class="clearfix"></div>
                <div class="floder-layer">
                    <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="general">   
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                            <div class="more-detail">
                                <h2>General Inquiries</h2>
                                <ul>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-1" href="#q-1-1">What is Azure?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure is a flexible and open cloud platform that enables you to quickly build, deploy, and manage applications in the data centers. Azure supports all major operating systems, languages, or development tools and integrates public cloud applications with the existing IT infrastructure.</p>
                                                <p>Azure offers international class Service Level Agreements that enable you to build and run highly available applications without having to focus on the infrastructure. It provides the ability to automatically repair operating systems and services, and has built-in network load balancing and hardware fault recovery capabilities. It supports the deployment models that allow you to upgrade applications with no downtime.</p>
                                                <p>Azure enables you to generate applications in any language and by any framework or tool. Azure utilizes the public functions and services of open REST protocol. Azure’s client libraries are available in a variety of programming languages and are published under open source licenses and hosted on GitHub.</p>
                                                <p>Azure offers a flexible cloud platform that meets the needs of any application.</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_new" href="/what-is-new/">What's New</a></li>
                                                    
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_sta" href="/starter-guide/">Starter Guide</a></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-2" href="#q-1-2">What are the prices of Azure services in China?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>We will continue to update and release more information on pricing. You can get the latest information on the <a id="FAQ-1" href="/pricing/overview/">Pricing Page</a>.
												
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-3" href="#q-1-3">Are Azure services in China the same as Azure services in other areas?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>In China, <a id="support_faq_wa" href="//www.azure.cn/">Azure</a> is operated by Shanghai Blue Cloud Technology Co., Ltd., a wholly-owned subsidiary of Beijing 21Vianet Broadband Data Center Co., Ltd. (abbreviated as "21Vianet"). 21Vianet is China’s largest neutral third-party Internet infrastructure service telecommunications provider to which Microsoft has authorized technologies. In China, Azure combines Microsoft’s global technologies and 21Vianet’s local operating experience to build an enterprise-level international cloud computing platform for China.</p>
                                                <p>Outside China, <a id="support_faq_mic" href="//azure.microsoft.com/">Microsoft Azure is operated by Microsoft itself</a>. China’s Azure customers will be able to enjoy exactly the same user experiences and service level as customers in other areas.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-4" href="#q-1-4">What is an SLA (Service Level Agreement)? What kind of SLA does Azure offer in China?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>We provide international class Service Level Agreements for each of the Azure services that are officially available for commercial use. If a certain service level is not reached, the customer can receive the corresponding service fee deduction. Details on SLAs provided by Azure in China are listed at: <a id="FAQ-2" href="/support/legal/sla/" class="single-link">Service Level Agreements</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-5" href="#q-1-5">What are some success stories of Azure in China?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>In China, a large number of enterprises like GMW.cn, Linekong, Spring Airlines, Mobike, Digital China, Coca Cola, Kingdee, PPTV, ChinaCache, and Qoros have landed onto the Azure platform in China. Please go to the <a id="FAQ-3" href="/partnerancasestudy/case-studies/">Success Stories</a> page for more information on these cases.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-6" href="#q-1-6">How is Virtual Machines charged? Why does my virtual machine still incur costs when it’s stopped?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Virtual Machines billing consists of two parts: the cost of the virtual machine itself and the cost iccurred by its disk (including managed disk and non-managed disk), so as long as your virtual machine and the disk are not deleted, disk storage cost always exists. Please refer to the<a href="/pricing/details/storage/"> Price Details of Disc Storage</a> for billing details.</p>
                                                <p>In addition, note that the two virtual machine statuses "Stopped" and "Stopped (de-allocated)" are charged differently. Please refer to the following table:</p>
                                                <table>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <th>Status</th>
                                                        <th>Virtual Machine cost</th>
                                                        <th>Disc cost</th>
                                                        <th>Detailed information</th>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Starting Up</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>This is the initial starting state of the virtual machine, during which the virtual machine is going through a startup cycle and is charged as normal, as the virtual machine is running.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Running (already started)</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>The virtual machine is running and charged as normal.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Stopped</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>The shutdown operation is performed through the virtual machine, and the virtual machine will be in a "Stopped (de-allocated)" state. During this time, the core is not released, so the virtual machine is still being charged.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Stopped (de-allocated)</td>
                                                        <td>No</td>
                                                        <td>Yes</td>
                                                        <td>The shutdown operation is performed through the <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a>, and the virtual machine will be "Stopped (de-allocated)". During this time, the computing resources will no longer be allocated to the virtual machine, so the virtual machine will no longer be charged for it. However the cost of disk storage still exists, as the disk still exists.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Deleted (including the disk)</td>
                                                        <td>No</td>
                                                        <td>No</td>
                                                        <td>You should ensure the disk has been deleted while deleting the virtual machine. Otherwise, there will still be disk storage costs.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                </table>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-7" href="#q-1-7">How do I select Azure computing services: Web Apps, Cloud Services or Virtual Machines? If I’m an enterprise user, which services should I select to migrate the existing enterprise applications to the Azure cloud computing platform when provided with these three different computing capabilities?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>According to the following characteristics, you can select the service that is suitable for your needs:</p>
                                                <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <th align="center">&#160;</th>
                                                        <th align="center"><strong>Characteristics</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="center"><strong>Suitable For</strong></th>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td><a id="support_faq_web" href="/home/features/web-site/">Web Apps</a></td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>You can easily deploy a highly scalable cloud environment by building a highly scalable website on Azure, which can start at a very small scale.</li>
                                                                <li>You can use language and open source applications of your own choice, such as WordExpress, FTP, Git or TFS, and easily integrate them with Azure services, such as SQL databases, caches, CDN and storage.</li>
                                                                <!-- <li>Web 应用的特点在于快速部署，只能提供基本功能，比如 Application 和 Data。它不支持高级功能，比如 Startup Task，Native Code，Virtual Network 等。
                                                                </li> -->
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Modern Web Apps. Include client scripts, server-side scripts and database applications, and can be scaled horizontally.</li>
                                                                <li>Continuous development. You can use Git or Team Foundation directly from the source code libraries for deployment.</li>
                                                                <li>Using open source applications. You can directly use open source applications, such as WordPress.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td><a id="support_faq_clo" href="/home/features/cloud-services/">Cloud Service</a></td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Expand your enterprise applications on Azure.</li>
                                                                <li>A rich PaaS environment can be utilized to create highly available and scalable applications and services. Advanced multi-layer architecture, automatic deployment and elastic computing are supported.</li>
                                                                <li>Through a virtual network, you can connect the network of the local LAN to the Azure public cloud network to allow the enterprise network to enjoy the highly elastic computing and interoperability brought by the public cloud, while ensuring network security.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>For multi-layer applications, each layer can expand itself. When using Web Role and Worker Role, Web Role can respond to the display at the front end, while the complex business is handled at the back end.</li>
                                                                <li>Advanced management. You can use Cloud Service if your application requires administrator rights, remote desktop access, or escalated authority to run the code.</li>
                                                                <li>Private cloud + public cloud. You can use Azure Connect for point-to-point connection with Azure or use the Azure virtual network to connect the enterprise internal or private network to Azure.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td><a id="support_faq_vir" href="/home/features/virtual-machines/">Virtual Machines </a></td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>IaaS service is provided. Windows and Linux operating systems are supported</li>
                                                                <li>You can easily deploy and run Windows Server and Linux virtual machine and migrate the operating load in a few minutes, without changing the existing code. For applications based on Windows OS, you can deploy them to Hyper-V, save it as a VHD file and upload it to Azure for deployment and management.</li>
                                                                <li>Virtual network supported. You can connect your LAN enterprise application with the public cloud directly and enjoy the convenience of cloud computing.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Windows or Linux supported. You can quickly migrate the existing Windows or Linux applications to Azure.</li>
                                                                <li>More service applications are supported. You can use SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, and SharePoint applications in Azure.</li>
                                                                <li>Migrating existing applications to the public cloud is supported. You can save persistent non-relational data in Azure VHD.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                </table>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-8" href="#q-1-8">How do Azure services in China ensure the security of users’ data and services?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Security and stability of Cloud Services have always been the focus of the industry. As the first international public cloud service landed in China, Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet has gained recognition from many industry users, and provided users with reliable, flexible and highly valuable public Cloud Services.</p>
                                                <p>
                                                    Being the first to land all-round cloud services including IaaS, PaaS, SaaS in China , and reliable localized operation, international standard monthly Service Level Agreements with financial security, powerful data security, rich client returns and other advantages, Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet has obtained 6 credible cloud certifications including Yunfen, Cloud Engine (Cloud Services) and the Whole Network Load Balancing (Traffic Manager), representing recognition from the industry for the quality of localized international  cloud service provided by 21Vianet.
                                                </p>
                                                <p>
                                                    Moreover, according to the GBT 22240-2008 Information Security Technology - Guide on Determination of Security Protection Levels for Information Systems, the assessment organization authorized by the Ministry of Public Security has conducted an assessment of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet as per GB/T 22239-2008 Information Security Technology - Basic Requirements of Security Protection Levels of Information Systems. The Information Security Protection of Azure has been classified as the third Level (Information System Classified Security Protection (DJCP), Level 3) and has been issued with record-keeping certificates.
                                                </p>
                                                <p>In full compliance with China’s policies and regulations, Azure data service in China provides up to six geo-redundant backups, which are distributed in 2 data centers (China North and China East). In addition, with decades of experience in providing enterprise customers with online services applied in the Azure platform, we strive to keep the leading position in the industry in terms of security, privacy and control and compliance practices.</p>
                                                <p>For more details, see the <a id="support_faq7_tru" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/">Data Security</a>, <a id="support_faq7_sec" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/security/">Privacy</a> and <a id="support_faq7_pri" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/privacy/">FAQ</a> pages in the Azure <a id="support_faq7_faq" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/resources/FAQ.html">Trust Center</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-9" href="#q-1-9">I have an MSDN subscription, and when I enable "Azure Benefit" for my account, can this service be available in Azure China at the same time?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>No. China's Azure service is operated by 21Vianet. The "Azure Benefit" in your account can only be operated on platforms in other areas of Azure. MSDN accounts cannot be enabled on Azure China's platform operated by 21Vianet. If you’re interested in applying for one of the Microsoft Azure services operated by 21Vianet, please fill out the <a id="FAQ-7" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/">Azure Trial Application Form</a> to experience Azure with the 1RMB Trial plan.
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <!-- <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-10" href="#q-1-10">Does Azure support open-source software in China?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure supports a large number of open source applications, frameworks and languages, and the number is still growing. We understand that developers want to use the most suitable tools based on their own experience, skill, tool and application needs, and our goal is to allow developers to choose tools as needed.</p>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li> -->
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-11" href="#q-1-11">What kind of roles does Microsoft play in Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Microsoft Azure in China is a public cloud platform that is operated and sold independently by 21Vianet in China mainland. Based on Microsoft's decades of rich online service experience for global enterprise customers, Azure, a world-class technology, is developed to fully serve customers in China, and guarantee to provide globally consistent service quality for our customers all over the world.</p>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-12" href="#q-1-12">Where can I find details on the new features?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can find the details of the new features through the <a href="/what-is-new/">What's New</a>.</p>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-13" href="#q-1-13">How will 21Vianet use the information I stored in Azure?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>21Vianet will only use the customer data you stored in Azure to provide you with Azure services. These services may include the troubleshooting for preventing, detecting, or fixing issues that affect the operation of Azure; and also the improvement of features that detect and resist emerging and evolving threats to users (such as malicious software and junk mail).</p>
                                                <p>As per 21Vianet policy, in addition to providing you with cloud productivity services, we will never mine or use your customer data for advertising purposes. If you want to know more about our commitment regarding your data, please go to the <a href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/privacy/">Privacy </a>and <a href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/resources/FAQ.html">FAQ</a> pages in the Azure Trust Center.</p>				
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-14" href="#q-1-14">I want to learn more about Azure. In addition to the Starter Guide, do you have any further study materials?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can browse the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/">Documentation Center</a>.</p>
                                                <p>This page contains links and the following content:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Developer center: .NET, Node.js, Java, Python</li>
                                                    <li>Details of various services: computing, data services, app services, network</li>
                                                    <li>Multiple resources: architectural structure, reference documentation, advice on effective use, performance, and answer to questions, etc.</li>
                                                    
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>Publish and search questions in the <a href="//social.msdn.microsoft.com/Forums/zh-CN/home?forum=windowsazurezhchs">Azure Forum</a>.</p>
                                                <p>Browse the <a href="//school.azure.cn/">Azure School</a> for related Azure courses and expert columns.</p>
                                                <p>Browse <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/">Azure Operations Guide</a> for Azure common questions and instructions.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-15" href="#q-1-15">Are all data stored in Azure encrypted? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure provides Storage Service Encryption for all new and existing storage accounts. Your data is secured by default. For more information, see<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/storage/common/storage-service-encryption">Azure Storage Service Encryption for Static Data</a>(Chinese).</p>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-1-16" href="#q-1-16">What cloud and data security certifications has Azure obtained in China? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>See our <a href="//www.trustcenter.cn/en-us/compliance/default.html">Trust Center</a>for the latest content.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                   
                                </ul>   
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="tab-control-container" id="registration">
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                            <div class="more-detail">
                                <h2>Registration Questions</h2>
                                <ul>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-1" href="#q-2-1">What is the 1RMB Trial subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>
                                                   This is a promotional activity launched by the Microsoft Azure and operated by 21Vianet. You can sign up online and pay RMB1 to activate your 1RMB Trial subscription and get RMB1,500 in Azure service credits that are valid for one month.
                                                </p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_offers" href="/offers/ms-mc-azr-44p/">Details of the 1RMB Trial Subscription Promotion</a></li>
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_1rmb-trial-full" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial-full/?form-type=identityauth/">Apply for 1RMB Trial Now</a></li>
													<li><a id="support_faq_1rmb-trial-sign-up-guidance" href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-with-1rmb-trial-subscription/">Sign up process for the 1RMB Trial subscription</a></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-2" href="#q-2-2">What is the standard Pay-in-Advance (PIA) subscription? What are the characteristics of such subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Standard Pay-in-Advance (PIA) subscription needs to be purchased by Pay-in-Advance. The balance will be deducted according to the actual usage of the user, and overuse is not supported. When the balance is 0, the service will be stopped immediately, and recharge is required to continue using. The minimum prepayment amount of standard Pay-in-Advance (PIA) subscription is RMB1,000 with online payment, and RMB5,000 with Wire Transfer, which is valid for 12 months after each recharge. </p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_standard" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">Standard Pay-in-Advance (PIA) Product Details</a></li>
                                                    <li><a id="support_faq_pia-waiting-list" href="/pricing/pia-waiting-list/?form-type=identityauth/">I want to purchase</a></li>
													<li><a id="support_faq_pia-sign-up-guidance" href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-and-get-a-pia-subscription/">Standard Pay-in-Advance Subscription Process</a></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-3" href="#q-2-3">Can I apply and sign up for more than one 1RMB Trial Subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>No. In order to allow more customers to experience Azure services, each new customer has only one opportunity to enjoy this promotion, and only one purchase can be made for the same identification card and the same paid account.</p>
                                                <p>If you need more than one subscription, or your 1RMB Trial subscription has expired, please use the <a href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-4" href="#q-2-4">What should I do when a phone validation problem is met while signing up for the 1RMB Trial?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>If you have applied for the 1RMB Trial subscription with your mobile phone number and passed verification via the mobile phone, and you did not complete the entire sign up process before quitting, then you may not be able to apply again with the same phone number. If you encounter such problems, try using another mobile phone number to revalidate, or you can contact the <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet support team</a> for help.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-5" href="#q-2-5">Do I have to provide identification card information to complete the registration?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes, in order to comply with the requirements of relevant laws and regulations and ensure the safety of each subscriber’s account, each registered user needs to provide personal identity information for real-name system certification, so as to obtain secure Azure service.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-6" href="#q-2-6">What is Organization, OrganizationID and Account?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Organization usually refers to an enterprise or other group such as a school.<p>An enterprise can also sign up multiple organizations in Azure AD, e.g. different departments are registered as different organizations.</p>
                                                    <p>Multiple enterprises can also jointly sign up in Azure AD as an organization for a collaborative project.</p></li>
                                                    <li>OrganizationID, or OrgID for short, is a special user name system provided by Microsoft Azure, which is operated by 21Vianet.
                                                        <p>Currently, the domain available for sign up is *.partner.onmschina.cn. The * represents the user’s registered name, which is the unique identifier of the organization registered in Azure AD by the user.</p></li>
                                                    <li>Account is the account created by a customer in a registered organization and can be used to sign in to a subscription.<p>If the customer’s registered organization domain name is contoso.partner.onmschina.cn, you can create an account for ABC in the organization: ABC@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn.</p></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-7" href="#q-2-7">I have an Office 365 account. Can I use the account information for Azure subscription registration?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes. If you have already bought Office 365 products and want to use the same account to manage Office 365 and Azure services at the same time, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-use-existing-office-365-account-azure-subscription">purchasing an Azure subscription via an Office 365 account</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-8" href="#q-2-8">After creating the account, if the whole signup process is not completed, how can I get back to the previous account and continue sign up?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You may sign into <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a> or <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/">Azure account center</a> with the account you created earlier, and you may see either of two prompts:</p>
                                               <p>1. When you see the yellow bar reminder that "Your XXXX is waiting for payment", select the yellow Pay for the Suspended Subscription bar below to continue to pay</p>
                                               <p>Note: Using the UnionPay Online payment, after the order is submitted, the payment should be completed within 15 minutes. If the payment time is over 15 minutes, the payment may not be successfully done and the order should be resubmitted.</p>
                                               <p>2. If you see the message that "No subscription has been found" or "It appears that you haven't created a subscription",</p>
                                               <p>you can refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/commerce/billing/aog-billing-no-subscription-found">tips for "No subscription has been found" in the Azure portal or the Azure Account Center</a> for help.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-9" href="#q-2-9">When signing up for an Azure account, why do I see "Sorry! The 1RMB Trial subscription/Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA service is not available. You are not eligible for this specific Promo product/service"?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>This prompt indicates that the activation code of your registered Azure account is expired and needs to be re-applied. Please refer to the <a id="support_faq_promo" href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-with-1rmb-trial-subscription">1RMB Trial subscription signup</a> for the specific application process.</p>
												
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-10" href="#q-2-10">When an Azure account is registered, the payment information cannot be loaded or the payment information is not received during the payment stage.</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>If this problem occurs, the possible reason is that your browser does not support third-party Cookies, and you can refer to "<a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/articles/azure-operations-guide/commerce/billing/aog-billing-sign-in-issues-faq">Azure online sign up FAQs</a>" for more help.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-11" href="#q-2-11">When applying for the 1RMB Trial subscription, why is there a message showing that payment was successful, but when I return to the Azure registration page, I still see a payment failure message?</a>
                                            <section>
                                               <p>Each new customer can only enjoy this trial offer once, so one paid account (including UnionPay and Alipay accounts) can only be used to apply for 1RMB Trial once. If you use a payment account that has successfully applied for the trial subscription to apply again and pay RMB1, the aforementioned problem will occur, namely: the subscription page shows that payment is complete, but the Azure sign up page shows that payment has failed.</p>
                                               <p>The refund system will automatically return the money to the paid account for the RMB1 transaction. The specific refund time will be different due to the different operations of each bank and bank card.</p>
                                               <p>If you need more than one subscription, or have tried the 1RMB Trial subscription, please refer to the <a href="//www.azure.cn/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA Subscription</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-12" href="#q-2-12">When does the one-month validity of the 1RMB Trial subscription start?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Validity starts from successful payment and lasts one month.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-13" href="#q-2-13">In the one-month validity period of the 1RMB Trial subscription, can the subscription be converted into a standard Pay-in-Advance subscription? How do I do this?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes. You can upgrade the subscription to the Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription at any time during the validity of the 1RMB Trial. You can click "Upgrade now" at the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions">Azure Account Center</a> and recharge at least RMB1,000 to your account to turn it into a Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-upgrade-1rmb-trial">1RMB Trial subscription upgrade detailed procedures</a>.</p>
												
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
										
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-14" href="#q-2-14">How should I monitor the balance and the period of validity, in order to avoid any inconvenience caused by the cease of service?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>During the service period for Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet, you will receive a reminder email of the balance and expiration in your contact email every week. You can also sign into the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions">Azure account center</a> to check the balance and the validity at any time. It is recommended that you make an assessment based on the actual usage and reserve a sufficient balance.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
                                    
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-15" href="#q-2-15">Is payment by wire transfer supported? What should I do?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>1RMB Trial subscription<p>Not supported. The 1RMB Trial subscription only supports Alipay and UnionPay online payment.</p> </li>
                                                    <li>Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription<p>Supported. The Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription supports three payment methods, i.e. Alipay, UnionPay and online payment and wire transfer. The minimum payment amount of the first two online payment methods is RMB1,000, the lowest payment amount of wire transfer is RMB5,000. Please refer to the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer">wire transfer instructions</a> for detailed wire transfer operations.</p></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-2-16" href="#q-2-16">Can I use foreign currency for remittance when I choose to pay by wire transfer for my Azure subscription account?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Only the Chinese yuan is accepted as the payment currency for Azure’s service in China.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
                                </ul>   
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="tab-control-container" id="billingAndSubscription">
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                            <div class="more-detail">
                                <h2>Billing, subscription and Fapiao</h2>
                                <ul>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-1" href="#q-3-1">What should I do if I cannot complete the full subscription ID due to the bank’s limits?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can send the following remittance information to azure_invoice@oe.21vianet.com, so that we can distinguish the remittance sources and recharge your subscription in a timely manner.</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Subscription ID (you can sign in to the <a href="https://account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_account">Azure Account Center</a>, click the subscription name, and the "Subscription ID" appears on the right side of the page).</li>
                                                    <li>Remittance amount</li>
													<li>Remittance date</li>
													<li>Remittance bank account</li>
													<li>Name of remitter (remitter on the remittance slip)</li>
													<li>Company name</li>
													<li>Mobile phone of contact</li>
                                                </ul>                                                          
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
				
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-2" href="#q-3-2">How can I upgrade the 1RMB Trial to a Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription, or recharge a Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                
                                                <p>The Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription supports three payment methods, i.e. Alipay, UnionPay and Online Payment and wire transfer, and each payment method has the minimum recharge amount. If you select "Alipay" or "UnionPay Online" and other methods of online remittance, after clicking on "Upgrade" or "Recharge", enter the recharge amount according to the prompt (the minimum amount is RMB1,000, and the maximum amount is RMB150,000), and then click on the check mark. The payment page will appear and you should follow the instructions to complete the payment. If you select wire transfer, the minimum recharge amount should be RMB5,000. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-recharge-an-existing-pia-subscription" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_billing-recharge-an-existing-pia-subscription">recharging Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscriptions</a> for details.</p>
                                                <p>Note: Microsoft Azure services currently operated by 21Vianet only accepts payments in RMB.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-3" href="#q-3-3">What’s the time zone in usage report? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                
                                                <p>Azure is a global service. To ensure that customers located in different physical locations can share with the same time zone, we use Coordinated Universal Time (UTC) to calculate the usage.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-4" href="#q-3-4">How to download and analyze the monthly usage report?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Users purchasing online (including 1RMB Trials and Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscriptions)</p>
												<ul>
													<li>Download<p>The usage report can be obtained via the platform, including the monthly consumption summary, billing amount and daily consumption of each service. This operation is restricted to the account managers who purchase subscriptions online. For detailed steps, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-get-usage-information" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_billing-get-usage-information">Downloading monthly usage reports for online purchasers</a>.</p></li>
													<li>Analysis<p>The monthly usage report is presented in Excel format, which consists of three parts:</p>
                                                    <p>* Subscription and account validity information</p>
                                                    <p>* Monthly service usage and billing information</p>
                                                    <p>* Daily service usage</p>
                                                    <p>Refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-understand-your-usage" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_billing-understand-your-usage">Understanding monthly usage reports</a> for details.</p>
                                                </li>
																				
												</ul>
												<p>Enterprise Agreement User</p>
												<ul>
													<li>Download<p>You can sign into the<a href="https://ea.azure.cn/" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_ea-azure-protal"> Enterprise Portal</a> to view the historic usage and current remaining amount in the contract. The usage in the system can be delayed for up to 5 days, and you can see the details by date through the Download Usage feature.</p>
                                                    <p>The <a href="https://ea.azure.cn/" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_ea-azure-protal1">Enterprise Portal</a> provides customers with three viewing methods: monthly report downloading, advanced report downloading and API access key. The monthly report and advanced report provide the service content, service amount and the corresponding billing amount consumed in each department, account and subscription every day up to the date of the report. Please refer to <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-get-ea-usage-info" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_billing-get-ea-usage-info">Downloading usage reports for Enterprise Agreement users</a> for details.</p></li>
													<li>Analysis<p>The monthly usage report is presented in CSV format, which provides each account and the corresponding usage information every day, including usage and the corresponding costs. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-understand-ea-usage-report" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_billing-understand-ea-usage-report">Understanding Monthly Usage Reports</a> for details.</p></li>	
												</ul>
												<p>In order to help you better use Azure and boost your cloud business, Azure provides you with informative training tutorials. You can refer to the Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA billing portal training at the <a href="https://www.azure.cn/video-center/" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_video-center">Azure Video Center</a> to understand the specific operations for creating pivot tables through bills.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-5" href="#q-3-5">How are the remaining days and remaining credits viewed?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ol>
													<li>Sign into the <a id="subscriptions-remaining-days-account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Center</a></li>
													<li>Click the subscription for which you want to view the remaining days and the remaining credits</li>
													<li>The remaining days and remaining credits are displayed on the right side of the page</li>
												</ol>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-6" href="#q-3-6">Under what circumstances will my subscription be suspended? How can I reactivate it?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>1RMB Trial subscription<p>When the remaining usage of your subscription is 0 or when the usage credits expire, your subscription will be disabled. You need to recharge it within 15 days and upgrade the subscription to the Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription, and then you may continue to use this subscription.</p></li>
                                                    <li>Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription<p>When the remaining usage of your subscription is 0 or when the usage is expired, your subscription will be disabled. You need to recharge it within 90 days to resume this subscription.</p></li>
                                                    <li>Enterprise Agreement User
                                                        <p>* When the excessive amount or annual order is not paid, your subscription will be disabled. After you finish the payment, the business team will help you manually restart the contract and subscription.</p>
                                                        <p>* When your subscription is unexpectedly canceled by the account owner, you need to contact the <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet support staff</a> to help you manually restart it.</p>
                                                        <p>If the subscription is disabled for other reasons, please contact the <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet support team</a> for help.</p>
                                                    </li>
                                                </ul>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-7" href="#q-3-7">What will happen to me after my subscription is disabled? Will my data be preserved? Can I take out the data in my subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>When your subscription is disabled, the resource services deployed in the subscription will be disabled and the resources in temporary storage will be released. You can still sign into the portal to view the resources, but you can't edit them.</p>
                                                <p>The data in your subscription will be preserved, but at the time, the data cannot be backed up. The data can be exported only after the subscription is reactivated. If it is not recharged within the specified period, your subscription and all the data in the subscription will be automatically deleted.</p>
                                                <p>* After the 1RMB Trial subscription is suspended, your data will be kept for 15 days, and if you recharge it within 15 days, the subscription can be resumed.</p>
                                                <p>* After the Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription is suspended, your data will be kept for 90 days, and if you recharge it within 90 days, the subscription can be resumed.</p>
                                                <p>* After the Enterprise Agreement subscription is suspended, your data will be kept for 90 days, and you need to pay for the excess amount and annual order within 90 days. You can contact <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet customer support</a> to help you restart the subscription.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-8" href="#q-3-8">What are the payment methods for my subscription? Can I change after the selection?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>1RMB Trial subscription
                                                        <p>* New purchase: The two online payment methods of Alipay and UnionPay Online are supported, and the payment method cannot be changed before the recharge order fails.</p>
                                                        <p>* Upgrade now: The three online payment methods of Alipay, UnionPay Online and wire transfer are supported, and the payment method cannot be changed before the recharge order fails.</p>
                                                    </li>
                                                    <li>Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription
                                                        <p>* New purchase: The three online payment methods of Alipay, UnionPay Online and wire transfer are supported, and the payment method cannot be changed before the recharge order fails.</p>
                                                        <p>* Recharge: The three online payment methods of Alipay, Unionpay Online and wire transfer are supported, and the payment method can be changed at any time.</p></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-9" href="#q-3-9">How can I deal with an interruption in the process of using Alipay or UnionPay Online when purchasing a standard pay-in-advance account?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                
												<p>Sign into <a id="pay-interrupt-account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Center</a> and click the yellow bar on the underside of the subscription to continue to pay.</p>
												<p>Note: Using the UnionPay Online payment, after the order is submitted, the payment should be completed within 15 minutes. If the payment time is over 15 minutes, the payment may not be successfully done and the order should be resubmitted.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-10" href="#q-3-10">How can I get my unpaid order? How long is the valid period of the order?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Alipay Orders <p>Alipay orders are valid for 3 days. If you fail to complete the payment in time during the payment process, you can see the relevant prompt in the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions">Azure Account Center</a> within 3 days: "Your RMB1,000.00 payment is waiting to be completed. If you have already completed the payment, please check it later. Click here to complete payment before XX/XX/XXXX." Click this prompt to continue your payment. Alipay orders cannot be canceled manually. The system will automatically cancel them three days later.</p></li>
                                                    <li>UnionPay Online Orders<p>UnionPay online orders generally expire within 1 hour, after which the Azure Account Center will give you the prompt: "Recharge on your subscription failed. Please click here to try again". At this point, you can make the payment again and change the payment method.</p></li>
                                                    <li>Wire Transfer Orders<p>Wire transfer orders shall be valid for 7 working days. If the payment is not completed within 7 working days, the wire transfer order will be cancelled on the back-end. If you need to cancel the wire transfer order, you need to contact the 21Vianet service hotline at 400-089-0365.</p>
                                                    <p>Please refer to the <a href="/pricing/billing/azure-wire-transfer-overview">Introduction to Wire Transfers</a> for operation steps and remittance information.</p></li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-11" href="#q-3-11">What should I do if I enter the wrong account/amount when I make a payment, and the payment is not completed?</a>
                                            <section>
												<ul>
                                                    <li>If you are upgrading the 1RMB Trial to a Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription or purchasing a Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription for the first time, you will be required to resubmit the order and pay for it after the expiry of the order. (UnionPay online orders are valid for 1 hour/Alipay orders are valid for 3 days/wire transfer orders are valid for 7 working days).</li>
                                                    <li>If you are recharging the Standard Pay-in-Advance PIA subscription, you can get back to the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions">Azure Account Center </a>and make the payment by clicking "Recharge".</li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-12" href="#q-3-12">Can the monthly usage report detail the cost of each Azure service I create (for example, a single virtual machine)?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>No, the billing information in the Monthly Usage Report will be aggregated according to the Azure service and related types and specifications, so you cannot accurately query the individual charge for each Azure service.</p>
                                                <p>Take the virtual machine as an example: if you have created multiple virtual machines of the same size and model, the billing information thereof will be displayed in a row in the monthly usage report. The "Consumed" column accumulates the usage of multiple virtual machines for billing.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-13" href="#q-3-13">What is the specific procedure for requesting a Fapiao? What types of Fapiaos are there? What are the space limits on a Fapiao?</a>
                                            <section>
											<ol>
                                                <li>Sign into the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/">Azure Account Center</a></li>
                                                <li>Click the subscription for which you need to apply for a Fapiao</li>
                                                <li>Click "Payment History"</li>
                                                <li>Click "Manage Fapiao" to sign up and apply. Please see <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-get-invoice">Applying for Chinese Tax Fapiaos</a> for the detailed application process.</li>
                                            </ol>
                                            <p>The Azure service in China can provide Chinese tax Fapiaos, including VAT special Fapiaos and VAT ordinary Fapiaos.</p>
                                            <p>For the Fapiao title, enterprise customers should fill in information according to the actual situation.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-14" href="#q-3-14">After applying for a Fapiao, how do I get the Fapiao? Do I have to pay any extra costs?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The Fapiao can be sent by express delivery or obtained by yourself. It is printed and delivered by 21Vianet Shanghai Blue Cloud Technology Co., Ltd, and you can select Yunda Express or SF Express (for freight collect payment only).</p>
                                                <p>Except for the above-mentioned freight payment collected by SF Express, you do not need to pay any extra fees.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-15" href="#q-3-15">When can I apply for a Fapiao?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can apply for a Fapiao within 3 working days after the payment is successfully completed. Should you have any special requirements, please contact the 21Vianet Customer Service Center at 86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-16" href="#q-3-16">What is the tax rate?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>According to relevant Chinese regulations, the tax rate for Azure Cloud Computing Services operated by 21Vianet is 6%.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-17" href="#q-3-17">How do I sign in to a Fapiao account? What should I do if I can’t apply Fapiao after activating Fapiao account successfully? What should I do if I can’t apply for Fapiao?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>After entering the <a id="support_faq_login" href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView">Fapiao Application Interface</a>, you can click “Sign Up Account” in the right corner of the page and choose the product you’ve purchased to sign up for an Azure account.</p>
                                                <p>If you are unable to apply for Fapiao after activating Fapiao account successfully, please call 21Vianet Customer Service Center: 86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p> 
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-18" href="#q-3-18">When applying for a Fapiao, I chose to obtain the Fapiao by myself. What address can I pick it up at? Can I still change to express delivery?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The self-pickup address is 21Vianet Shanghai Branch, located at Building 3, Room 657, German Centre, No.88 Keyuan Road, Pudong District, Shanghai. You can contact Zhu Qinqin at 021-28986102.</p>
                                                <p>You can sign into the <a href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView">Fapiao Management System</a> at any time to modify the delivery method of your Fapiao. For now, you can only select Yunda Express or SF Express (for freight collect payment only).</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-19" href="#q-3-19">How can I modify the registered mailbox in the Fapiao Management System?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Click the mailbox at the upper right corner of the <a href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/">Fapiao Management System</a>, and select Modify Email Address via the drop-down menu to enter your current password and new email and confirm the same. Then you can modify your email with a click. After the modification is completed, two emails will be sent to your two mailboxes, respectively, for notification.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>                                           
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-20" href="#q-3-20">What can I do if I cannot receive an activation email when signing up for an Fapiao Management System account?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Please confirm that you have filled in the correct email address. If you fill in the wrong email address, then you surely cannot receive the activation email. At this point, you cannot continue to re-sign up. You need to wait for the automatic expiry of the signup link in the activation email (the activation link is generally valid for 24 hours) before you can re-sign up with the correct mailbox.</li>
                                                    <li>After your confirmation that the email you filled in is correct, and you have not received the account activation email within 24 hours after signup, you can click the "Resend" button on the <a href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/Register">Fapiao Management System Account Signup Interface</a>, and then the system will send the account activation email to your signup email. If you still cannot receive the activation email, please contact the <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet support team</a> for help.</li>
                                                </ul>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-21" href="#q-3-21">Can I change the subscription name?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes, you can use the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/">Azure Account Center</a> or <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a> to rename your subscription. For detailed steps, please refer to the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-how-to-change-azure-account-profile" id="support_faq_how-to-change-azure-account-profile">Changing Subscription Names and Account Contacts Link</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-22" href="#q-3-22">Can I change the service administrator?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes. You need to establish new user’s information in the <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a> first, and then change the role of the service administrator through the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/">Azure Account Center</a>, referring to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/commerce/subscription-management/aog-commerce-subscription-management-billing-portal-guidance#%E8%AE%BE%E7%BD%AE%E6%9C%8D%E5%8A%A1%E7%AE%A1%E7%90%86%E5%91%98">How to Set the Service Administrator</a> for specific steps.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-23" href="#q-3-23">How to establish the subscription user’s role and authorize different management limits for users? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>There are three roles including the owner, contributor and reader under the Azure Account, and the roles are applicable to all resources. As the administrator of the account, you can distribute different roles to the business personnel in your company in accordance with the business requirements of your company. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-add-change-azure-subscription-administrator#add-azure-administrator-role">Add or Alter the Role of the Azure Administrator Managing the Subscription or Service</a> for specific steps.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-24" href="#q-3-24">How many roles does the Azure Account have? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <th align="center">Roles</th>
                                                        <th align="center"><strong>Description</strong></th>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Account Administrator (AA)</td>
                                                        <td>The account administrator possesses the login information of an OrganizationID and is able to access the account center to perform various administrative tasks. For example, creating subscriptions, canceling subscriptions, changing subscription billing, creating a user and authorizing the corresponding role of the user, and deploying the services under each subscription.</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Owner</td>
                                                        <td>The owner has full access rights to all resources in a single subscription, including the right to delegate access rights to other users</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Contributor</td>
                                                        <td>A contributor has full access rights to all resources in a single subscription, while they cannot authorize the access rights to other users</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Reader</td>
                                                        <td>A reader can check the current Azure resources in a single subscription, while they cannot deploy services or authorize roles to users</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                </table>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                   
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-25" href="#q-3-25">Can I alter the Profile of the Account Administrator? </a>
                                            <section>
                                               <p>Yes. You can alter the Profile of the Account Administrator through the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/">Azure Account Center</a>, referring to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/billing/billing-how-to-change-azure-account-profile">Change Account Subscription Name and Contact Method</a> for specific steps.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-26" href="#q-3-26">How to view the current Azure quota and its service conditions?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a>, <a href="/azure-cloud-assistant/">Cloud Assistant APP</a> and PowerShell all provide the service conditions of the Azure quota resources. Refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/commerce/quota-increase/aog-commerce-quota-increase-process#%E6%B3%A8%E6%84%8F%E4%BA%8B%E9%A1%B9">How to View Azure Quota Resources</a> for specific steps.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-3-27" href="#q-3-27">Can I apply for the Azure quota resources? And how can I apply for it?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes. You can contact the <a href="/support/contact/">21Vianet support team</a> to submit a service request. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/commerce/quota-increase/aog-commerce-quota-increase-process">How to Apply for Azure Quota Resources</a> for details.</p>
                                                <p>Note: if your quota demand is quite large and urgent, we recommend that you apply for it at least three working days in advance.</p>
												
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
                                </ul>   
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="tab-control-container" id="implementationAndMaintenance">
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">         
                            <div class="more-detail">
                            <h2>MySQL Classic Retirement Customer FAQ</h2>
                            <p>We are ending the MySQL Database on Azure service on December 1st, 2019, which will be replaced by the Azure Database for MySQL service. </p>
                            <p>If you are an existing customer:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>· No interruption of service</li>
                                <li>· You will be automatically migrated to the new service before the end of life of the existing service</li>
                                <li>· Migration will begin on Feb 15th, 2019</li>
                                <li>· Special pricing will be lost when scaled to a different service tier or if server is deleted</li>
                                <li>· You will continue to pay the same price post migration – detailed information about the SKU mapping between the old service and the new service will be published before end of December 2018</li>
                                <li>· No action necessary for now. At a minimum, 30 days prior to your scheduled migration you will receive additional notifications including the exact timeline for your migration</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p>If you are a new customer:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>· You will not be accepted on the “MySQL Database on Azure” service as of the date of this announcement</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question4">Will my total bill increase when moving from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL? </a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>No. Your monthly total bill once on Azure Database for MySQL will be the same as your total monthly bill on MySQL Database on Azure. For example: if you are an MS4 customer currently paying ¥1,071.36 per month for MySQL Database on Azure, you will continue to pay ¥1,071.36 per month once on Azure Database for MySQL.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question5">Will my bill look different after I migrate from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL? How will my bill look different?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>Yes, your bill will look different after we migrated you from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, but your total bill amount will remain the same. Today with MySQL Database on Azure you are charged for the version   you are using (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2), which includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. If you use more storage than is included in this free database capacity, then you are billed ¥0.6116 per GB per month for that excess storage.</p>
                                        <p>After the migration to Azure Database for MySQL, you will be charged for the compute and storage resources you provision. Compute resources are charged per vCore per hour. Storage is charged  per provisioned GB per month. Azure Database for MySQL does not include “free database capacity”. </p>
                                        <p>Let us look at an example that describes how you will be billed before and after you migrate to Azure Database for MySQL: </p>
                                        <p>Let us assume you are using MS5 with 200 GB of storage. MS5 includes 100 GB of “free database capacity”. That makes the bill look like this:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>MS5 server:  ¥2.1613 per hour x 744 hours per month = ¥1,608.01 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage Overage: ¥0.6116 per GB per month x (200 GB used – 100 GB free) = ¥61.16 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,608.01 per month + ¥61.16 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>During the migration to Azure Database for MySQL the MS5 server will migrate to General Purpose 4 vCore with 200 GB provisioned storage.  The pricing look as follows:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Compute: ¥0.5198 per vCore per hour x 4 vCore x 744 hours per month = ¥1,546.85 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage: ¥0.6116 per GB per Month x 200 GB = ¥122.32 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,546.85 per month + ¥122.32 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>So in this example, the total monthly bill for MySQL Database on Azure MS5 and the equivalent offer on Azure Database for MySQL is the same.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question7">How will you maintain my total bill if you are charging for storage?</a>
                                 <section>
                                        <p>MySQL Database on Azure includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. This free database capacity varies by version (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2).</p>
                                        <p>Azure Database for MySQL does not include free storage. Instead Azure Database for MySQL charges for compute in vCores per hour and provisioned storage  in GB per month separately. Each MySQL Database on Azure migrated to Azure Database for MySQL will be provisioned with a minimum storage size equivalent to the free database capacity for MySQL Database on Azure. For example, if you are an MS1 customer, your database will be provisioned with a minimum of 100 GB of storage.</p>
                                        <p>To maintain the same total monthly bill for customers who have migrated from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, migrated customers will be billed using a special “legacy” compute and storage meters that maintain your total monthly bill. These “legacy” meters are priced to offset the loss of the “free database capacity” included in MySQL Database on Azure.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question8">What happens if I notice an increase in my total bill?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You should not see an increase in your total monthly bill. If you do, please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">open a support ticket</a> so that the team can investigate.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question9">How will my server be mapped to the new offering?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We have published detailed meter mapping information <a href="https://www.azure.cn/en-us/support/announcement/mysql-china-meter-migration-table-201812">here</a> for your reference.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question10">When will my server be migrated?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You will get an email notification at least 30 days prior to the date your server is scheduled to migrate. Migrations will not start before Feb 15th, 2019.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question11">How will the billing meters be mapped?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We have published detailed meter mapping information <a href="https://www.azure.cn/en-us/support/announcement/mysql-china-meter-migration-table-201812">here</a> for your reference.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question12">Do I have to migrate myself or will you provide assistance to migrate?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You do not have to take any action, your MySQL server will be migrated for you. You will receive another communication with additional details 30 days prior to your scheduled migration. Please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">file a support ticket</a> if you wish to be migrated earlier.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question13">What if I migrate to using a mysqldump and mysqlrestore?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You can migrate using mysqldump and mysqlrestore, however you will not be able to maintain use the legacy meters put in place to maintain your exact current price points. You will be billed using new pricing model.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question14">What happens if I want to change the performance level after I migrate (ex: I have migrated to a General Purpose 4 vCore from MS5, and then want to upgrade to General Purpose 8 vCore)?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>If you decide to increase your database size once on Azure Database for MySQL after you have migrated, you will no longer receive the “legacy” prices, but will migrate to the Azure Database for MySQL prices as displayed <a href="https://www.azure.cn/en-us/pricing/details/mysql/">here</a>.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>

                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question15">What is the experience during the migration?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>The impact to your server and workload will be minimal. We migrate server from MySQL Database for Azure to the new Azure Database for MySQL using replication. This means that the server will be online during the migration except for the final phase of the migration that includes the failover to the new server. The connection string to the server will remain the same, so that you do not have to change your application logic. </p>
                                        <p>Below are the migration steps in short:</p>
                                        <ol>
                                            <li>We take a snapshot of the server in MySQL Database for Azure.</li>
                                            <li>We restore that snapshot in a new Azure Database for MySQL server.</li>
                                            <li>Set up replication between the old and the new server to catch up all changes since the snapshot.</li>
                                            <li>When the new server is caught up except for in-flight transactions, we set the old server to read-only mode for new transactions.</li>
                                            <li>The new server catches up with the latest changes and we stop the replication.</li>
                                            <li>We then copy configurations, firewall rules and redirect DNS from the old to the new server and finally stop the old server. </li>
                                            <li>All new connections to against the new server. No changes to your application are required.</li>
                                        </ol>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            </ul>
                                <h2>Other Technical FAQ</h2>
                                <ul>
                                    
                                    <!-- <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-1" href="#q-4-1">During the maintenance period, how long will a single IaaS virtual machine or single PaaS role instance stay offline?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>
                                                    Answer: For IaaS Virtual Machine or PaaS role instance, it requires about 15 minutes for self-service maintenance, and 30–45 minutes for planned maintenance.
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li> -->
                                    <!-- <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-2" href="#q-4-2">If my Virtual Machine is impacted for a relatively short time, can I define the maintenance time on my own?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>
                                                    Answer: Yes. For maintenance requiring restarting the virtual machine, customers will be informed by the system in advance. The planned maintenance has two stages: self-service maintenance by the user and maintenance by the system. Customers can check the status of the virtual machine, start self-service maintenance and restart the virtual machine in the self-service maintenance stage. Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/maintenance-and-updates">Maintenance and Updates for Azure Virtual Machines and Maintenance in the Plan</a> for more information about the maintenance of virtual machines.
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li> -->
                                    <!-- <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-3" href="#q-4-3">Can I opt to have my virtual machine exit this maintenance?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>
                                                    Answer: You may achieve this by shutting down the virtual machine during the whole maintenance stage.
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li> -->
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-4" href="#q-4-4">What measures should I take to reduce the impact and risk on production applications caused by this maintenance?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>
                                                    Answer: We recommend that you use the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/virtual-machines-linux-manage-availability">Availability Set</a> in the architecture to ensure continuity of business. For Cloud Services and Virtual Machines in an Availability Set, maintenance updates only one instance of an Update Domain (UD). We also encourage customers to cooperate with Microsoft contacts (sales field staff, technical account managers, etc.) on Availability Set. For more information, please visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/virtual-machines-linux-manage-availability">Virtual Machine Management Availability</a> web page.
                                                </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-5" href="#q-4-5">Why can’t I access the VIP IP address and ports of Azure VM from the local Ping?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>When accessing a virtual machine via a VIP address, network traffic needs to go through Azure Load Balancer. Azure Load Balancer currently blocks the ICMP protocol. Ping belongs to the ICMP protocol group and cannot get through the Load Balancer. If customers need to verify the connectivity of virtual machines via VIP, they can do it with tools based on TCP Protocol. For more information, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/virtual-network/aog-virtual-network-tcp-psping-paping-connectivity">Using the PsPing &amp; PaPing for TCP port connectivity testing</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-6" href="#q-4-6">Can I create a virtual machine inside Azure Virtual Machine?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The Dv3 and Dv3 VM sizes support nested virtualization. Both VM sizes are available on China East2 and China North2 region.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-7" href="#q-4-7">Can I create a Windows Server 2003 virtual machine in Azure?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The officially supported Windows Server virtual machine templates are:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Windows Server 2008 R2</li>
                                                    <li>Windows Server 2012, Windows Server 2012 R2</li>
                                                    <li>Windows Server 2016</li>
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>Customers can create their own virtual machine template locally on Hyper-V for Server 2003 and upload it to Azure cloud, but Microsoft does not provide official support if there’s any problem with virtual machines created this way.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-8" href="#q-4-8">Is it supported to deploy Microsoft Exchange, Lync and Sharepoint in Azure? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The SharePoint Virtual Machine templates can be selected from Azure Virtual Machine templates and can be officially supported by Microsoft. Exchange Server and Lync Server can be customized and uploaded, but not officially supported.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-9" href="#q-4-9">What is the load balancing mechanism?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure Load Balancer is based on the fourth layer protocols (TCP, UDP), serving to distributing incoming traffic to the well-operating service instances defined in a load-balancing set, so as to improve the availability and network performance of applications.</p>
                                                <p>Azure Load Balancer can be configured to:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>perform load balancing on Internet traffic going to the virtual machine. This configuration is called <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/load-balancer/load-balancer-internet-overview">Internet-facing load balancing</a>.</li>
                                                    <li>perform load balancing on network traffic among virtual machines in the virtual network, network traffic among virtual machines in the Cloud Services, or network traffic between local computers and cross-premises virtual networks. And this configuration is called <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/load-balancer/load-balancer-internal-overview">Internal Load Balancer</a>.</li>
                                                    <li>forward external traffic to designated virtual machines.</li>
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>For more details about Azure Load Balancer, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/load-balancer/load-balancer-overview">Overview of the Azure Load Balancer</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-10" href="#q-4-10">How do I perform data backup?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure backup provides two types of redundancy: Local Redundant Storage (LRS) and Geo-Redundant Storage (GRS). Local Redundant Storage copies the data in the matching data centers of the same region three times (creating three data copies). Geo-Redundant Storage copies the data to a secondary region several kilometers from the primary location of the source data. In order to prevent temporary storage unavailability arising from a disaster in one region, we recommend that customers back up their data using Read/Access Geo-Redundant Storage (RA-GRS). This way, in case of unavailability of the storage account of the primary region, the data can be accessed from the secondary region.</p>
                                                <p>The following table describes backup and disaster recovery capabilities of different data services in Azure, as well as the corresponding backup methods:</p>
                                                <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                        
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Service Name</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Local data redundancy mode</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Local backup</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Remote data mirroring</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Backup methods</strong></th>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>Storage service</td>
                                                        <td>3 copies, Active-Active</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>Asynchronous replication to the remote location, no RTO</td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Local Redundant Storage (LRS)</li>
                                                                <li>Geo-Redundant Storage (GRS)</li>
                                                                <li>Read/Access Geo-Redundant Storage (RA-GRS)</li>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/storage/aog-storage-how-to-use-azcopy">Use AzCopy</a></li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>SQL Database</td>
                                                        <td>3 copies, one master and two backups</td>
                                                        <td>No (new function in development)</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/sql-database-export">Use Azure portal</a></li>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/sql-database-export">Use SQLPackage utilities</a></li>
                                                                <li><a href="//github.com/richorama/SQLDatabaseBackup">Use SQLDatabaseBackup scripts</a></li>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/sql-database-export">Use PowerShell</a></li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>IaaS virtual machine OS disk and mounted disk</td>
                                                        <td>Only preserves data, same as storage service</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>Only preserves data, same as storage service</td>
                                                        <td>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/backup-recovery">Azure Backup</a></li>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/backup-recovery">Azure Site Recovery</a></li>
                                                                <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/backup-recovery">Managed Snapshot</a></li>
                                                                <li>Database in IaaS virtual machines. Customers can use various database backup tools or back up the file by exporting the database</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>IaaS virtual machine temporary disk</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>PaaS Cloud Services, mobile services and Web Apps</td>
                                                        <td>Only preserves published packages and code</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td>None</td>
                                                        <td><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/app-service/web-sites-backup">Backup options on the Azure portal application page </a></td>
                                                    </tr>
                                                </table>
                                                
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-11" href="#q-4-11">Can I specify regions for VIP addresses when creating related services (Cloud Computing)?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>VIP address is determined in accordance with the selected region of the services being created and is randomly assigned from the IP address pool managed by Microsoft. For instance, if the customers choose China North, they will be preferentially assigned within an IP address in China North.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-12" href="#q-4-12">What should I be aware of when running a business application on a virtual machine?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure will regularly update the host environment to ensure that all the applications and virtual machines on the platform are always in a secure environment.</p>
                                                <p>There may be data lost during virtual machine migration. Some reasons for virtual machine migration are as follows:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Adjusting the size of the virtual machine</li>
                                                    <li>Updating the host</li>
                                                    <li>Hardware failure on the host</li>
                                                    <li>User configures AutoScale for automatic expansion and contraction</li>
                                                    
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>In order to guarantee high availability of applications/services hosted in Azure virtual machines, we recommend:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li><p>1. Use multiple virtual machines in an Availability Set.</p></li>
                                                    <li><p>2. Deploy high availability structure for all components (front-end interface/application logic/data storage, etc.) of the pplications; Deploy each component on multiple virtual machines in Availability Sets, so that any individual virtual machine involved in the application deployment going offline does not bring the entire system offline.</p></li>
                                                    <li><p>3. After the key business applications are deployed to Azure Virtual Machines, test the applications thoroughly for the potential impact of virtual machine reboot.</p></li>
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>For more information, please refer to the following links:</p>
                                                <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/manage-availability">Manage Availability of Windows Virtual Machine on Azure</a></p>
                                                <p><a href="//blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/azchina/2014/04/18/azure-vm/">Why are Azure VMs rebooted ?</a></p>
                                                <p><a href="/support/faq/">Service Level Agreement</a></p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-13" href="#q-4-13">What should I be aware of about using virtual machines to store application data?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure Virtual Machine disks include a temporary disk, the D: disk (Windows) or /dev/sdb1 (Linux). They only provide temporary storage, so there is a risk of data loss, and the data cannot be completely recovered under some conditions. It is recommended against to use the disk to store data that require long term preservation, otherwise users must bear the risk of data lost resulting from this. Data loss on temporary disk usually occurs when virtual machines are migrated to different hosts. Reasons for virtual machine migration include: adjustment of virtual machine size, host update, or failures in host hardware. Exact time of virtual machine migration cannot be predicted, and it is very likely to occur without any user operation. For more information on virtual machine disks and high availability, refer to the following links:</p>
                                                <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/about-disks-and-vhds">About disk storage of Azure Windows VM</a></p>
                                                <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/manage-availability">Manage Availability of Windows Virtual Machine on Azure</a></p>
                                                <p><a href="//blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/azchina/2014/04/18/azure-vm/">Why are Azure VMs rebooted ?</a></p>
                                                <p><a href="/support/faq/">Service Level Agreement</a></p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-14" href="#q-4-14">How do I add virtual machines into a virtual network? What is the difference whether or not adding virtual machines into a virtural network? And how do I put an existing virtual machine into a new virtual network? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>First, create a virtual network; select the previously-created virtual network when creating a virtual machine; add the virtual machine to the virtual network. For detailed steps, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-network/virtual-network-get-started-vnet-subnet">How to Add the Virtual Machines to the Virtual Network</a>.</p>
                                                <p>When adding into virtual networks, virtual machines can guaranteed to communicate with each other via intranet, and advanced functions, such as P2S and S2S VPN, can be configured.</p>
                                                <p>If a virtual machine is not added to a virtual network during creation, it cannot be added to a virtual network later. Currently, the only approach is to delete the virtual machine (select to save the data disks), create a new virtual machine from the previously saved data disk, and choose to join an existing virtual network during the creation.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-15" href="#q-4-15">What are the supported versions of customized Windows OS and Linux OS on Azure?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>For details, please refer to: <a id="FAQ-31" href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/create-vm-specialized/">Create a Windows VM from a designated disc</a> and <a id="FAQ-32" href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/linux/endorsed-distros/">Linux Release Versions Accepted by Azure</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-16" href="#q-4-16">List of validated local network VPN devices that are compatible with Azure Site to Site VPN?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Please refer to <a id="FAQ-33" href="//docs.azure.cn/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-vpn-devices/">Site to Site VPN</a> for details.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-17" href="#q-4-17">How to configure websites deployed in Azure virtual machine to be accessible from public networks?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>By default, Azure virtual machines only open limited ports corresponding to its VIP, used for remote connection or management. If a newly built website needs to be accessed via a certain port of a VIP, it is required to add an Endpoint to this virtual machine. This operation can be completed through Azure portal or Powershell.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-18" href="#q-4-18">What is  availability set? How do I use availability set to increase the availability of applications? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Availability set is a type of logical grouping function. Applying it in Azure ensures that VM resource are mutually isolated after deployment. </p>
                                                <p>Azure can ensure that the VM deployed in availability sets can run across multiple physical hosts, computer racks, storage units and network switches. In case of hardware failure, Azure software issue, or VM and applications update, only part of the VM will be affected and the applications as a whole can maintain functional for users.</p>
                                                <p>For more details, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/training/azure-iaas-user-manual-part1">Azure IaaS User Manual</a> and <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/tutorial-availability-sets">How to use Availability Set</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-19" href="#q-4-19">How about the security of the Azure Storage service?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Azure Storage provides a comprehensive set of security capabilities. You can:</p>
                                                <ol>
                                                    <li>Secure the storage account by using Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) and Azure Active Directory.</li>
                                                    <li>Secure data in transit between an application and Azure by using client-side encryption, HTTPS, or SMB 3.0.</li>
                                                    <li>Set data to be automatically encrypted when it's written to Azure Storage by using Storage Service Encryption.</li>
                                                    <li>Set OS and data disks used by virtual machines (VMs) to be encrypted by using Azure Disk Encryption.</li>
                                                    <li>Grant delegated access to the data objects in Azure Storage by using shared access signatures (SASs).</li>
                                                </ol>
                                                <p>You may refer to<a href="//docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/security-storage-overview/"> Azure Storage security overview</a>for the latest information.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-20" href="#q-4-20">What is the difference between Azure SQL Database and the traditional SQL Server Database? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Though SQL Server and Azure SQL Database sometimes handle the same application working load, one is a traditional database server under the software licensing model, while the other one is under the service-model cloud database running in the data center of <span>21Vianet</span>, and is available as a pay-as-you-go model or a commitment rate model. You can easily choose the platform and business model that best suits your technological requirements between these two products.</p>
                                                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>SQL Server</strong></th>
                                                        <th align="left"><strong>Azure SQL Database</strong></th>
                                                    </tr>
                                                    <tr>
                                                        <td>SQL Server is an enterprise-level database server, which is able to provide "vertical scalable" relational data storage and handle a wide-range of internally deployted applications and scenarios. SQL Server is not a service product and does not use a pay-as-you-go consumption model. SQL Server is licensed per server or per processor, and involves a rich set of server hardware. SQL Server runs on the hardware in your data center or your hosting provider's data center.</td>
                                                        <td>Azure SQL Database is a highly-available distributed "horizontal scalable" database service, hosted in the Cloud operated by 21Vianet. With Azure SQL Database, users can easily configure and deploy the relational database as a service. Developers or administrators do not have to install, configure, patch or manage any software. This service has built-in high availability, backup and recovery, geographical distribution, and disaster recovery.<br><br>In addition to the difference between vertical/horizontal scaling, there are major differences in operating modes. Azure SQL Database service covers management of hardware and operating system, and therefore users can focus on building the solutions instead of purchasing, managing, patching, and licensing the hardware, virtual machines, operating systems and application platform software. However for the dedicated database servers (whether installed as traditional servers in on-premises deployment, hosted in the virtual machine, or hosted by the third-party service provider), developers and IT professionals are still responsible for installing, configuring, updating, and patching the operating system and database software. Furthermore, users of the database server must design their own solutions for high availability, vertical scaling and disaster recovery, resulting in increased overall management costs.<br><br>Azure SQL Database is targeted at designing and optimizing applications towards high scalability and high availability at a lower cost than a traditional vertical-scaling structure. As a result, Azure SQL Database is able to provide highly-available vertical-scaling solutions on commercial hardware and provide database functions as a service.</td>
                                                    </tr>   
                                                </table>
                                                <p>For more details, please refer to the <a id="FAQ-35" href="https://www.azure.cn/blog/2010/05/24/sql-azure-vs-sql-server">SQL Azure</a> web page.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-21" href="#q-4-21">How is Azure’s data redundancy guaranteed?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>We provide geo-redundancy. One dedicated line is used to connect the two data centers in Beijing and Shanghai. It is dedicated to data synchronization between the data centers. In terms of data storage, Azure provides four redundancy levels for storage:</p>
                                                <ul>
                                                    <li>Local Redundant Storage (LRS): we maintain multiple data replica in a region so as to provide high durability.</li>
                                                    <li>Geo-Redundant Storage(GRS): we provide extra data durability through asynchronous replication between two regions hundreds of miles apart. In the two regions, we maintain multiple data replicas.</li>
                                                    <li>Read-Access Geo-Redundant Storage (RA-GRS): in addition to GRS services, we provide read-only access to the storage account in the secondary region (which has a final edition consistent with data in the primary region). When the storage account in the primary region is not available, customers can use this service to access the data.</li>
                                                </ul>
                                                <p>For details on Azure Redundant Storage, please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/storage/common/storage-introduction">Introduction to Azure Storage</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/">Pricing Details</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-4-22" href="#q-4-22">Are there any other detailed self-help information on Azure hot topics?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You may refer to<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/azure-operations-guide/"> Azure Operations Guide</a>(Chinese) for Azure common questions and instructions.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                </ul>   
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
					<div class="tab-control-container" id="wd-support">
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                            <div class="more-detail">
                                <h2>Online Purchase Customer Support</h2>
                                <h3>Azure Support Overview</h3>
								<ul>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-1" href="#q-5-1">For which languages does 21Vianet provide support? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>21Vianet provides support in two languages: Chinese and English.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
									<li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-2" href="#q-5-2">Do I get 24x7 support?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>21Vianet provides 24x7 technical support in Chinese and English for severity A only. Severity A support is available only to customers who have signed the 21Vianet Online Services Advanced Agreement (purchase services through the sales team).</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-3" href="#q-5-3">What is considered local business hours for support? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>For China, business hours are defined as 9:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M Beijing time during week days (weekends and holidays are excluded). </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-4" href="#q-5-4">What kind of support will I get from 21vianet technical support team? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>21vianet technical support team will provide you with break-fix and limited advisory support. Break-fix issues are technical problems you experience while using Azure services. "Break-fix" is an industry term that refers to “work involved in supporting a technology when it fails in the normal course of its function, which requires intervention by a support organization to be restored to working order." Limited advisory support generally includes answers to common questions and best practices sharing. </p>
                                                <p>For customer specific architectural support such as design reviews, performance tuning, code optimization and personalized configuration, please get support from Premier service. You can contact your account manager to learn how to purchase.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-5" href="#q-5-5">What is a Public Preview service or feature? Will it be supported?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Public Preview services or features are available to Azure subscribers through the Azure Portal, these services are intended to be used as an early-look into what is coming and as a chance to test upcoming services and features. Public Preview services or features are identified by “Preview” tag in the Azure Portal and Azure.cn product page.</p>
                                                <p>When you’re offered early access to Azure preview services and features, they are subject to reduced or different service terms as set forth in your service agreement and the preview supplemental terms. Preview Services and Features are provided “as-is”, “with all faults”, and “as available”, and are excluded from the Service SLAs or any Limited Warranties provided for Azure Services released to general availability (GA), and are made available to you on the condition that you agree to these terms of use, which supplement your agreement governing use of Azure. 21Vianet provides support from Public Preview service or feature.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <h3>Using Azure Support</h3>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-6" href="#q-5-6">How do I contact Azure Support? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Our<a href="/support/contact/">contact support page </a>provides all avaible entrances to Azure support. You can easily get access to Azure Support by submitting a support request online or via mobile (app), contacting support through WeChat account or calling 21Vianet hotline. </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-7" href="#q-5-7">Why is submitting a request online the preferred method of contacting Azure Support? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Submitting support requests online allows support team to deliver fast and deep technical expertise in the most effective and efficient manner possible. Due to the detailed nature of the requests, it is much easier to provide relevant information online, compared to reading this information over the phone. This model also eliminates unproductive hold time for a simple, intuitive online process. As a result, customer problems are routed more quickly, to the most qualified engineer.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-8" href="#q-5-8">Is there a phone number I can call to contact the Azure Support? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Contacting Azure Support over the phone will not speed up the processing of your request and you will get a much better and faster experience by submitting support requests online. If you cannot submit a request online, please call 21V service hotline: 400-089-0365.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-9" href="#q-5-9">How do I submit a support request? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <pYou can submit online (or via mobile) support request directly from<a href="//support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">here</a>.                                             Also, you will be redirected to online support from “<a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Help + support</a>”blade in Azure Management Portal. Visit<a href="/support/contact/">contact support page</a>for all avaible entrances to Azure support. </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-10" href="#q-5-10">How do I submit a support request if I cannot log in to the management portal? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can submit online (or via mobile) support request directly from<a href="//support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">here</a>. Refer to<a href="/support/contact/">contact support page</a>for all avaible entrances to Azure support.  </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-11" href="#q-5-11">How do I get support if I don’t have an Azure subscription yet, and I get an error message while creating one? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>You can open a Subscription Management support request from<a href="//support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">here</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-12" href="#q-5-12">What is Initial Response Time and how quickly can I expect to hear back from someone after submitting my support request?  </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Initial Response Time is the period from when you submit your support request to when a Support Engineer contacts you and starts working on your support request. The Initial Response Time varies with the Business Impact of the request (also known as Severity).</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-13" href="#q-5-13">How quickly will you resolve my support request?  </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>21 Vianet is committed to assist you in resolving your issue as soon as possible. Sometimes that means focusing efforts on reducing the business impact and mitigating any negative impact to your operation, before moving to a full solution. Therefore, 21Vianet make a commitment to Initial Response Time and also in working with you until the impact of your issue is mitigated, having no direct SLA for support request resolution. The time it takes to troubleshoot and resolve a support request varies greatly based on the specifics of the issue. Support engineer will work with you to get the issue resolved as fast as possible.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-14" href="#q-5-14">I’m running a non-Microsoft technology on Azure or a custom application built using Open Source Software (OSS). Will it be supported? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Customers can run non-Microsoft technologies on the Azure platform, including but not limited to Linux, Oracle, SAP, and IBM. For all scenarios that are eligible for support, 21V Support team will help in isolating the issue between the Azure Service and your custom application.</p>
                                                <p>Full technical support will be provided if the issue is determined to be caused by an Azure service or platform. Commercially reasonable support will be provided to all other scenarios. When an adequate solution to your issue is not achieved, you might be referred to other support channels that are available for the non-Microsoft software.</p>
                                                <p>For open source code, please refer to <a id="FAQ-8" href="//github.com/Azure?utf8=%E2%9C%93&q=azure-sdk&type=&language=">Microsoft Azure SDK</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-15" href="#q-5-15">	How do I get support during an Outage or Service Interruption Event (SIE)? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>During a SIE (Service Outage), 21Vianet provides frequent and timely updates to the <a href="/support/service-dashboard/">Azure Service Dashboard</a>. This is the best way to receive the latest information. You can also <a href="/support/contact/">chat</a>through WeChat account with a support engineer who will work with you to determine whether your issue is related to an ongoing SIE.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-16" href="#q-5-16">Can I request a Root-Cause Analysis (RCA)?  </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>If you have opened an Azure technical support case and need an RCA, you can request one.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <h3>Azure Support for Enterpise/Premier </h3>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-17" href="#q-5-17">How do I purchase an Enterprise contract?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Please consult Purchase Process section in this article:<a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/articles/azure-china-purchasing-guidance/go-china-playbook-ospa-purchase-process">Enterprise Purchase Process</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-5-18" href="#q-5-18">What if I already have a Premier contract and I want to learn more about how to get the most from it? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Contact your Technical Account Manager (TAM) to discuss options for best utilizing your existing Premier support agreement or rightsizing your Premier agreement to better suit your Azure needs.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                </ul> 
							</div>			
						</div>
					</div>
                    <div class="tab-control-container" id="ea-support">
                        <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                            <div class="more-detail">
                                <h2>Enterprise Customer Support</h2>
                                <h3>Azure Support Overview</h3>
                                <ul>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-1" href="#q-6-1">I have purchased one OSPA contract. How do I log in EA portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Please log in <a href="https://ea.azure.cn/">EA Portal</a>with your account in contract and password.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-2" href="#q-6-2">How should I create one account which has the same domain name with Enterprise Administrator?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>3 steps need to be done to create such account:</p>
                                                <p>Step1: Log in<a href="https://portal.partner.microsoftonline.cn ">O365 Portal</a>with your Enterprise Administrator to create one new account.</p>
                                                <p>Step2: Log in EA portal with your Enterprise Administrator and then add your new account just creating in O365 portal in ‘Account’ .</p>
                                                <p>Step3: Log in EA portal with your new account and add subscriptions for the new account.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>

                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-3" href="#q-6-3">What is Account Owner?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The person identified to manage subscriptions and service administrators on Microsoft Azure. They also have the ability to view usage data on this account and its associated subscriptions.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-4" href="#q-6-4">What is Enterprise Administrator?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The person(s) identified to manage departments and department owners and accounts and account owners on Microsoft Azure. They also have the ability to manage enterprise administrators and view usage data, billed quantities and unbilled charges across all accounts and subscriptions associated with the enterprise enrollment.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-5" href="#q-6-5"> What is Amendment Subscription?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>A single one year or coterminous subscription under the Enrollment Amendment.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-6" href="#q-6-6">How to add subscriptions?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>(1)  If you purchased the OSPA contract just now, the first subscription should be added in EA Portal. The step is: log in EA portal and select ‘Manage’- Subscription-add subscription.</p>
                                                <p>(2)  Log in <a href="https://account.windowsazure.cn">Account center</a>and click subscription- add subscription.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-7" href="#q-6-7"> Can I cancel my subscriptions by myself?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes, you can.  You should log in your <a href="https://account.windowsazure.cn">Account center</a>and select the subscription that you want to cancel and then cancel it. If you would like to reactive the subscription, please contact 21V customer service support for help.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-8" href="#q-6-8"> How can I delete my account in EA Portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Log in EA Portal and click ‘Manage-Account-select account-delete account’.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-9" href="#q-6-9">  How should I change my subscription name and account contact details?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>There are 2 ways to edit your subscription name and account contact details.</p>
                                                <p>(1)  Log in <a href="https://portal.azure.cn/"> Azure portal </a>and click subscription to edit the name.</p>
                                                <p>(2)  Log in<a href="https://account.windowsazure.cn">Account center </a> to edit both subscription name and account contact details.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-10" href="#q-6-10"> How to add department in EA Portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Log in EA Portal and click’ Manage-Department-add department’.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-11" href="#q-6-11"> If I have one 1RMB Trail account, PIA account and  EA Trail account, can I upgrade these accounts to EA Enterprise accounts?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Yes, you can. You should log in EA portal with your Enterprise Administrator and add these accounts in ‘Account’ and then they will be upgraded to EA Enterprise accounts. But, once they have been upgraded to EA Enterprise accounts, they cannot be downgraded to the trail account.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-12" href="#q-6-12"> Where can I find the OSPA purchasing process? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Please view Azure China  <a href="//docs.azure.cn/en-us/articles/azure-china-purchasing-guidance/">Azure Purchasing Guide</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-13" href="#q-6-13"> where should I go to view the notifications published in EA portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> Log in EA Portal and Click the ‘Notification’ in the left Page.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-14" href="#q-6-14">  Is there any documents that introduce the EA Portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> Yes. Please log in EA portal and click ‘Help’ where you can view and download documents.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-15" href="#q-6-15"> Is there any videos to introduce the EA Portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> Yes, please view <a href="/video-center/">video center</a>.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-16" href="#q-6-16"> Where could I check my billing data?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>There are 3 ways to check billing data in EA Portal.</p>
                                                <p>1. View usage summary.</p>
                                                <p>2. Download monthly usage report or advanced usage report.</p>
                                                <p>3. Download usage report through API.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-17" href="#q-6-17"> Is tax included in the EA Portal price list and cost?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>No, it does not include the tax.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-18" href="#q-6-18"> What is Frequency of the Notification of my usage in EA portal?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> Administrator and notification contacts are automatically enrolled to receive notification when the consumption usage meets 50%, 75%, 90% ,100% and 125% of their monetary commitment. Meanwhile, the administrator has the ability to change the frequency of the notification to Daily, Weekly, Monthly or None. Basing on your business requirement, you can select the relevant Notification Frequency.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <h3>Indirect OSPA</h3>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-19" href="#q-6-19">How to pay as an indirect OSPA customer?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Indirect OSPA customers pay directly to partners, all terms and payment methods will be suggested by partner. Partner will issue VAT invoice to customer once payment is completed.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-20" href="#q-6-20"> How to view my Indirect OSPA price?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>For Indirect OSPA, all pricing will be suggested by Indirect partner. 21 Vianet and Microsoft will not provide or engage in customer pricing or billing. Please contact Indirect Partner for more information.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-21" href="#q-6-21">How to pay overage as an Indirect OSPA customer?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> In Indirect OSPA, Customers’ overage will be informed and charged by partner. VAT invoice will be provided by partner after customer paid. The overage service unit price will be the same as the commitment service unit price. Please consult your partners for payment terms, frequency, and methods.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <h3>Credit Check</h3>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-22" href="#q-6-22">Under what circumstances do you need to do credit check?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Before 21Vianet sends out the contract package to customers, credit check is the prerequisite to all enterprise customers to complete.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-23" href="#q-6-23">What materials customer should provide?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>The materials customer should provide includes:</p>
                                                <p>Business license with registered capital；</p>
                                                <p>Tax register certification；</p>
                                                <p>Recent 2 years’ financial report；</p>
                                                <p>Contract details with commitment, payment terms and Microsoft related contact persons (Microsoft team will help to consolidate)</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-24" href="#q-6-24">Do you need to do credit check in next year?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> If the next year annual commitment amount is greater than 150% of previous year, customer need to follow the same process for credit check one more time.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-25" href="#q-6-25">How long credit check will take?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Standard credit check will take 2 working days. </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <h3>EA Trial</h3>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-26" href="#q-6-26"> How to apply Azure EA trail account? </a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p> You need to check with your account manager to apply.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-27" href="#q-6-27">How may subscription can EA trail account have?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Only one subscription.</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                    <!-- <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-28" href="#q-6-28">企业试用订阅的计费周期是自然月吗？还是账单月？</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>计费周期为自然月。</p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li> -->
                                    <li>
                                        <i class="icon icon-plus"> </i>
                                        <div>
                                            <a id="q-6-28" href="#q-6-28">Is there any notification will be sent to customer when subscription going to cancelled?</a>
                                            <section>
                                                <p>Email notification will be sent when credit used by 30%，50%，70%，90%, and also 30days，14days，7days，1days to account expiration. </p>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </li>
                                </ul>
                            </div>          
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
        </div>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Azure FAQ - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Azure, service content, FAQ, general inquiries, registration, billing, subscription and maintenance</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Windows Azure Support FAQ summarize some of the common issues when using Azure and classifies these FAQs into five types: general questions, registration, Billing, subscriptions and Fapiao, Technical, Online Purchase Customer Support, Enterprise Customer Support helping you learn more about the Windows Azure through answering questions.]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>support-faq</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName>FAQ</urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
	<banner><![CDATA[
      <!-- BEGIN: Banner -->
          <div class="common-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#002050', 'backgroundImage':'//wacndevelop.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/support/banner-faq@2x.png','imageHeight':'180'}" id="support-contact-banner">      
            <div class="common-banner-image">
              <div class="common-banner-title">
                <h1>FAQs</h1>
              </div>
            </div>
          </div>  
        <!-- End: Banner-->
    ]]></banner>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate></pageTemplate>
    <localize>0</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <headerText>
      <![CDATA[<div class="_faq-banner">
</div>]]>
    </headerText>
    <forbidPublish>0</forbidPublish>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
