<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-01T16:41:59" urlName="stream-analytics" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="stream-analytics" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/stream_analystics.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/stream-analytics@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Stream Analytics</h2>
                        <h4>Real-time data stream processing from millions of IoT devices</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_site_trial_stream_analytics">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_site_pia_stream_analytics">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Azure Stream Analytics </a>is an event-processing engine in the cloud that uncovers insights from data generated by devices, sensors, cloud infrastructure services, and applications in real time.With out-of-the-box integration for <a id="home_landing_event" class="link-btn_tow" style="color: #00a8d9;"  href="/home/features/event-hubs/" target="_blank">Event Hubs</a>,Azure Stream Analytics can simultaneously ingest and process millions of events per second, and can deliver actionable insights or alerts with ultra-low latencies, rich visual dashboards, and kick off actions to other services.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <!--<p>流分析按处理的数据量以及进行处理所需的流式处理单位数来定价。</p>--> <!-- <p>从2016年4月1日起，价格会下调 25.5%，以下是下调后的新价格：</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"><strong></strong></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Price</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Standard streaming unit</td>
                            <td>￥0.723/hour</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
					<!--<p>自 2017 年 2 月 1 日起，Azure 流分析即将使用全新的定价模型，引入更为丰富的功能。流分析现有用户在 2017 年 12 月 31 之前或当前订阅期结束之前，可以继续使用现有定价模型。订阅到期后，所有流分析作业都将迁移到新的定价模型。</p>-->
                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <!--
						<li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="que-multiple_output_stream_analytics">“处理的数据量”是什么意思？</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>流作业处理的实际数据量。流处理查询可能从事件源中一次或多次读取同一输入事件，这种情况通常在查询具有多个输出和/或多次引用同一输入时发生，此时将引发附加数据量，每次从事件源中读取这些数据时均收取费用。</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
						-->
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>                                
                                <a id="que-api_stream_analytics">What is the streaming unit? </a>
                                
<section>
                                    <p>The streaming unit is a unit of stream processing capacity with a maximum handling capacity of 1MB/s. The number of stream processing units is chosen by the customer through the Azure portal or the stream analytics management API. And the stream processing unit can be used to extend stream processing operations to achieve higher handling capacity. Moreover, more stream processing units may be needed to achieve performance requirements, according to the complexity of the query and the required handling capacity.</p>
                                    <p>Streaming units are billed hourly, based on the maximum number of units selected during this hour..</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>                                
                                <a id="que-influence-flow_stream_analytics">What are the factors affecting the pricing of the stream operations? </a>
<section>
                                    <p>The primary factors that impact streaming units pricing are query complexity, query latency, and the volume of data processed. .</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>                                
                                <a id="que-limit_stream_analytics">Is there a limit on the number of streaming units that can be selected?</a>
                                
<section>
                                    <p>There's no limit on the number of stream units. While the default quota for streaming units per region for a single subscription is 48, you can request a larger number of streaming units by filing a support ticket.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>                                
                                <a id="que-event-center_stream_analytics"> Does the running steam require Event Hubs during operation? </a>
                                
<section>
                                    <p>It is recommended that Event Hubs be used as the transfer center for the scalable event, so as to be regarded as the solution for stream analytics. Currently, stream analytics also supports pulling data from Azure Blob. We may consider integrating with other input sources in the future.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>Stream Analytics service is available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China East, China North</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                
                <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="stream-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<p>We guarantee that availability of the stream analytics API is at least 99.9%.</p>
				<p>We guarantee that the deployed stream analytics operation will process data 99.9% of the time.</p>
				<p>To learn more about the details about our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/stream-analytics/" id="pricing_stream_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
                </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                                    
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Stream Analytics Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-stream-analytics</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Stream Analysis, price, data processing, analysis service, stream processing and 1RMB Trial</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the pricing details of Azure Stream Analytics. Azure Stream Analytics is a real-time cloud service for data analysis. Stream Analytics is priced by the amount of data processed and the number of stream processing units for processing. A 1RMB Trial gets you ￥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer to enjoy a Service Level Agreement of up to 99.99%.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - Stream Analytics</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
