<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-07-24T09:41:59" urlName="hdinsight" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="hdinsight" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/hd_insight.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/hdinsight@2x.png" />
                        <h2>HDInsight<span>HDInsight</span></h2>
                        <h4>Provision cloud Hadoop, Spark, HBase, and Storm clusters</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_hd_trial">Apply for 1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_hd_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>Cloud Hadoop services for business</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Extend to petabyte level as needed</li>
                    <li>Process unstructured and semi-structured data</li>
                    <li>Develop in environments including Java and .NET</li>
                    <li>No need to purchase and maintain hardware</li>
                    <li>Just pay for the services you use</li>
                    <li>Create Hadoop clusters in minutes</li>
                    <li>Present your Hadoop data intuitively in Excel</li>
                    <li>Easily integrate local Hadoop clusters</li>
                </ul>
                <h2>Flexible scaling to your requirements</h2>
                <p>HDInsight is a version of Hadoop driven by cloud technology. This means that the HDInsight architecture can process any quantity of data and you can scale its data processing capacity from terabytes to petabytes as required. You can quickly create any quantity of nodes whenever you want. We will only charge you for the computing and storage that you actually use.</p>

                <h2>Deal with structured, semi-structured and unstructured data all at once</h2>
                <p>As HDInsight complies with the Apache Hadoop standard, it can process unstructured or semi-structured data from sources including website clickstreams, social media, server logs, devices and sensors.</p>

                <h2>Develop in the languages you’re used to</h2>
                <p>HDInsight has powerful programming scalability that works with many languages, including C#, Java and .NET. You can use the programming languages you are familiar with to create, configure, submit and monitor Hadoop jobs.</p>

                <h2>No need to purchase or maintain hardware</h2>
                <p>With HDInsight, you can deploy Hadoop in the cloud without buying new hardware or incurring other startup costs. There is no need to spend lots of time installing or configuring, as Azure can do all this work for you. You can start your first cluster in minutes.</p>

                <h2>Present your Hadoop data intuitively with Excel</h2>
                <p>As HDInsight is integrated with Excel, you can intuitively present and analyze your Hadoop data in tools that enterprise customers are familiar with. Users can select Azure HDInsight as the data source within Excel.</p>
                <p><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/HDInsight-1.png" /></p>

                <h2>Easily integrate local Hadoop clusters with the cloud</h2>
                <p>HDInsight can also be integrated with the Hortonworks data platform, so you can move Hadoop data from onsite datacenters to Azure Cloud and use it for backup, development/testing and cloud bursting. Using the Microsoft Analytics Platform System, you can even simultaneously query local and cloud Hadoop clusters.</p>

                <h2>Includes NoSQL transaction features</h2>
                <p>HDInsight also includes Apache HBase, a type of columnar NoSQL database that runs on the Hadoop Distributed File System (HDFS). This means that you can perform large amounts of online transaction processing (OLTP) for nonrelational data and implement particular use cases, such as enabling interactive websites or sensors to write data into Azure Blob Storage.</p>
                <p><img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/HDInsight-2.png" /></p>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section link-group-container">
                <h1>More</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li><a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/events/TechEd/NorthAmerica/2014/DBI-B328/" id="feature_hdinsight_services_BI_B328">Video: Getting Started with HDInsight</a></li>
                    <li><a href="http://channel9.msdn.com/Events/Build/2014/3-613/" id="feature_hdinsight_services_3_613">Video: Integrate HDInsight with Azure Apps</a></li>
                    <li><a href="http://aka.ms/IntroHDInsight/PDF" id="feature_hdinsight_services_pdf">Introduction to Hadoop HDInsight (E-Book)</a></li>
                    <li><a href="http://hortonworks.com/hdp/" id="feature_hdinsight_hdp">Hortonworks Data Platform</a></li>
                    <li><a href="http://www.microsoft.com/aps" id="feature_hdinsight_aps">Microsoft Analytics Platform System</a></li>
                    <li><a href="https://docs.azure.cn/hdinsight/hdinsight-hadoop-use-blob-storage/" id="feature_hdinsight_blob-storage">Using Azure Blob Storage with HDInsight</a></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->              
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>HDInsight_Hadoop Services_Hadoop Data - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-hdinsight</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, HDInsight, Features, Hadoop, Hosting, Analysis Service, Big Data</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[As part of Azure Analysis Services, HDInsight provides Hadoop hosting, Spark and R clusters in the cloud supported by Azure Service Level Agreements (SLA), allowing you to stay up and running at all times.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>HDInsight</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
