<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2018-06-25T12:00:00" updateDate="2018-08-15T17:00:00" urlName="mysql" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
      <style>
                .cognitive-banner{
                    margin: 30px 0;
                }
                .cognitive-figure{
                    padding-bottom: 30px;
                    margin-bottom: 30px;
                    border-bottom: 1px #ccc solid;
                    overflow: hidden;
                }
                .cognitive-figure .col-md-3{
                    padding-left: 0;
                    padding-right: 0;
                }
                .cognitive-figure .col-md-9{
                    padding-left: 2%;
                    padding-right: 0;
                }
                .pricing-page-section .cognitive-figure .col-md-9 h2, .container .pure-content .pricing-page-section .cognitive-icon-group .cognitive-text h2{
                    margin-top: 4px !important;
                }
                .cognitive-icon-group{
                    margin-top: 20px;
                    margin-bottom: 0;
                    list-style:none;
                    padding-left:0 !important;
                }
                .cognitive-icon-group li{
                    width:100%;
                    overflow:hidden;
                    margin-bottom: 30px !important;
                }
                .cognitive-icon-group li div{
                    float: left;
                }
                .cognitive-icon{
                    width: 10%;
                    min-width: 100px;
                    margin-right:-120px;
                }
                .cognitive-text{                   
                    margin-left:120px;
                }
                .cognitive-icon-group li:last-child{
                    margin-bottom: 0 !important;
                }
                @media only screen and (max-width: 769px){
                    .cognitive-figure{
                        padding-bottom: 20px;
                    }
                    .cognitive-figure .col-md-9{
                        padding-left: 0;
                    }
                    .pricing-page-section .cognitive-figure .col-md-9 h2{
                        margin-top: 26px !important;
                    }
                }
            </style>
           <tags ms.service="mysql" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/mysql-database%20on%20azure.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/mysql_database_on_azure_icon@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Azure <small>Database for MySQL</small></h2>
                        <h4>Trusted MySQL Database services geared toward app developers</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_mysql_trial">Apply for 1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_mysql_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div width="100%" style="background-color:#e5f1fb;margin-bottom:20px;border: 1px solid transparent;border-color: rgba(0,120,215,0.5);padding: 0 15px;">
                    <p>This page is concerning new service content under Azure Database for MySQL. To view legacy MySQL Database on Azure services, please visit <a href="/home/features/mysqldatabaseonazure/">MySQL Database on Azure service features page</a>. </p>
                </div>
                <p>Azure Database for MySQL delivers fully trusted, enterprise-ready Community MySQL database as a service. The MySQL Community edition helps you easily move to the cloud using languages and frameworks of your choice. Most importantly, you will get built-in high availability and dynamic scaling to help you easily adapt to changes in customer demands. In addition, you can benefit from unrivaled security and compliance, including Azure IP advantage and Azure’s industry leading business coverage. All these with a flexible pricing model so that you can choose the resources for your workload without any hidden cost.</p>

                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-01-focus-on.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Community MySQL that’s fully trusted</h2>
                        <p>Combine MySQL Community edition with the advantages of being a fully trusted service provider in order for developers to easily manage infrastructure and database, allowing them to focus on building exceptional applications.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-02-develop-with-ease.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Languages and frameworks of your choice</h2>
                        <p>Azure Database for MySQL supports popular open source frameworks and languages, offering tight integration with Azure Web applications. Popular content management applications (such as WordPress and Drupal) deliver a fully integrated experience supporting your application development demands.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-03-availability.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Built-in high availability</h2>
                        <p>Trust Azure to keep your enterprise applications running continuously. Azure Database for MySQL offers high availability (99.99% SLA) to ensure your applications run as per normal when needed without extra configuration, replication or cost.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-04-scale-on-the-fly.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Scale within seconds</h2>
                        <p>Provision within minutes and scale compute or storage with independence and flexibility within seconds.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-05-pay-one-simple.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Simple and flexible pricing</h2>
                        <p>Enjoy everything you need with simple and flexible pricing. Azure Database for MySQL delivers all capabilities you need, including capabilities such as automatic database patching, automatic backup, built-in monitoring, security, and more, at no extra cost.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="cognitive-figure">
                    <div class="col-md-3">
                        <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-06-rest-assured.png">
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-9">
                        <h2>Unrivaled security and coverage</h2>
                        <p>Run your app on top infrastructure and the world’s most trusted cloud. Azure Database for MySQL is a fully integrated service that offers you Microsoft global network of datacenters, unrivaled security and round-the-clock monitoring.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
                <div class="pricing-page-section">
                    <h1>What can you build with Azure Database for MySQL?</h1>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <!-- <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-02.png">
                        </div> -->
                        <div class="col-md-12">
                            <h2>Intelligent applications</h2>
                            <p>Use the state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms and integrated visualization tools to develop complex and transformational applications to obtain actionable insights and analysis.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-02.png">
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <h2>Retail and e-commerce</h2>
                            <p>Build secure, scalable e-commerce solutions that meet the demands of both customers and businesses. Engage customers with customized products and offers, process transactions quickly and securely and focus on product delivery and customer service.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-03.png">
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <h2>Scalable Web and mobile applications</h2>
                            <p>Swiftly build engaging and scalable cross-platform and native applications for iOS, Android, Windows or Mac.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-04.png">
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <h2>Digital marketing</h2>
                            <p>Engage customers around the world with a rich and personalized digital marketing experience. Quickly build and launch automatically scalable digital marketing campaigns based on customer demands.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-06.png">
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <h2>Finance management applications</h2>
                            <p>Securely store critical data and deliver high-value analytics and insights over aggregated data to users, using in-built security and performance.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cognitive-figure">
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <img role="presentation" src="//wacnppe.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/css/images/mysql-pro-05.png">
                        </div>
                        <div class="col-md-6">
                            <h2>Gaming</h2>
                            <p>Flexibly scale databases to accommodate unpredictable bursts of traffic and deliver low latency multi-player experiences.</p>
                            <p><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mysql/">Find out more</a></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand All</em>
                    <h3>MySQL Database on Azure Retirement Customer FAQ</h3>
                    <p>We are ending the MySQL Database on Azure service on December 1st, 2019, which will be replaced by the Azure Database for MySQL service. </p>
                    <p>If you are an existing customer:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>· No interruption of service</li>
                        <li>· You will be automatically migrated to the new service before the end of life of the existing service</li>
                        <li>· Migration will begin on Feb 15th, 2019</li>
                        <li>· Special pricing will be lost when scaled to a different service tier or if server is deleted</li>
                        <li>· You will continue to pay the same price post migration – detailed information about the SKU mapping between the old service and the new service will be published before end of December 2018</li>
                        <li>· No action necessary for now. At a minimum, 30 days prior to your scheduled migration you will receive additional notifications including the exact timeline for your migration</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>If you are a new customer:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>· You will not be accepted on the “MySQL Database on Azure” service as of the date of this announcement</li>
                    </ul>
                        <ul>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question4">Will my total bill increase when moving from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>No. Your monthly total bill once on Azure Database for MySQL will be the same as your total monthly bill on MySQL Database on Azure. For example: if you are an MS4 customer currently paying ¥1,071.36 per month for MySQL Database on Azure, you will continue to pay ¥1,071.36 per month once on Azure Database for MySQL.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question5">Will my bill look different after I migrate from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL? How will my bill look different?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>Yes, your bill will look different after we migrated you from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, but your total bill amount will remain the same. Today with MySQL Database on Azure you are charged for the version you are using (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2), which includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. If you use more storage than is included in this free database capacity, then you are billed ¥0.6116 per GB per month for that excess storage.</p>
                                        <p>After the migration to Azure Database for MySQL, you will be charged for the compute and storage resources you provision. Compute resources are charged per vCore per hour. Storage is charged per provisioned GB per month. Azure Database for MySQL does not include “free database capacity”. </p>
                                        <p>Let us look at an example that describes how you will be billed before and after you migrate to Azure Database for MySQL: </p>
                                        <p>Let us assume you are using MS5 with 200 GB of storage. MS5 includes 100 GB of “free database capacity”. That makes the bill look like this:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>MS5 server: ¥2.1613 per hour x 744 hours per month = ¥1,608.01 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage Overage: ¥0.6116 per GB per month x (200 GB used – 100 GB free) = ¥61.16 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,608.01 per month + ¥61.16 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>During the migration to Azure Database for MySQL the MS5 server will migrate to General Purpose 4 vCore with 200 GB provisioned storage. The pricing look as follows:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Compute: ¥0.5198 per vCore per hour x 4 vCore x 744 hours per month = ¥1,546.85 per month</li>
                                            <li>Storage: ¥0.6116 per GB per Month x 200 GB = ¥122.32 per month</li>
                                            <li>Total Bill: ¥1,546.85 per month + ¥122.32 per month = $1,669.17 per month</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>So in this example, <b>the total monthly bill for MySQL Database on Azure MS5</b> and <b>the equivalent offer on Azure Database for MySQL</b> is the same.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question7">How will you maintain my total bill if you are charging for storage?</a>
                                 <section>
                                        <p>MySQL Database on Azure includes a free amount of storage called “free database capacity”. This free database capacity varies by version (MS1, MS2, MS3, MS4, MS5, MS6, MP1, or MP2).</p>
                                        <p><b>Azure Database for MySQL</b> does not include free storage. Instead Azure Database for MySQL charges for compute in vCores per hour and provisioned storage in GB per month separately. Each MySQL Database on Azure migrated to Azure Database for MySQL will be provisioned with a minimum storage size equivalent to the free database capacity for MySQL Database on Azure. For example, if you are an MS1 customer, your database will be provisioned with a minimum of 100 GB of storage.</p>
                                        <p>To maintain the same total monthly bill for customers who have migrated from MySQL Database on Azure to Azure Database for MySQL, migrated customers will be billed using a special “legacy” compute and storage meters that maintain your total monthly bill. These “legacy” meters are priced to offset the loss of the “free database capacity” included in MySQL Database on Azure. </p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question8">What happens if I notice an increase in my total bill?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You should not see an increase in your total monthly bill. If you do, please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">open a support ticket</a> so that the team can investigate.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question9">How will my server be mapped to the new offering?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We will publish detailed mapping information before end of December 2018.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question10">When will my server be migrated?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You will get an email notification at least 30 days prior to the date your server is scheduled to migrate. Migrations will not start before Feb 15th, 2019.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question11">How will the billing meters be mapped?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>We will publish detailed meter mapping information before end of December 2018.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question12">Do I have to migrate myself or will you provide assistance to migrate?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You do not have to take any action, your MySQL server will be migrated for you. You will receive another communication with additional details 30 days prior to your scheduled migration. Please <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">file a support ticket</a> if you wish to be migrated earlier.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question13">What if I migrate to using a mysqldump and mysqlrestore?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>You can migrate using mysqldump and mysqlrestore, however you will not be able to maintain use the “legacy” meters put in place to maintain your exact current price points. You will be billed using new pricing model.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question14">What happens if I want to change the performance level after I migrate (ex: I have migrated to a General Purpose 4 vCore from MS5, and then want to upgrade to General Purpose 8 vCore)?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>If you decide to increase your database size once on Azure Database for MySQL after you have migrated, you will no longer receive the “legacy” prices, but will migrate to the Azure Database for MySQL prices as displayed <a href="https://www.azure.cn/en-us/pricing/details/mysql/">here</a>.</p>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>

                            <li>
                                <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                <div>
                                    <a id="pricing_mysql_question15">What is the experience during the migration?</a>
                                    <section>
                                        <p>The impact to your server and workload will be minimal. We migrate server from MySQL Database for Azure to the new Azure Database for MySQL using replication. This means that the server will be online during the migration except for the final phase of the migration that includes the failover to the new server. The connection string to the server will remain the same, so that you do not have to change your application logic. Below are the migration steps in short:</p>
                                        <ol>
                                            <li>We take a snapshot of the server in MySQL Database for Azure.</li>
                                            <li>We restore that snapshot in a new Azure Database for MySQL server.</li>
                                            <li>Set up replication between the old and the new server to catch up all changes since the snapshot.</li>
                                            <li>When the new server is caught up except for in-flight transactions, we set the old server to read-only mode for new transactions.</li>
                                            <li>The new server catches up with the latest changes and we stop the replication.</li>
                                            <li>We then copy configurations, firewall rules and redirect DNS from the old to the new server and finally stop the old server.</li>
                                            <li>All new connections to against the new server. No changes to your application are required.</li>
                                        </ol>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More --> <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section link-group-container">
                <h1>了解更多</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <a href="">documnet1</a>
                    </li>
                    
                </ul>
            </div> --> <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->             
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Database for MySQL - fully trusted services - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-mysql</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure Database for MySQL, fully trusted services, trusted services, trusted services provider</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Database for MySQL is a fully trusted database service for app developers. Find a trusted services provider that could meet all your database demands]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Azure Database for MySQL</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
