<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2018-06-12T16:00:00" urlName="sql-data-warehouse" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText>
            <![CDATA[
      
            <tags ms.service="sql-data-warehouse" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/sql_database_warehouse.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/SQL_DW_icon.png" />
                        <h2><!-- <sup style="color: #a5ce00; font-weight: bold; text-transform: uppercase; font-family: '微软雅黑'; font-size: 20px;" class="wa-previewTag">预览 --> </sup>SQL Data Warehouse</h2>
                        <h4>Elastic data warehouse as a service with enterprise-class features</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_warehouse_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_warehouse_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Azure SQL Data Warehouse is a data columnar storage service that is elastic, scalable, fully entrusted and extendable to one trillion bytes. It is completely compatible and integrated with SQL Server ecological system. This is the first cloud data warehouse that allows users to expand or shrink calculating capacity within seconds, which is absolutely exclusive in the industry. SQL Data Warehouse can independently extend or shrink storage and computing capacity, enabling users to pay for querying performance only when needed.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
            <div class="technical-azure-selector tab-control-selector">
                <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="tabContent1">
                    <!-- BEGIN: Table1-Content-->
                    <h2>Pricing Details</h2>
                    <p>Computing and storage are independently charged. Since the usage about computing capacity is displayed in DWU (Data Warehouse Units), the customer can expand or shrink performance as needed through DWU. When data warehouse is not used, computing can be paused so as to save on costs.</p>
                    <!-- <p>存储费率基于标准 <a id="pricing_warehouse_storage" target="_blank" href="/pricing/details/storage/"> RA-GRS 页·Blob 费率</a>。客户只需支付存储的数据，无需存储交易费。</p> --> <!-- <p>Azure SQL 数据仓库现已正式上线，自即日起至 2 月 28 日，将继续按照预览版价格（即以下标准价格的 50%）计费，3 月 1 日起恢复按标准价格计费。</p> -->
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*The following prices are tax-inclusive.</div><br />
                        <div class="ms-date">*Monthly pricing estimates are based on 744 hours of usage per month.</div>
                    </div>
                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                        <tr>
                            <th align="left"></th>
                            <th align="left"><strong>Pricing</strong></th>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>100 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥8.05/hour (about ¥5,989.2/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>200 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥16.1/hour (about ¥11,978.4/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>300 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥24.15/hour (about ¥17,967.6/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>400 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥32.2/hour (about ¥23,956.8/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>500 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥40.25/hour (about ¥29,946.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>600 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥48.3/hour (about ¥35,935.2/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>1,000 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥80.5/hour (about ¥59,892.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>1,200 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥96.6/hour (about ¥71,870.4/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>1,500 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥120.75/hour (about ¥89,838.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>2,000 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥161/hour (about ¥119,784.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
						<tr>
                            <td>3,000 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥241.5/hour (about ¥179,676.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
						<tr>
                            <td>6,000 DWU</td>
                            <td>¥483/hour (about ¥359,352.0/month)</td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    <div class="tags-date">
                        <div class="ms-date">*When Azure SQL Data Warehouse is commonly used, a higher extension limit can be applied.</div>
                    </div>
                    <!-- END: Table1-Content--> <!-- BEGIN: Table2-Content-->
                    <h3>Storage</h3>
					<h3>Data Storage and Snapshots</h3>
                    <p>Data storage service is charged at the rate of <a id="pricing_warehouse_storage" target="_blank" href="/pricing/details/storage/">Azure Premium Storage</a> i.e. ¥906.29/TB/month (¥1.22/TB/hour). Data storage service covers data warehouse storage and 7 days of incremental snapshot storage.</p>
					<p><strong>Note:</strong> Storage transactions are free of charge. In other words, you only need to pay for the data storage service, and no transaction fees are needed.</p>
					<h3>Geo-Redundant Disaster Recovery</h3>
                    <p>Data warehouse can be copied into Geo-Redundant Storage (GRS) for disaster recovery. Storage for Geo-Redundant copies will be charged based on the <a id="pricing_warehouse_storage-disk" target="_blank" href="/pricing/details/storage/">rate</a> of the Azure standard disk RA-GRS rate of ¥1.056/GB/month.</p>
                    <!-- END: Table2-Content-->
                </div>
                <!-- END: TAB-CONTAINER-1 -->
            </div>
            <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
           
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <div class="more-detail">
                    <h2>FAQ</h2>
                    <em>Expand all</em>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_what_is_dwu">What is a DWU (Data Warehouse Unit)?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>The Data Warehouse Unit (DWU) has been introduced into SQL Data Warehouse to offer customers a more predictable performance experience. DWU represents potent query performance and is quantified through workload objectives: how fast you can scan, load, and copy rows. This metric helps customers assess the relative performance required by their SQL Data Warehouse.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_bill">How is SQL Data Warehouse usage reflected in my bill?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>Your bill will be composed of a predictable monthly storage fee and a changeable computing fee. The computing fee may vary from month to month, depending on the amount of used computing resources and duration (DWU). Storage and computing are two separate items on the bill so that you can easily figure out the level of computing resources used.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_one_hour">What if the duration of my DWU usage is less than one hour?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>As long as your database is active (not paused), DWU is charged by the hour. If the activity time of DWU is less than one hour, the bill will reflect the fee for a whole hour. If the database is stopped for one hour, no fees will be charged for that period of time.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_different_levels">What if I use DWUs of different levels within one hour?</a>
                                <section>
                                    <p>DWU will be charged by the hour based on the unit pricing of the highest-grade performance used within the hour.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_pause">What is the pause feature?</a>
                                <section>
                                 <p>SQL Data Warehouse has the exclusive capacity of pausing and recovering computing. If your team does not use the data warehouse instance for a period of time, e.g., at night, on weekends, on holidays or for other reasons, you can pause the data warehouse instances and then choose where you left off after you return. Note: since storage is separate from computing, your storage service will not be paused in such cases. For more information about pauses, please refer to <a id="documentation_warehouse_ms_sql-data-warehouse-performance-scale" href="//docs.azure.cn/sql-data-warehouse/sql-data-warehouse-manage-compute-overview#pausing-compute-resources" target="_blank">Documentation</a>.</p>
                                </section>

                            </div>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                            <div>
                                <a id="warehouse_quation_account">Can I use a regular Azure Storage account together with SQL Data Warehouse?</a>
                                <section>
                                   <p>If you have regular Azure storage account (Web Blob or Block Blob), you should just import it into SQL Data Warehouse by using Polybase. Supported file layouts include texts with separators, Hive RCFile or Hive ORC.</p>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Region</h2>
                <p>SQL Data Warehouse is available in the following regions:</p>
                <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="table-col6">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Territory</strong></th>
                        <th align="left"><strong>Region</strong></th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mainland China</td>
                        <td>China North, China East</td>
                    </tr>
                </table> -->
                
           <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h2>Support &amp; SLA</h2>
                <p>If you have any questions or need help, please visit <a href="/support/contact/" id="warehouse-contact-page">Azure Support</a> and select self-help service or any other method to contact us for support.</p>
				<!--<p>SQL 数据仓库功能预览期间，不提供服务级别协议。若要了解有关我们的服务器级别协议的详细信息，请访问<a href="/support/legal/sla/" id="pricing_sql-database-warehouse_sla">服务级别协议</a>页。</p> -->
				<p>We promise client-side operations performed in SQL Data Warehouse will be successful at least 99.9% of time. To learn more about the details of our Service Level Agreement, please visit the <a href="/support/sla/sql-data-warehouse/" id="pricing_sql-database-warehouse_sla">Service Level Agreements</a> page.</p>
            </div>
                <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <!--<?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="support-and-service" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />--> <!--END: Support and service code chunk--> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                                                                                 
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>SQL Data Warehouse Service Pricing Details - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>pricing-details-sql-data-warehouse</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, Azure SQL Data Warehouse, pricing details, pricing, billing</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Learn about the details of Azure SQL Data Warehouse. Computing and Storage are independently charged. The user only pays for data storage, and no storage transaction fees need to be paid. SQL Data Warehouse offers preview versions at present. The current pricing covers a 50% discount for the preview version. A 1RMB Trial gets you ¥1,500 in service credits. You can also make a direct purchase and become a Pay-in-Advance Azure customer.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Pricing Details - SQL Data Warehouse</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
