<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="302" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2018-08-24T11:34:25">
    <bodyText>
    <![CDATA[
        <p><tags ms.service="legal-en" ms.date="" wacn.date="" wacn.lang="en"/></p>

        <p><div class='language-switch'><ul><li><a href='/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/'>中文</a></li><li class="active"><a href='/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p-en/'>English</a></li></ul></div></p>

        <h1>Offer Details</h1>
        <h2>Azure Operated by 21Vianet</h2>
        <h2>Standard Pay-In-Advance Offer</h2>
        <p>You will receive Azure Credits equal to the amount of funds you add to your account. We offer three types of payment options, Alipay, China UnionPay (CUP), and Wire Transfer. If choosing the first two online payment options, the minimal amount is 1,000 RMB. If paying with Wire Transfer, the minimal amount is 5,000 RMB. Azure Credits are valid for 12 months. Upon using all Azure Credits in your account, your subscription will be suspended and Customer Data will be permanently deleted after 90 days.</p>
        <p>You may purchase additional Azure Credits, which will be valid for 12 months from the date of purchase, but this will not extend Azure Credits previously purchased and any Azure Credits not used within 12 months of their purchase will be forfeited. </p>
        <p>This offer is billed at the standard <a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_overview" href="/pricing/overview/">Pay-In-Advance rates</a>.</p>
        <p>You will be notified at least 30 days in advance of any increases to the Pay-In-Advance rates. New services may be added periodically to the Azure platform. We will notify you of these new services and any fees that might be charged for using them. However, you would only be charged if you elect to use the new services.</p>
        <p><a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_pia" href="/pricing/pia/">Pay In Advance Now &gt;</a></p>
        <p><a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_azure-pia-application-and-signup" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-and-get-a-pia-subscription/">View Pay in Advance Sign-up Guidance &gt;</a></p>
        <h2>Payment Options</h2>
        <p>We offer three types of payment options, Alipay, China UnionPay (CUP), and Wire Transfer. If choosing the first two online payment options, the minimal amount is 1,000 RMB. If paying with Wire Transfer, the minimal amount is 5,000 RMB. The details of Wire Transfer can be found in <a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_azure-wire-transfer-overview" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer/">Wire Transfer details</a>.</p>
        <p>More details on pricing and billing, including the prices for individual Azure features, can be found on our <a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_overview" href="/pricing/overview/">Pricing page</a>.</p>
        <h2>Cancelation Policy</h2>
        <p>You may cancel this subscription at any time but will forfeit any prepaid amounts in your account.</p>
        <h2>Usage Quotas</h2>
        <p>The following monthly usage quotas are applied. If you need more than these limits, please contact <a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_contact" href="/support/contact/">customer service</a> at any time so that we can understand your needs and adjust these limits appropriately.</p>
        <h2>Cloud Services and Virtual Machines</h2>
        <p>The standard quota is 20 concurrent Standard Small (A1) compute instances or an equivalent number of other types or sizes of compute instances as determined by using the compute instance quota conversion table below.</p>
        <table>
        <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>1 COMPUTE INSTANCE IN THE FOLLOWING</th>
            <th>NUMBER OF EQUIVALENT STANDARD SMALL (A1) INSTANCES</th>
        </tr>
        </thead>
        <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Extra Small (A0)</td>
            <td>1</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Small (A1)</td>
            <td>1</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Medium (A2)</td>
            <td>2</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Large (A3) or A6</td>
            <td>4</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Extra Large (A4) or A7</td>
            <td>8</td>
            <td></td>
        </tr>
        </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2>Storage</h2>
        <p>20 concurrent storage accounts</p>
        <h2>Cloud Services</h2>
        <p>20 cloud services accounts. Each cloud services account will have 2 deployment environment: Staging and Production.</p>
        <h2>Active Directory</h2>
        <p>150,000 objects</p>
        <p>An object is an entry in the directory service, represented by its unique distinguished name. An example of an object is a user entry used for authentication purpose.</p>
        <p>If you exceed the above quotas for a given month, you will still be responsible for charges that exceed the quotas. </p>
        <h2>Service Level Agreements</h2>
        <p>We provide a set of robust service level agreements for each of the Azure platform services in General Availability. More details on our SLAs can be found on our SLA page. </p>
        <h2>Resource Commitment</h2>
        <p>Any quota described in the Usage Quotas section is not a commitment that there will be sufficient resources available for you to reach the quota.</p>
        <p>For any subscriptions of this offer that are not incurring charges and are inactive for over 90 days, we reserve the right to remove any compute resources including hosted service(s), virtual machines and websites. Please note that no data would be deleted and customers can redeploy at any time. We will also provide advance notice prior to removing any compute resources.</p>
        <p>You can also avoid having your compute resources removed by doing either of the following every 90 days:</p>
        <p>1.Log into the management <a id="ms-mc-arz-33p-en_manage.windowsazure" href="https://portal.azure.cn/">portal</a></p>
        <p>2.Access your hosted service(s) via our Azure APIs</p>
    ]]>
    </bodyText>
    <redirectURL>/www.azure.cn/en-us/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/</redirectURL>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Offer Details | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription>
        <![CDATA[
            Offer Details - Standard Pay-In-Advance Offer
        ]]>    
    </metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
